Subtitles by explosiveskull
Sync by GoldenBeard
- Are you okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, I like this.
Maybe this time
we get lucky
- and make a baby?
- Let's just have some fun.
Oh, I like fun.
Just shut up and kiss me.
- Ow!
- Sorry.
Hold on.
It's this damn watch.
Come on. Mm-hm.
What's wrong?
You feel that?
No...
Huh. It stopped.
That's weird,
I didn't feel anything.
Hold on!
Babe, are you okay?
Yeah. Okay.
Okay, what the hell was that?
Oh, my God.
Look out there.
What is that?
There he is.
How's our little guy
this morning?
Hello, how are you?
Look at you!
Look, you're all sitting up!
Oh, oh! Kick it!
Look at that big smile!
So happy!
You're
crawling, look Kyle!
Look at him crawl!
Look at these overalls,
he's like a mini you.
Look at you, putting your
little butt in the air.
Yeah, you're gonna work
on the farm like Daddy?
Yes, just like a Breyer!
Okay, I'm gonna turn this off,
- say "bye."
- Bye.
Brandon?
It's time to get ready
for school.
Got ya!
Not even close.
I'm gonna find you.
Better not be in that barn!
You totally got me!
You are getting
too big for this.
You'll always be
my baby boy.
- Okay, let's go.
- Took you long enough
to find me.
- Uh-oh.
- Morning guys.
What're ya doing in there?
I was just hiding.
You know the rules of
the barn, right?
- Yeah, I mean...
- All the boards and nails
and shit, don't want
you breaking your neck.
He was only in there
for, like, two minutes.
Uh-huh.
Did you eat breakfast?
- Not yet.
- Want some waffles?
- Sounds good.
- You're making waffles?
- Yeah.
- What about some bacon?
And that is what we call
a hive.
Wasps and bees,
members of the same
insect family,
both with two pairs
of wings,
both with stingers.
Can anyone tell me any
differences between them?
Mr. Breyer?
Uh, well, um,
bees are pollinators,
and wasps
are predators.
Good, good. Anybody else?
And wasps are more aggressive,
more dangerous.
One species,
the Polistes sulcifer,
is what's called
a brood parasite,
they've lost the ability
to make nests,
so they use brute force
to make other wasp species
raise their young.
And they make them feed
their babies things
like beetle larvae
and maggots.
Bro, why are you always
talking about maggots?
You must be one.
Okay, alright.
Don't worry,
smart guys end up
ruling the planet.
Brandon?
Brandon.
Brandon...
Brandon?
Brandon.
Hey.
Hey! Shh, hey.
- Hey, it's me. It's mom.
- Where... Where am I?
It's mom. Mom. Look at me.
You're all right. Shh, shh, shh.
You're all right.
You were sleepwalking.
I think.
Yeah... it was...
these voices or something.
I know,
it'll be okay now.
You're okay now.
Where's it coming from?
Everything all right?
Yeah, he was, uh...
sleepwalking,
I guess?
Where?
Nowhere. He was
just downstairs.
He's fine.
We should
go to bed, yeah?
It's getting so late.
Hold underneath.
Keep it stiff.
All right, I think
that's gonna hold it.
- Want one of these?
- Sure.
First couple of years
after we adopted you,
I had no clue
how to be a dad.
Your mom, she was
out one day,
and you were
bawling your eyes out.
But I had
a secret weapon.
So you gave me
a piece of candy?
Yep.
- Did it work?
- I guess.
You didn't turn
out that bad, did you?
Huh?
All right. Think you'll
be able to get the lawn?
- I gotta get to the seed store.
- No worries. I'll handle it.
Dang it.
Come on.
Stupid thing!
You're not beating me.
I love it!
You can't go
that close.
What about this brown one?
I feel he's easy to pick up.
You were right in front of it.
- This has to be it.
- Oh! Come on!
There you go.
This is for little kids.
Come on, make a wish,
thank you, Erika.
Didn't know
they were gonna bring it,
If you don't want any,
just slide it over here.
So Brandon, I hear
you're killing it in school.
- Tested in the top one percent.
- No, he tested in the top
one tenth of one percent.
The whole faculty
is talking about him.
He's our little super genius.
So a special guy
deserves a very special present.
This is from me
and your Aunt Merilee.
Go ahead, open it.
I shot my first buck
with that very same model.
Whoa, no, no, no.
No guns.
- We talked about this, Tori.
- I know...
Come on, he's still
just a kid.
I'm 12 years old.
I know, exactly,
you're still a child.
Give it to me.
I'm sorry, what did
you just say to me?
I said, "give it to me."
Brandon.
Okay, we're done here.
We're not having ice cream.
Thank you. Let's go.
Brandon, let's go.
Brandon!
Up now.
Brandon...
Listen to your father.
We are leaving,
let's go.
So fun, thank you so much.
Okay... sorry.
- Don't worry about.
- So sorry.
Nope. Yep, bye.
I love you guys!
Babe, I told you.
You sure you want kids?
I just don't get
that kid.
Turns 12, all of sudden
he gets a mouth on him.
So strange,
it was so unlike him.
I worry about him.
Getting older,
changing.
We were so much worse
when we were his age.
You remember all the running
around we did, sneaking out.
Fooling around in
my parents' basement.
My parents knew
exactly what we were doing.
They didn't give a shit,
they'd already written me off.
Oh, babe.
We can never
do that to Brandon.
He needs to know
we give a shit.
He will.
Why don't we go
camping this weekend?
Just the three of us,
go up to Drywood.
- We haven't done that in so long.
- Mm-hm.
You know what else we
haven't done in a while?
- I know what you're thinking,
- A little bit more...
gone to church. We have
not gone to church in a while.
That's not all
I was thinking about.
We need to clean out
the closet,
- that's what you were thinking.
- Nope, no.
Okay,
but you gotta be quiet.
I will be,
I'm always quiet.
- He's not asleep yet.
- Shh.
Here.
What's that,
three or four?
We got three,
we're good.
I'm good.
Go get the flashlight.
This needs batteries.
Brandon, it's gonna be cold.
You're gonna need
your warm jacket, okay?
Hey, did you hear
your mother, bud?
Hey.
Brandon.
Hey, hon, um...
Look what I found.
What is that?
Is that the kid's
idea of porn?
- I think so.
- Wow.
Bra ads.
Guess we knew
this day was coming.
The hell is that?
Is this like a guy thing?
No, that's not
a guy thing I know.
Ew.
Maybe we should
have the talk with him.
Hey, Brandon.
You know, you just
had your birthday.
Which means that you
are becoming a young man.
Your body's changing.
Okay.
Well, you're going to
start developing, you know...
feelings about women,
women's bodies,
I was just like you
when I was your age.
And I also thought about
girls all the time, heh.
You know, nobody was
around to tell me that...
it was okay to, uh...
touch it
or play with it.
With what?
Uh, you know,
with, uh...
Your penis.
- Okay.
- Look, the thing about...
you know, sex,
it's not...
it's not about organs
or body parts,
I mean, it is that too, but...
You know, it's about finding
the right person
and falling in love.
Look, all I'm saying is
you're a guy, you know,
and you're gonna have
certain urges,
you know, about girls
you see in films,
or girls in class
or whatever.
I'm just saying that it's okay
to give in to them
now and again.
Like, now?
What?
Like now?
No, no, no.
Not...
not right now, no.
Good talk.
Brandon?
Mom?
What's wrong?
Someone's there,
by the curtain.
Honey, there's no one here.
You have to believe me,
he was right there.
Who was?
Brandon Breyer.
Brandon?
Brandon,
where are you, baby?
Can you hear me?
Brandon!
Brandon.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, Brandon.
Your father and I
were freaked out.
I didn't mean to,
I was just taking a pee.
So you don't think I need
to take him to someone,
- like a specialist...
- For what?
For talking back to his dad
and keeping
weird jerk-off material
under his mattress?
It's more than that, Mer.
I don't know,
he's always been
my little sweet guy,
and now...
- he's so different.
- It's called puberty.
I'm overreacting.
- A little bit.
- Obviously, I am.
- I love you.
- Thank you.
- I'll call you.
- Okay, call me later.
What's that?
What? I wasn't snooping
or anything.
It was nice line work.
It was good shading.
Fucking wolf.
Brandon.
Hey, what are
you doing, buddy?
Buddy, it's 10:30
at night.
Are you all right,
buddy?
Think so.
Come on, man,
let's get inside.
Oh, my God.
Tori. Tori!
- Tori, hey, wake up.
- What is it?
I need you
to come outside.
- You see? Right?
- Oh, shit.
- So the wolf is back.
- No, no, baby, I...
This isn't a wolf,
I mean...
This isn't
an animal. I think,
I think this might
be Brandon.
He was out here
earlier tonight,
just staring at them.
The chickens...
They were all
fucking going crazy.
Babe, a wolf can't do this!
It can't rip a door off
and break a lock.
But our 12-year-old son can?
So you can't explain
it, either?
Kyle, stop.
It was the wolf.
I'm going to bed.
This game is called
willows in the wind.
It's about working
together,
and building trust.
Lean back,
and depend on your classmates.
Whoa, come on now, focus!
All right, very good guys.
When we trust
each other,
good things happen.
All right, you're up next,
big guy.
- Let's hear it for Brandon.
- Loser.
Nothing to be afraid of,
your classmates
have your back.
Good job.
Ew!
Oh, shit.
Way to trust the floor.
Hey, hey.
Knock it off.
You okay, bud?
Damn, Caitlyn,
give him a hand up.
Hey, hold on,
we all on the same team here.
He's a pervert.
You lie.
- Idiot.
- Caitlyn, help him up.
or you fail this class.
What are you doing?
Brandon!
Let go. Stop it!
Brandon stop!
Erika, he said he's sorry.
It was an accident,
they're just kids.
Did you see
my daughter's hand?
He's a goddamn animal,
is what he is.
Can we just calm down
here, please?
I want him in handcuffs,
- I want him gone.
- We're taking action.
- He's going to be suspended for...
- Suspended?
- Do you job, arrest him.
- Sorry ma'am, not your call.
After the suspension,
he'll be in sessions
with our school counselor
Ms. Merilee.
His aunt. Jesus fucking Christ.
- Right now, she's the only...
- Know what? Her son
was inside my daughter's
bedroom last Saturday night.
He was camping
with us 30 miles away.
Do you even know
who his real mother is?
- I'm his real mother.
- I meant whatever inbred
- psycho gave birth to him.
- Hey.
I know exactly
what you meant.
But if trash talking
a 12-year-old child,
lets you sleep better
at night, Erika,
maybe you're the one
who needs help.
Sorry about your daughter.
Get up,
let's go.
Shit like that,
breaking a girl's hand?
Goddamn it.
Dad would've
whooped my ass.
Yeah, well, this isn't something
we can ass-whoop away.
I just...
I need to tell
you something.
The other night when
I found him
sleepwalking,
he wasn't downstairs,
He was in the barn.
Did he find it?
No... No.
But he was tugging
at the trap door.
How'd he even know
it's in there?
I don't think he does.
- It was like he was drawn to it.
- Babe.
He may look like us,
and sound like us,
but he's never bled,
not once in his
whole life,
he's never been cut,
or broken a bone,
or had a bruise.
And now he's
hurting people.
Take. Take.
"Yychhagaro" means "take".
Brandon!
Oh, God.
Take larum...
Take the...
Oh, God, oh, God.
Brandon!
Take the...
Oh, God.
Oh, Brandon.
Baby, it's okay.
Baby...
It cut me.
Oh.
Oh, uh, okay.
You'll be okay.
It'll be okay,
it'll be okay.
It'll be okay.
You're okay.
Who am I?
You're our son.
What is this?
Where did I come from?
Listen, baby, I...
I know it's been
difficult for you lately,
that you feel different
from other kids.
You are different.
After you dad and I
got married, we prayed
and prayed for
a baby for so long,
to God, to the universe,
to anyone that would listen.
One night,
one perfect night,
someone listened.
We did not adopt you.
from an agency.
You came here...
arrived here,
in that.
We found you in the woods.
You were just a little guy,
all alone.
You could barely breathe,
and so we...
We took you in.
And you have been
a gift,
my baby boy.
I... I can't even imagine
how overwhelmed
you must feel
right now.
But you have to know,
your dad and I believe
that you came here
for a reason.
That you are special.
And that you're
going to do incredible...
You lied to me!
We just wanted to take
care of you.
- And we always planned to tell...
- You lied to me! You lied!
Wait.
I hate you,
you lied to me. You're liars!
You lied.
I hate you! I hate this place.
What is going on
in here?
He... He found it.
He found it.
Take the ghhol.
Ghhol.
Ghhol. Ghhol.
Take the world.
Don't scream.
What are you doing here?
I brought you flowers.
You can't be here.
Don't be scared.
I wanna talk to you.
I want to tell you
what I learned tonight.
I learned that
I'm very
special.
You're one of the only
people in the world
that knows how
special I am.
But someday...
they will all know.
My mom told
me not to talk to you.
I'm gonna take care of that.
Have good one, Gary.
Hey, who's messing
with me?
Is that you, Gary?
Get out of here!
Leave me alone!
Is he awake?
I called up two times
already,
I heard him
walking around.
Should somebody go
get him, I mean...
Morning.
Hey, bud.
Uh, you know you're
going to be late for school.
Yeah, I know, I was just
up in my room... thinking.
Thinking about what?
Just about everything.
And, uh,
it's totally cool.
I feel good.
I'm glad you
feel that way, buddy.
Me too.
Why don't you grab
a seat?
Ten minutes late never
killed anyone.
You say she hasn't responded
to any calls or texts?
That's correct.
This was the last place
she was seen.
Doesn't look like
a robbery.
Good, God.
Have you talked
to her daughter?
She's a mess right now.
Scared shitless.
I barely got two words
out of her.
What is that?
So I know this
is kind of strange,
I'm your aunt,
and I'm also your counselor,
but I'm the only one
the district's got,
so you are stuck with me.
So Brandon,
your mom tells me
that you've been having
some issues lately
about being adopted.
Nothing bad,
- only good ones.
- Really?
How so?
I've realized I'm special.
Because my real parents aren't
from a stupid place like here.
You don't think of you mom
and dad as your real parents?
I do, but I just know
I'm something else.
Something superior.
Brandon,
do you feel bad
about what you did to Caitlyn?
You know,
sometimes
when bad things
happen to people,
it's for a good reason.
Brandon,
part of my job
is to update the school,
and to update your mom
on your progress,
and to let them know
if you are showing any
growth or remorse,
and I...
I can't take it easy on you
because you're my family.
I'm giving you an opportunity
to talk to me,
I'm supposed to update
the sheriff tomorrow,
and I have to be
honest with him.
Yeah, my buddy said
the diner was just...
Was just wrecked.
And the waitress Erika
was gone.
It's been 24 hours.
Wow, Kyle, you think
your son could have done it?
- Dude!
- What?
He crushed
her daughter's hand.
That's not funny
right now, okay?
- Okay, I'm sorry.
- So, uh...
What's gonna happen
with all that?
I don't know.
He got suspended for a few days,
and I'm sure I'm gonna get
a call from some lawyer
telling me my son's
a monster, which...
I don't even know anymore.
Maybe he is.
They're all monsters.
I'm going home.
Come on. One more.
- One more. Come on.
- No, no. I gotta get home,
- or Merilee's gonna kill me.
- I'll drive you.
It's just a few miles
down the road.
- No, hang. I'll drive.
- Mommy, I'm okay.
Brandon!
I'm home.
I got us sesame chicken.
Brandon?
What?
Alert. Motion, backyard.
Who the hell?
- Hey.
- Brandon, Jesus.
What are you doing here?
I need to talk to you.
I know it's late,
but I promise I won't take long.
Okay. Fine.
Back in your office,
you mentioned something about
talking to
the sheriff tomorrow?
Mm-hmm.
That's right.
Yeah, the thing is...
that can't happen, ever.
It's just not good for anyone.
Not for me,
not for my parents,
and it's really,
really not good for you.
At all.
Brandon,
listen to me, okay?
I have to do my job.
And to be honest, you showing up
at my house this late
is very inappropriate.
I'm gonna need you
to go home now, okay?
Okay.
I'll walk back.
Okay, sweetie.
Be safe.
You too.
Alert. Motion, backyard.
What the hell? Seriously?
Alert.
Motion, backyard.
Brandon, is that you?
This is so annoying.
Alert. Alert. Alert.
- Motion, backyard.
- Ugh, great.
The whole freaking house
is falling apart.
Oh, shit.
Brandon? What the fuck
are you doing?
Aunt Merilee was helping me
with my homework.
No, what the fuck
are you doing in my closet
- wearing this creepy mask?
- It's not creepy.
You scared the shit out of me,
weirdo! I'm taking you home.
- This is fucking insane, man.
- I didn't do anything.
Are you gonna
tell my parents?
You're lucky
if that's all I do!
Get in the truck.
You shouldn't tell my parents.
Brandon, get in the truck!
Shit.
What the fuck!
Holy sh...
What the...?
No. Come on, come on.
No, no, no.
Come on, come on, come on.
Ah, man!
Come on, not now!
Just... Come on!
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on!
Damn it.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on!
Stupid piece of shit!
Oh, shit. Okay.
Okay, it's time to go.
Come on!
Nope. Mm-mmm.
No, no, no.
Come on!
Get out of here!
Gotta go!
Let's go! Come on!
Uh...
Okay.
Um... uh...
This is, uh, really bad.
What the... What the fuck!
No, stop, stop!
Come on, put me down!
Hey, man, stop!
Oh, shit! Oh, fuck.
No, no. Fuck, fuck, fuck!
Oh, shit! Oh, God!
Goddamn it!
God! Fuck!
Hi, Merilee. I know
I'm leaving a lot of messages.
It's after 10 now, and we still
haven't seen him, so...
Did she say anything
to him at school?
Maybe he said something
to you at school or...
- Like he got a ride home or...
- Shut up!
...where he
to go after school.
I'm rambling
because I'm freaking out,
so just please call me back.
Thank you, honey.
- Would you please stop?
- I didn't say anything.
Oh, my God, baby!
Where have you been?
Where were you?
What happened to your shirt?
I was playing soccer.
You've been playing soccer
this whole time?
Well, after school,
Royce and them asked me
if I wanted to play.
And as soon as
the game started, they were...
They were tripping me
and pushing me to the ground,
and, you know,
they were all laughing
because my shirt got ripped.
I just decided I'd walk
all the way home.
I know I should have called.
- Yes.
- Actually, I'm...
I'm just really tired.
I'm gonna go to bed.
Okay, well,
let me take this...
No. No.
Don't worry about it.
It's fine.
I'll come up
in a couple minutes.
- He's lying.
- Yeah, obviously.
If we don't do something,
this is gonna get worse.
- What the fuck do we do?
- I don't know.
Maybe we need
to talk to somebody.
- He needs a specialist.
- What?
- And say what to them?
- I don't know.
"Hello, this is our son.
We found him in a fucking
spaceship in the woods.
Now what?"
No, we should have
done something a long
time ago. This is on us.
Maybe this time,
we get lucky and make a baby?
Just shut up and kiss me.
There's, like,
a light in the woods.
What the...?
Tori?
Hey, baby.
What are you doing?
It's a boy.
Oh, we've tried for so long
to have a baby, and he's here.
He's here. A gift.
Hello?
- Oh, God.
- Hey, hey. Huh?
Mer.
You all right?
No. They won't let me see him
because his...
They said that his face
is too mangled.
Do they know what happened?
They were...
They found him on Route 18.
They think that he swerved
to not hit a deer, and...
They're doing
the toxicology
to make sure
that he wasn't drinking.
Was he drinking?
No, he just had
like two or three drinks of...
I mean,
I wasn't counting.
How's Brandon?
He's okay.
We didn't tell him anything.
No, but did
he get home okay?
- Yes, he did.
- Okay.
Thank God. Thank God.
He came over and I didn't
remember when he left,
so I'm just glad
that he's okay.
He left you?
Morning, baby.
Um...
There's something that
we need to discuss with you,
and it's probably
gonna be hard to hear.
Last night,
your Uncle Noah...
He died last night.
Okay.
Brandon,
do you understand?
Your Uncle Noah passed away.
He's gone.
I feel like you want me to cry
or something.
Do you wanna cry?
Brandon, we know you were
at Aunt Merilee's last night.
Honey, I'm your mom.
I will always defend you.
But if you know something
about what happened to Noah,
you need to tell us.
I don't know
what happened to him.
But I would never
hurt Uncle Noah.
I love him.
That is bullshit.
He is fucking lying!
Kyle.
Look, we know you were there.
What else are you
lying to us about?
Can you calm down?
- Were you in Caitlyn's bedroom?
- He was camping with us.
Where were you Wednesday
when Caitlyn's mom went missing?
- This is not helping!
- He is lying to our faces!
- I'm gonna go upstairs.
- You're what...
No, you're not.
You are not going anywhere
until we get all this
on the table.
- Kyle, I will handle it!
- No, no, no.
Did you hurt Noah?
What did you do to him!
He was my friend,
and you just...
Leave me alone!
Brandon.
You need to go to your room.
Just go to your room.
Are you all right?
Honey?
He's hiding that shirt
for some reason.
Honey.
Shit.
Dad?
Hey, bud.
I wanted to apologize.
We've been going through
a lot lately, and...
I shouldn't have said
what I said to you.
Okay.
- Come here, get in here.
- What? What?
- It's right there.
- That could be anything.
No. That is why he was hiding
this from us last night.
- That is Noah's blood.
- How?
How could Brandon
have killed Noah
and then made it look
like a car accident?
Who knows what kind
of weird shit he could do?
Noah was drunk
and wrecked the car
- because you let him drive.
- No, that is not what...
And now you are trying
to take out your guilt
- on our 12-year-old son.
- Babe...
You are making
a hard situation impossible.
Babe, we've got
to do something.
If we don't, more people
are gonna get hurt.
More people will die.
You gotta be with me on this.
I will never
turn against our son.
He's not our son!
He is some thing
we found in the woods.
How fucking dare
you say that to me.
- How dare you.
- Babe!
How can you
fucking say that to me?
Babe. Come on,
he's killing us.
We now turn to
more somber news tonight
as authorities are reaching out
to the public for information
in their search for missing
Darbo's waitress, Erika Connor,
who was last seen at the iconic
Route 74 diner Wednesday.
Anyone with information
about her whereabouts
is strongly urged
to contact police officials...
You okay?
I think I'm gonna take him...
I'm gonna take him away
this weekend.
Just the two of us.
Take him out to Drywood.
Be his dad.
Let him know I love him.
Here, don't forget these.
- Just wear them for me.
- Okay.
Come here.
You'll always be
my baby boy.
Even though
you're getting so tall.
Go have fun
with your dad, okay?
All right.
- Seat belt.
- Right.
See you Sunday.
Afternoon, Tori.
Hey.
Your boy around,
by chance?
Brandon went hunting
with his dad.
- Hmm.
- Is something wrong?
Maybe you can answer
a question for me.
This look familiar to you?
Some kind of signature
left at the spots
where both Erika
went missing and Noah died.
No. Mm-mm.
Doesn't that look
like a "BB," maybe,
as in "Brandon Breyer"?
I don't see it.
Do you mind if I come in,
take a look around?
I do mind. I think,
actually, you should go.
All right.
But you know I'll be back.
These are deer tracks.
Looks like there's more
than one set of tracks.
No.
Oh, God.
Brandon?
Oh, man.
Oh, God.
No. Please stop.
Please. Please.
God... Ah!
Brandon, please, stop, stop.
Don't hurt me, okay?
Brandon, please, please.
Please. Brandon, don't.
Don't.
I'm sorry.
Pick up, pick up.
Kyle.
Kyle, I'm sorry.
You were right.
Baby, you were right.
He killed Noah.
He... Brandon...
Brandon...
He killed Noah.
And...
Kyle?
Mom.
Brandon.
Where's Dad?
He's gone.
Gone where?
You know.
No.
No, I don't.
I don't know where.
Where are you?
I'm home, Mom.
Brandon?
Please pick up.
Please help me.
Please...
911.
Got a
call from the Breyer residence.
Tori was screaming,
then the line went dead.
Shit. I'm on my way.
What the fuck?
Yeah.
Tori!
You got the sheriffs here.
Where are you?
Come to the sound
of my voice, Tori.
I'm here, I'm here...
Jesus Christ,
what the fuck was that?
Tori!
I'm here!
- You're safe now.
- No, no.
- We got...
- You need to get...
Go! Take cover!
- No, you don't understand...
- Go!
- Hide! Hide!
- We need to get out.
Oh, my God.
Request for backup
at the Breyer residence.
Immediate help.
We have a 217 in progress
on Route 9.
Requesting backup.
I repeat, I need backup!
Come in.
Repeat,
I have a 217 in progress
at the Breyer residence.
I need backup immediately!
Officer?
If anyone can read me,
I have eyes on the suspect.
He's outside.
Officer?
Officer Ayres, come in.
Come in, Officer Ayres.
Hello?
Officer Ayres, please respond.
The ship.
It cut him.
It cut him, it cut him.
Okay.
Erika.
Brandon?
Where are you, baby?
Brandon.
Mom?
Listen to me.
I have never
stopped loving you.
I believe...
I still believe
you were a blessing
that fell to this Earth.
When we found you,
you were so tiny and fragile.
And all we could do
was keep you safe.
Whatever you've done,
I know there is good
inside you.
I want to do good, Mom.
I do.
And you will.
You will always be...
...my baby boy.
Brandon, I'm sorry.
Oh, Brandon.
Rescue one, we have rescue...
Breaking news at this hour.
A passenger jet has crashed
in the small town
of Brightburn, Kansas.
Details are still coming in,
but there are believed
to be no survivors
among the 268 passengers
onboard.
Investigators
are not yet sure
what caused the plane
to drop suddenly from the sky
and crash into
this small family farm.
Among the reported dead are
the residents of the farmhouse,
Kyle and Tori Breyer.
They are survived by
their 12-year-old son, Brandon.
You see that? What is that?
The mainstream media, as usual,
tried to sell you all
a load of bullshit.
Just like that half man,
half sea creature
capsizing fishing vessels
in the South China Sea!
Like what we were talking
about last week,
some kind of witch woman
who chokes people out
with ropes and cords.
They are all out there,
they are all waiting,
and they are all gonna eat
our fucking breakfast
unless we get our shit together
and do something!
Subtitles by explosiveskull
Sync by GoldenBeard