

16
00:00:51,630 --> 00:00:53,920
收下这个娃娃就是一个天大的错误
It was a big mistake acknowledging this doll.

17
00:00:53,920 --> 00:00:54,630
一旦它到了你的手中
And through that,

18
00:00:54,630 --> 00:00:56,330
无形的恶灵就迷惑了你的心智
the inhuman spirit tricked you.

19
00:00:56,510 --> 00:00:58,870
是你允许它入侵你的生活
You gave it permission to infest your lives.

20
00:00:59,300 --> 00:01:01,000
无形的恶灵是什么
What's an inhuman spirit?

21
00:01:01,510 --> 00:01:04,210
那是一种不会以人形存在的东西
It's something that's never walked the earth in human form.

22
00:01:05,480 --> 00:01:06,730
那是一种邪恶的东西
It's something demonic.

23
00:01:06,730 --> 00:01:09,670
那这个娃娃没有被附身吗
So, the doll was never possessed?

24
00:01:10,310 --> 00:01:13,070
是的  这个娃娃只是一个媒介
No, it was used as a conduit.

25
00:01:13,070 --> 00:01:15,990
它几经易手  让人误以为是她被附身了
It was moved around to give the impression of possession.

26
00:01:15,990 --> 00:01:18,740
恶灵不会附身在东西上
Demonic spirits don't possess things.

27
00:01:18,740 --> 00:01:20,270
只会附身在人身上
They possess people.

28
00:01:20,780 --> 00:01:23,100
它想要占据你的心
It wanted to get inside of you.

29
00:01:23,370 --> 00:01:25,980
基于这种特殊的情况
And given this unusual feature,

30
00:01:26,460 --> 00:01:28,730
这个娃娃需要进行妥善的存放
the doll will need to be properly cared for.

31
00:01:28,920 --> 00:01:29,980
妥善
Cared for?

32
00:01:30,330 --> 00:01:31,900
这娃娃就该被毁掉
It should be destroyed.

33
00:01:34,590 --> 00:01:36,660
那只会让事态恶化
That would only make things worse.

34
00:01:37,720 --> 00:01:39,950
我们觉得最好还是由我们带走这个娃娃
We think it best the doll come with us.

35
00:01:41,430 --> 00:01:43,080
我们会把它放在安全的地方
We'll keep it somewhere safe.

36
00:01:43,720 --> 00:01:45,710
听起来是个不错的主意
That sounds like a great idea.

37
00:01:46,060 --> 00:01:47,250
她是你们的了
She's all yours.

38
00:02:01,370 --> 00:02:02,990
我的梦*
*The dreams I hold

39
00:02:02,990 --> 00:02:05,560
是金色的*
*Is a band of gold

40
00:02:05,580 --> 00:02:07,580
而爱留下的*
*And the memories

41
00:02:07,580 --> 00:02:10,320
这些记忆*
*Of what love could be

42
00:02:10,670 --> 00:02:12,530
你觉得还有多久能到
How much longer, do you think?

43
00:02:13,130 --> 00:02:14,040
大概还有一小时
About an hour.

44
00:02:14,050 --> 00:02:15,920
你还是把座椅放下来休息一下吧
Why don't you put your head back? Get some rest.

45
00:02:15,920 --> 00:02:19,200
不行  你从超市回家都能迷路
No, you get lost coming home from the supermarket.

46
00:02:19,300 --> 00:02:22,580
我要是睡着的话  醒来我们就在加州了
If I do that, we might end up in California.

47
00:02:22,680 --> 00:02:25,140
那你醒来就能听到太平洋的声音了
Well, so you wake up to the sound of the Pacific.

48
00:02:25,140 --> 00:02:26,420
那有什么不好的
Nothing wrong with that.

49
00:02:27,560 --> 00:02:28,920
我还能顺路接上朱蒂
I'll pick up Judy on the way.

50
00:02:29,140 --> 00:02:31,350
听起来很棒  爱德
Ah, that actually sounds so nice, Ed.

51
00:02:31,350 --> 00:02:33,050
我们应该好好计划一下
We should plan on it.

52
00:02:36,070 --> 00:02:37,010
怎么回事
What's this?

53
00:02:47,450 --> 00:02:50,690
你们得掉头  前头发生了很严重的交通事故
You folks need to turn around. Pretty bad accident up ahead.

54
00:02:51,540 --> 00:02:53,150
我们能帮什么忙吗
Uh, anything we can do?

55
00:02:53,540 --> 00:02:54,990
你是医生什么的吗
You a doctor or something?

56
00:02:55,340 --> 00:02:56,450
是什么的吧
Or something.

57
00:03:00,130 --> 00:03:03,410
-他只是想说我们很乐意帮忙  -好吧
- He just meant if you need an extra set of hands. - Yeah.

58
00:03:03,680 --> 00:03:05,290
我们能搞定  谢了
We got it covered. Thanks.

59
00:03:11,390 --> 00:03:12,540
娃娃不错
Nice doll.

60
00:03:13,060 --> 00:03:14,250
看起来不错而已
That's what you think.

61
00:03:16,730 --> 00:03:19,440
你们得回到三英里前的那个出口
All right, you're gonna head three miles back to the last exit.

62
00:03:19,440 --> 00:03:21,110
你们转26号路
You'll hop on 26,

63
00:03:21,110 --> 00:03:22,390
可以绕道
that'll loop you around.

64
00:03:22,700 --> 00:03:25,140
-26号路  明白了  -谢谢  警官
- 26. Got it. - Thank you, Officer.

65
00:03:27,950 --> 00:03:29,390
只是一个路人和他的娃娃
A guy and his doll.

66
00:03:46,350 --> 00:03:48,180
我觉得我们开过头了
I think we missed our turn.

67
00:03:48,180 --> 00:03:50,720
没有  布里奇沃特路就在前面
We didn't miss it. Bridgewater's just up ahead.

68
00:03:50,730 --> 00:03:52,520
什么布里奇沃特路  我们要去老布里奇路
Bridgewater? Old Ridge Road.

69
00:03:52,520 --> 00:03:54,290
你怎么会觉得是布里奇沃特路
Where did you get Bridgewater from?

70
00:03:56,020 --> 00:03:58,470
好吧  我觉得我们是开过头了
Well, you know what? I think we missed our turn.

71
00:04:00,190 --> 00:04:02,760
我会留心找太平洋的
I'll keep my eye out for the Pacific.

72
00:04:05,360 --> 00:04:06,350
爱德
Ed?

73
00:04:08,200 --> 00:04:09,690
-爱德  -别急  别急
- Ed? - Hang on, hang on.

74
00:04:20,050 --> 00:04:22,110
-拜托  -发生了什么
- Come on. - What just happened?

75
00:04:24,010 --> 00:04:25,580
我打开前盖看看
I'll pop the hood and find out.

76
00:04:30,310 --> 00:04:31,330
小心点
Well, be careful.

77
00:04:45,650 --> 00:04:46,510
好了
There we go.

78
00:05:48,050 --> 00:05:51,750
玛丽威尔公墓

79
00:06:04,610 --> 00:06:06,220
我喜欢你的娃娃
I like your doll.

80
00:06:28,220 --> 00:06:29,910
我觉得好冷
I feel cold.

81
00:06:43,940 --> 00:06:46,050
你刚遭遇了一场交通意外
You were just in an accident.

82
00:06:48,400 --> 00:06:49,510
是吗
I was?

83
00:06:52,410 --> 00:06:53,270
抱歉
Sorry.

84
00:06:53,660 --> 00:06:54,850
搭错线了
Wires crossed.

85
00:07:09,470 --> 00:07:11,250
玛丽威尔公墓

86
00:07:11,050 --> 00:07:12,030
这样应该好了
That should do it.

87
00:07:15,510 --> 00:07:17,160
亲爱的  你没事吧
Honey, you okay?

88
00:07:29,070 --> 00:07:30,090
爱德
Ed!

89
00:07:33,860 --> 00:07:34,770
我没事
I'm okay.

90
00:07:36,950 --> 00:07:37,930
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry!

91
00:07:37,950 --> 00:07:40,200
我的车好像突然着了魔
All of a sudden it was like somebody took over my truck.

92
00:07:40,200 --> 00:07:42,330
我控制不了  你没事吧
I had no control. Are you okay?

93
00:07:42,330 --> 00:07:43,230
我没事
I'm fine.

94
00:07:47,630 --> 00:07:48,990
是那个娃娃  爱德
It's the doll, Ed.

95
00:07:50,920 --> 00:07:53,080
它是召唤其他灵体的灯塔
It's a beacon for other spirits.

96
00:09:25,060 --> 00:09:26,000
这边
Over here.

97
00:09:47,460 --> 00:09:50,030
-神父  越快越好  -是吗
- Father, sooner the better. - Yeah?

98
00:09:50,250 --> 00:09:51,230
是的
Yeah.

99
00:10:03,510 --> 00:10:06,720
不要自作聪明
Be not wise in thine own eyes.

100
00:10:06,730 --> 00:10:09,960
敬畏耶和华  远离恶事
Fear the Lord and depart from evil.

101
00:10:11,940 --> 00:10:16,010
耶和华咒诅恶人的家庭
The curse of the Lord is in the house of the wicked.

102
00:10:16,320 --> 00:10:20,600
赐福与义人的居所
But He blesseth the habitation of the just.

103
00:10:21,570 --> 00:10:24,490
他讥诮那好讥诮的人
Surely, He scorneth the scorners,

104
00:10:24,500 --> 00:10:28,540
赐恩给谦卑的人
but He giveth grace unto the lowly.

105
00:10:28,540 --> 00:10:32,030
智慧人必承受尊荣
The wise shall inherit the glory,

106
00:10:32,130 --> 00:10:36,570
愚昧人高升也成为羞辱
but shame shall be the promotion of fools.

107
00:10:41,390 --> 00:10:42,240
阿门
Amen.

108
00:11:00,110 --> 00:11:02,100
我们还需要一层防护屏障
We need another barrier of protection.

109
00:11:03,070 --> 00:11:04,100
圣洁的屏障
A holy one.

110
00:11:05,370 --> 00:11:06,430
我同意
I agree.

111
00:11:07,620 --> 00:11:09,690
祈祷的效果有限
The blessing will only do so much.

112
00:11:13,790 --> 00:11:15,080
三一教堂
That chapel glass

113
00:11:15,090 --> 00:11:17,820
被毁前的教堂玻璃
we got from Trinity Church before it was torn down,

114
00:11:18,130 --> 00:11:19,070
在哪里
where is that?

115
00:11:40,070 --> 00:11:41,530
"原谅他人
"Let us forgive those

116
00:11:41,530 --> 00:11:42,820
对我们的侵犯
who trespass against us

117
00:11:42,820 --> 00:11:44,820
并使我们不受
and lead us not into temptation,

118
00:11:44,820 --> 00:11:46,530
邪恶的诱惑"
but deliver us from evil."

119
00:11:46,530 --> 00:11:47,600
阿门
Amen.

120
00:12:00,050 --> 00:12:01,030
有用吗
Did it work?

121
00:12:08,260 --> 00:12:09,870
邪恶被压抑了
The evil is contained.

122
00:12:24,240 --> 00:12:37,130
沃伦收藏室是全世界最大的收藏遭到鬼魂影响和诅咒物件的收藏室
由于其藏有及极其邪恶的力量
沃伦夫妇每周会该收藏室进行祈祷赐福
收藏室中的每件物品都有其独一无二的恐怖来历
但是沃伦夫妇认为其中有一件物品蕴含的邪恶力量远甚于其他...

123
00:12:38,920 --> 00:12:51,180
安娜贝尔
回家

124
00:12:58,480 --> 00:13:01,400
一年后

125
00:13:07,030 --> 00:13:09,030
英雄还是骗子
争议驱魔引发热议

126
00:13:10,990 --> 00:13:12,350
好了  朱蒂
Okay, Judy.

127
00:13:13,200 --> 00:13:15,690
我看到玛丽·艾伦的车停着了  去拿好你的东西
I just saw Mary Ellen pull up. Go and get your things.

128
00:13:17,040 --> 00:13:18,330
但是先把你的麦片放...
But first put your cereal in the...

129
00:13:18,330 --> 00:13:20,030
好吧  算了
All right. Never mind.

130
00:13:20,340 --> 00:13:21,320
我来吧
I'll do it.

131
00:13:27,130 --> 00:13:29,750
英雄还是骗子
争议驱魔引发热议

132
00:13:39,900 --> 00:13:40,760
那是什么
What's that?

133
00:13:47,360 --> 00:13:49,970
你是我的英雄
Well, you're my hero.

134
00:14:23,360 --> 00:14:24,840
订披萨的钱放在柜子上了
The pizza money is on the counter

135
00:14:24,850 --> 00:14:26,530
号码就在电话机边
and numbers are by the phone.

136
00:14:26,530 --> 00:14:27,190
完美
Perfect.

137
00:14:27,190 --> 00:14:28,860
我们明天一大早就会回来
And we'll be back early tomorrow morning.

138
00:14:28,860 --> 00:14:31,010
你们不用着急  我们没事的
Well, and take your time, we'll be fine.

139
00:14:31,030 --> 00:14:32,220
-对吧  朱蒂  -嗯
- Right, Judy? - Yeah.

140
00:14:33,410 --> 00:14:35,540
-那你会...  -乖乖的
- So, you'll... - Behave? Yes.

141
00:14:35,550 --> 00:14:36,540
而且你会记得
And you'll remember to go to...

142
00:14:36,540 --> 00:14:37,870
记得准时上床睡觉
Remember to go to bed on time.

143
00:14:37,870 --> 00:14:39,020
绝对的
Absolutely.

144
00:14:39,620 --> 00:14:40,980
-好吧  别忘了...  -好好玩
- All right, don't forget to... - To have fun.

145
00:14:41,250 --> 00:14:42,820
-我知道  -也对
- I know. - That, too.

146
00:14:44,630 --> 00:14:46,950
你们是排练好的吗
Did you guys rehearse that, or what?

147
00:14:58,350 --> 00:15:00,480
圣托马斯
天主教学校

148
00:15:00,100 --> 00:15:01,210
地球呼叫朱蒂
Earth to Judy!

149
00:15:04,110 --> 00:15:05,090
怎么了
What's wrong?

150
00:15:05,270 --> 00:15:06,170
没什么
Nothing.

151
00:15:06,730 --> 00:15:07,800
我没事
I'm fine.

152
00:15:08,820 --> 00:15:11,140
还有几个小时就到周末了
Well, it's just a couple more hours until the weekend.

153
00:15:11,610 --> 00:15:13,740
我要趁有空赶紧去超市买点吃用
I'm gonna run to the market for supplies during my free period.

154
00:15:13,740 --> 00:15:15,100
然后我就来接你  好吗
I'll pick you up after, okay?

155
00:15:17,410 --> 00:15:18,560
听起来很棒
Sounds super.

156
00:15:23,920 --> 00:15:24,860
再见  朱蒂
Bye, Judy!

157
00:15:27,880 --> 00:15:29,160
过得愉快
Have a good day!

158
00:16:29,190 --> 00:16:30,930
法雷太太  就在这边
Mrs. Faley, it's right over here.

159
00:16:31,400 --> 00:16:32,340
我带你去
Let me show you.

160
00:16:32,440 --> 00:16:33,530
英雄还是骗子
争议驱魔引发热议

161
00:16:34,740 --> 00:16:37,030
你怎么能不告诉我  沃伦夫妇到底是干什么的
How could you not tell me what the Warrens did for a living?

162
00:16:37,030 --> 00:16:38,700
你现在不是应该在上数学课吗
Shouldn't you be in math class?

163
00:16:38,700 --> 00:16:39,730
玛丽·艾伦
Mary Ellen!

164
00:16:40,160 --> 00:16:41,950
我当初给史密斯夫妇当了两年保姆
I babysat the Smiths for over two years

165
00:16:41,950 --> 00:16:43,400
也没告诉过你他们是干什么的
and never told you what they did.

166
00:16:43,460 --> 00:16:44,730
那他们是干什么的
Oh, what do they do?

167
00:16:44,750 --> 00:16:46,360
他们是足疗师
They're podiatrists.

168
00:16:46,460 --> 00:16:47,820
这完全不一样
So not the same.

169
00:16:47,880 --> 00:16:49,840
好吧  我等下肯定要来找你
Well, obviously, I'm coming over later.

170
00:16:49,840 --> 00:16:51,460
我们要一起完成一个
We do have that social studies project

171
00:16:51,460 --> 00:16:52,660
社会调研
that we need to work on.

172
00:16:53,340 --> 00:16:54,550
我们没有什么调研
We don't have any project.

173
00:16:54,550 --> 00:16:55,910
但是他们怎么会知道
Okay, but how would they know?

174
00:16:56,430 --> 00:16:57,740
她可会通灵
She's psychic.

175
00:16:57,800 --> 00:16:59,620
那他们就是英雄
Then, they're heroes.

176
00:17:00,010 --> 00:17:01,560
我觉得他们只是
I think they're concerned parents

177
00:17:01,560 --> 00:17:02,970
不希望自己的孩子受到负面影响的
who wouldn't want negative influences

178
00:17:02,970 --> 00:17:04,250
一对操心的父母
around their child.

179
00:17:04,270 --> 00:17:05,680
什么负面影响
What negative influence?

180
00:17:05,690 --> 00:17:07,650
就因为我有时候会过了宵禁时间才回家吗
'Cause I sometimes stay out past curfew?

181
00:17:07,650 --> 00:17:09,340
不止如此
Among other things.

182
00:17:09,980 --> 00:17:11,400
那房子里是什么样的
So, what's it like inside the house?

183
00:17:11,400 --> 00:17:13,940
都是恐怖的音乐和蜘蛛网吗
Is it all creepy music and cobwebs?

184
00:17:13,940 --> 00:17:15,780
不  不  就是乏味的郊区房子
No. No, it's boring suburbia.

185
00:17:15,780 --> 00:17:17,720
连你的储物柜都比那里恐怖点
The inside of your locker is scarier.

186
00:17:19,910 --> 00:17:23,270
等等  谁要开派对  怎么没邀请我
Wait. Whose party, and why wasn't I invited?

187
00:17:23,370 --> 00:17:24,700
朱蒂的生日快到了
Judy's birthday is coming up,

188
00:17:24,700 --> 00:17:26,370
所以我们要提前庆祝
so we're gonna celebrate early.

189
00:17:26,370 --> 00:17:28,690
你真的是最棒的保姆
You really are the best babysitter, you know that?

190
00:17:29,420 --> 00:17:30,940
拍马屁也没用
Compliments will get you nowhere.

191
00:17:31,380 --> 00:17:32,710
那威胁呢
What about threats?

192
00:17:32,710 --> 00:17:35,530
你有没有注意到谁在收银呢
Did you, uh, happen to notice who's working checkout?

193
00:17:37,590 --> 00:17:39,220
-非常感谢  -再见
- Thank you so much. - See you soon.

194
00:17:39,220 --> 00:17:40,180
你不会这么做的
You wouldn't.

195
00:17:40,180 --> 00:17:42,120
你知道他们都管他叫什么吧
You know what they call him, right?

196
00:17:43,010 --> 00:17:43,920
什么
What?

197
00:17:48,690 --> 00:17:50,250
大胆鲍勃
Bob's-Got-Balls.

198
00:17:50,310 --> 00:17:51,340
你好吗
How you doing?

199
00:17:51,610 --> 00:17:52,760
你好  丹妮拉
Hi, Daniela.

200
00:18:01,320 --> 00:18:02,640
你好  玛丽·艾伦
Hi, Mary Ellen.

201
00:18:03,160 --> 00:18:04,580
就这些了吗
Is this everything?

202
00:18:04,580 --> 00:18:06,730
-我想是的  -好
- I think so. - Oh, cool.

203
00:18:06,870 --> 00:18:08,770
你住在沃伦家附近吧  鲍勃
You live near the Warrens, don't you, Bob?

204
00:18:09,080 --> 00:18:11,400
嗯  玛丽·艾伦今晚要去他们家做保姆
Yeah, Mary Ellen's babysitting for them tonight.

205
00:18:12,290 --> 00:18:14,610
嗯  我就住在他们家对面那条街
Yeah. Yeah, I live right across the street.

206
00:18:14,800 --> 00:18:17,050
你有没有注意到他们家有什么恐怖的地方
Do you ever see anything scary over there?

207
00:18:17,050 --> 00:18:18,780
有没有什么鬼魂
Like a ghost, maybe?

208
00:18:18,970 --> 00:18:19,740
鲍勃
Bob...

209
00:18:20,340 --> 00:18:21,640
法雷太太在五号货架
Mrs. Faley went ahead and dropped

210
00:18:21,640 --> 00:18:23,800
弄撒了一罐番茄酱
a can of tomato sauce in aisle five,

211
00:18:23,810 --> 00:18:26,210
那看上去就像是犯罪现场  去拿拖把
and it looks like a crime scene, so get the mop.

212
00:18:26,850 --> 00:18:28,600
女士们  你们还好吗
Ladies. Did you find everything okay?

213
00:18:28,600 --> 00:18:29,520
很好  先生
Yes, sir.

214
00:18:29,520 --> 00:18:31,380
鲍勃没给你们惹什么麻烦把
Bob here is not giving you any trouble, is he?

215
00:18:31,400 --> 00:18:32,230
-没有  -没有
- No. - No.

216
00:18:32,230 --> 00:18:33,400
-交给我吧  谢谢  爸爸  -好吧
- Yeah, I got it. Thanks, Dad. - All right.

217
00:18:33,400 --> 00:18:35,400
我马上就去
I'll do it right after.

218
00:18:35,400 --> 00:18:37,010
好了  你都看到了什么
So, what'd you see?

219
00:18:37,740 --> 00:18:39,640
在沃伦家
At the Warrens'?

220
00:18:39,860 --> 00:18:41,240
没什么  没什么
Uh, nothing. Nothing.

221
00:18:41,240 --> 00:18:44,480
一共3.5美元  那么...
Um, your total is $3.50, so...

222
00:18:46,200 --> 00:18:48,310
但是你早就知道沃伦夫妇是干什么的吧
But you knew what the Warrens did?

223
00:18:48,460 --> 00:18:50,660
是有一些传言  但是...
There were rumors, I guess, but...

224
00:18:50,670 --> 00:18:52,540
传言  有意思
Rumors. Interesting.

225
00:18:52,540 --> 00:18:55,450
你知道也有关于你的传言吗  鲍勃
Did you know there's a rumor going around about you, Bob?

226
00:18:55,460 --> 00:18:57,550
等等  真的吗  什么传言
Wait, really? What is it about?

227
00:18:57,550 --> 00:18:59,010
是关于一个女孩...
Uh, it's about a girl who has a...

228
00:18:59,010 --> 00:19:01,240
好吧  你可以来  住口
Fine. You can come. Stop.

229
00:19:03,510 --> 00:19:04,830
-抱歉  -抱歉
- Sorry. - Sorry.

230
00:19:05,060 --> 00:19:06,790
-都是我不好  -没关系
- That's totally my fault. - It's okay.

231
00:19:08,020 --> 00:19:09,430
那...
So, what...

232
00:19:09,430 --> 00:19:10,680
再见  鲍勃  谢谢
Bye, Bob. Thanks.

233
00:19:10,690 --> 00:19:11,500
再见
Bye.

234
00:19:13,560 --> 00:19:15,880
她忘了拿她的蛋
Uh, she forgot her eggs, so...

235
00:19:16,320 --> 00:19:17,260
给我
Here.

236
00:19:17,780 --> 00:19:19,300
她喜欢你
She likes you.

237
00:19:23,780 --> 00:19:25,520
那是个意外
There's been an accident.

238
00:19:36,090 --> 00:19:37,240
别碰她
Don't touch her.

239
00:19:38,250 --> 00:19:39,570
你会被服身的
You'll get obsessed.

240
00:19:40,050 --> 00:19:41,670
-是附身  -我说的就是附身
- It's "possessed." - That's what I said.

241
00:19:41,680 --> 00:19:43,930
既然你懂这么多
Anyways, if you know so much,

242
00:19:43,930 --> 00:19:47,000
你不如告诉我们  你能不能抓到鬼身上的虱子
why don't you tell us if you can catch cooties from a ghost?

243
00:19:47,180 --> 00:19:48,330
你抓不到的
You can't.

244
00:19:48,430 --> 00:19:49,750
那你怎么抓呢
Well, then how'd you get 'em?

245
00:19:50,020 --> 00:19:51,330
安东尼·莱欧斯
Anthony Rios!

246
00:19:51,730 --> 00:19:53,250
别逼我把你姐姐叫过来
Don't make me get your sister.

247
00:19:54,190 --> 00:19:55,020
拜托不要
Please don't.

248
00:19:55,020 --> 00:19:57,340
那就走开  你们都走开  快点
Then go. All of you. Come on.

249
00:19:57,770 --> 00:19:59,340
我们走
Come on. Let's go!

250
00:20:00,280 --> 00:20:03,010
很抱歉  我去不了你的生日派对了  朱蒂
I'm sorry I can't come to your birthday party, Judy.

251
00:20:03,950 --> 00:20:05,180
你也来不了了吗
You can't either?

252
00:20:05,620 --> 00:20:08,680
我父母说我还没有做好  面对死亡的准备
My parents said I'm not really prepared to process death yet.

253
00:20:10,540 --> 00:20:12,110
这是生日派对
It's a birthday party.

254
00:20:12,120 --> 00:20:13,190
对不起
I'm sorry.

255
00:20:26,140 --> 00:20:28,050
你收到这种待遇多久了
Hey, how long has that been happening?

256
00:20:28,050 --> 00:20:30,540
自从大家这周都知道那篇文章的事以后
Since everyone heard about the article this week.

257
00:20:31,680 --> 00:20:33,630
-求你不要告诉我父母  -我不会的
- Please don't tell my parents. - I won't.

258
00:20:33,940 --> 00:20:35,600
只要你不让我说
I won't as long as you do.

259
00:20:35,600 --> 00:20:37,690
-我不希望他们担心  -他们是父母
- I don't want them to worry. - They're parents.

260
00:20:37,690 --> 00:20:38,730
不管需不需要担心
They're worried about everything

261
00:20:38,730 --> 00:20:40,050
他们都会担心的
whether they need to be or not.

262
00:20:41,320 --> 00:20:43,400
纪念迈克尔·莫里塞神父

263
00:20:47,070 --> 00:20:48,120
你确定你现在的烦心事
Are you sure the bullying is

264
00:20:48,120 --> 00:20:49,680
只有受同学欺负吗
the only thing that's bothering you?

265
00:20:49,740 --> 00:20:51,030
那不是烦心事
That isn't bothering me.

266
00:20:51,040 --> 00:20:52,190
你懂我的意思
You know what I mean.

267
00:20:58,250 --> 00:20:59,330
记得我们说好的
And remember our deal.

268
00:20:59,340 --> 00:21:00,490
没有秘密
No secrets.

269
00:21:01,500 --> 00:21:02,360
我知道
I know.

270
00:21:02,960 --> 00:21:04,030
我没有秘密
I don't have any.

271
00:21:05,930 --> 00:21:07,290
你去超市买了什么
What did you get at the store?

272
00:21:08,140 --> 00:21:09,470
惊喜
A surprise.

273
00:21:09,470 --> 00:21:12,290
-你说没有秘密的  -惊喜不是秘密
- You said no secrets. - A surprise isn't a secret.

274
00:21:12,350 --> 00:21:14,380
-那是什么  -是惊喜
- What is it then? - It's a surprise.

275
00:21:31,950 --> 00:21:33,350
你会弄得一团糟的
You're gonna make a mess.

276
00:21:38,460 --> 00:21:39,750
给蛋糕留点
Save some for the cake.

277
00:21:39,750 --> 00:21:40,820
不
No.

278
00:21:47,950 --> 00:21:50,080
我觉得有人在敲门
I think there's someone at the door.

279
00:22:03,150 --> 00:22:05,720
我敲了十分钟的门
I was knocking on the door for, like, ten minutes.

280
00:22:06,860 --> 00:22:08,140
你怎么进来的
How did you even get in?

281
00:22:08,150 --> 00:22:09,180
后门
Back door.

282
00:22:09,530 --> 00:22:10,860
这是灵铃吗
Is this a spirit bell?

283
00:22:10,870 --> 00:22:11,990
什么是灵铃
What's a spirit bell?

284
00:22:11,990 --> 00:22:14,440
那会告诉你你身边有没有灵体
It tells you if you're in the presence of any spirits.

285
00:22:14,540 --> 00:22:16,400
-那的确是咯  -不是
- So, it is one. - No.

286
00:22:16,410 --> 00:22:19,190
这只是一个铃铛  我妈妈喜欢收集
It's just a bell. My mom collects them.

287
00:22:21,000 --> 00:22:22,030
你是谁
Who are you?

288
00:22:22,340 --> 00:22:25,250
她是丹妮拉  她吃完蛋糕就走
She's Daniela, and she leaves after cake.

289
00:22:25,260 --> 00:22:26,530
太好了
Oh, good!

290
00:22:26,670 --> 00:22:28,030
我爱蛋糕
I love cake.

291
00:22:29,340 --> 00:22:30,830
那么  朱蒂
So, Judy.

292
00:22:31,220 --> 00:22:35,160
你爸妈会不会留着些什么恐怖的东西
Don't your parents, like, keep any creepy stuff around?

293
00:22:37,230 --> 00:22:38,210
没有
No.

294
00:22:38,890 --> 00:22:40,750
他们把那些东西都锁在一个房间里
They keep it all locked away in a room.

295
00:22:43,650 --> 00:22:45,480
那我们至少能进去看看吗
Well, can we at least go in and look?

296
00:22:45,480 --> 00:22:46,340
不行
No!

297
00:22:48,360 --> 00:22:51,060
那个房间不该进去
It's not really good for anyone to go in there.

298
00:22:51,570 --> 00:22:52,520
为什么
How come?

299
00:22:53,410 --> 00:22:54,560
就是不应该
Just isn't.

300
00:22:56,490 --> 00:22:57,560
等等
Wait.

301
00:22:58,870 --> 00:22:59,810
来
Here.

302
00:23:00,420 --> 00:23:01,440
生日礼物
Birthday present.

303
00:23:05,210 --> 00:23:06,240
是什么
What is it?

304
00:23:06,500 --> 00:23:07,780
你看看
Look inside.

305
00:23:15,010 --> 00:23:16,350
你哪来的钱买的
How did you even afford those?

306
00:23:16,350 --> 00:23:17,460
那是我自己旧的那双
They're my old ones.

307
00:23:17,560 --> 00:23:18,600
但是我只用过一次
But I only ever used them once

308
00:23:18,600 --> 00:23:20,880
因为我第一次穿上就摔断了胳膊
'cause I broke my arm the first time I put them on.

309
00:23:21,560 --> 00:23:22,590
你开玩笑吧
You're kidding.

310
00:23:22,770 --> 00:23:24,880
她看上去协调性比我好多了
She looks way more coordinated.

311
00:23:25,400 --> 00:23:26,840
这会划坏地板的
They're gonna ruin the floors.

312
00:23:27,030 --> 00:23:28,630
那我们能去街上玩吗
Can we go around the block, then?

313
00:23:29,190 --> 00:23:30,930
-我觉得不该...  -好主意
- I don't think... - Good idea.

314
00:23:31,030 --> 00:23:32,070
你们去吧
You guys go.

315
00:23:32,070 --> 00:23:34,470
我会盯着蛋糕  确保不会烤糊
I'll watch the cake and make sure it doesn't burn.

316
00:23:35,660 --> 00:23:38,290
好吧  但是不要随意乱逛  不要乱碰东西
Fine. But don't snoop. Don't touch.

317
00:23:38,290 --> 00:23:39,940
什么都别做  拜托
Don't do anything. Please?

318
00:23:40,080 --> 00:23:42,060
待在厨房里  你保证
Stay in the kitchen. Promise me.

319
00:23:42,830 --> 00:23:44,070
我保证
I promise.

320
00:24:02,020 --> 00:24:10,070
沃伦夫妇恶魔巫术事物咨询所

321
00:24:10,440 --> 00:24:14,740
危险
请勿触碰任何东西

322
00:24:24,290 --> 00:24:25,360
不管了
Fuck it.

323
00:24:25,710 --> 00:24:28,570
我请求另一边的鬼魂
I am calling out to the spirits on the other side.

324
00:24:29,550 --> 00:24:31,780
请打开这扇门  让我进去
Please unlock this door and let me in.

325
00:24:46,450 --> 00:24:47,510
该死
Shit.

326
00:26:13,070 --> 00:26:14,430
请不要批判我
Please don't judge me.

327
00:26:18,320 --> 00:26:19,510
阿门
Amen.

328
00:27:30,890 --> 00:27:36,230
黑皮

329
00:27:48,330 --> 00:27:52,250
触觉配对

330
00:28:09,680 --> 00:28:11,750
你怎么会被关在这里面呢
What'd you do to get in there?

331
00:30:14,350 --> 00:30:16,750
如果这个房间里面有鬼魂
If there is a presence here in this room,

332
00:30:17,850 --> 00:30:19,500
请给我一个征兆
please give me a sign.

333
00:30:24,570 --> 00:30:25,880
任何征兆都行
Any sign at all.

334
00:30:31,530 --> 00:30:32,600
爸爸
Dad?

335
00:30:46,130 --> 00:30:47,360
这太愚蠢了
This is stupid.

336
00:31:24,920 --> 00:31:26,750
警告
绝对
不要
打开

337
00:32:28,480 --> 00:32:29,420
该死
Shit.

338
00:33:03,180 --> 00:33:05,130
你把蛋糕烤糊了  丹妮拉
You burnt the cake? Daniela.

339
00:33:05,310 --> 00:33:06,630
只有上面
Only the top.

340
00:33:06,650 --> 00:33:08,670
放点糖霜上去就好
Just put frosting on it.

341
00:33:08,900 --> 00:33:09,840
她不会知道的
She'll never know.

342
00:33:10,520 --> 00:33:11,400
轮滑鞋玩得怎么样
How'd it go with the skates?

343
00:33:11,400 --> 00:33:13,150
她很喜欢  直到她在回来的路上摔了一跤
She loved them until she fell on the way back

344
00:33:13,150 --> 00:33:14,300
蹭破了膝盖
and skinned her knee.

345
00:33:14,450 --> 00:33:15,850
总比摔断了手好
Better than breaking her arm.

346
00:33:16,280 --> 00:33:17,320
她现在在哪里呢
Where is she anyway?

347
00:33:17,320 --> 00:33:18,930
她在外面喂鸡
She's out feeding the chickens.

348
00:33:19,490 --> 00:33:20,810
他们还养了鸡吗
They have chickens?

349
00:33:25,750 --> 00:33:26,570
你的膝盖怎么样了
How's your knee?

350
00:33:28,330 --> 00:33:31,420
看起来至少你的牛仔裤需要缝几针了
Looks like your jeans will at least need some stitches.

351
00:33:31,420 --> 00:33:32,400
没事的
It's okay.

352
00:33:32,590 --> 00:33:33,860
总会有意外
Accidents happen.

353
00:33:38,590 --> 00:33:39,910
你已经害怕了吗
So, are you scared yet?

354
00:33:41,100 --> 00:33:42,540
害怕  什么  没有
Scared? What? No.

355
00:33:42,890 --> 00:33:44,210
谁说他们害怕了
Who says they're scared?

356
00:33:44,600 --> 00:33:46,130
我班上的同学
Kids in my class.

357
00:33:46,730 --> 00:33:48,670
安东尼·莱欧斯先开始的
Anthony Rios started it.

358
00:33:48,730 --> 00:33:49,670
我恨他
I hate him.

359
00:33:49,670 --> 00:33:52,420
等等  托尼·莱欧斯开始的吗
Wait. Tony Rios started it?

360
00:33:53,150 --> 00:33:54,340
你认识他吗
Do you know him?

361
00:33:55,280 --> 00:33:57,180
是啊  他是我弟弟
Yeah, he's my brother.

362
00:33:58,110 --> 00:34:01,140
安东尼·莱欧斯是你的弟弟吗
Anthony Rios is your brother?

363
00:34:01,280 --> 00:34:03,490
我懂  别把他和我相提并论
Yeah, I know. Don't hold it against me.

364
00:34:03,490 --> 00:34:05,150
我也不喜欢他
I don't like him either.

365
00:34:06,000 --> 00:34:07,610
你知道  他现在还尿床
You know, he still wets the bed.

366
00:34:08,580 --> 00:34:10,030
可别说是我说的
You didn't hear it from me.

367
00:34:10,290 --> 00:34:12,030
你也可以说  我不在乎
Or maybe you did, I don't care.

368
00:34:12,630 --> 00:34:13,570
但还是...
Still, just...

369
00:34:14,260 --> 00:34:15,780
别太为难他
go a little easy on him.

370
00:34:16,670 --> 00:34:18,620
今年发生了很多事
It's been a tough year.

371
00:34:22,100 --> 00:34:24,870
你失去了某个人  是吗
You lost somebody, didn't you?

372
00:34:26,640 --> 00:34:28,340
我爸爸...
My dad. Uh...

373
00:34:28,850 --> 00:34:30,500
玛丽·艾伦和你说的吗
Did Mary Ellen tell you?

374
00:34:32,110 --> 00:34:33,170
不是
No.

375
00:34:34,150 --> 00:34:35,260
我就是知道
I just knew.

376
00:34:37,780 --> 00:34:39,010
外送
Um, for delivery.

377
00:34:39,860 --> 00:34:41,890
我想点个大号的
Could I do one large, please?

378
00:34:42,620 --> 00:34:46,440
是维曼街3506号
Um, it's gonna be 3506 Wayman Street.

379
00:34:46,870 --> 00:34:48,650
太好了  谢谢
Oh, perfect. Thank you.

380
00:34:53,040 --> 00:34:53,940
来了
Coming.

381
00:34:57,720 --> 00:34:58,870
别着急啊
Hold your horses.

382
00:35:08,020 --> 00:35:09,080
谁啊
Who is it?

383
00:35:15,320 --> 00:35:16,220
有人吗
Hello?

384
00:35:18,280 --> 00:35:19,340
丹妮拉
Daniela?

385
00:35:28,160 --> 00:35:29,520
安娜贝尔在吗
Is Annabelle there?

386
00:35:37,380 --> 00:35:38,410
谁
Who?

387
00:35:39,090 --> 00:35:40,950
安娜贝尔能出来玩吗
Can Annabelle come out to play?

388
00:35:55,310 --> 00:35:56,440
我觉得你走错了
I think you have the wrong house.

389
00:35:56,440 --> 00:35:58,220
这里没有叫安娜贝尔的
There's no Annabelle here.

390
00:36:00,860 --> 00:36:02,220
她在呢
Yes, she is.

391
00:36:02,740 --> 00:36:04,680
她就在你后面
She's right behind you.

392
00:36:15,380 --> 00:36:17,690
人们总是...他们对死亡的态度好奇怪
People are just... They're really weird about death.

393
00:36:18,460 --> 00:36:20,530
也许学校里的孩子正是因此才找你麻烦的
That's probably why the kids pick on you at school.

394
00:36:20,920 --> 00:36:22,200
他们很害怕
It scares them.

395
00:36:22,760 --> 00:36:25,050
他们把死亡看做一种谁都不想沾染的疾病
They treat it like it's some disease they don't wanna get,

396
00:36:25,050 --> 00:36:27,250
即便其实人人都有这种病
even though everyone already has it.

397
00:36:28,060 --> 00:36:29,250
但其实是这样的
But here's the thing.

398
00:36:30,020 --> 00:36:31,850
我以前都认为死了就是一命呜呼了
I used to think it was fatal and whammo.

399
00:36:31,850 --> 00:36:32,960
就像是没了
It's, like, out.

400
00:36:32,980 --> 00:36:35,020
就像关掉了电视
Like turning off a TV.

401
00:36:35,020 --> 00:36:36,270
然后我知道了你父母的事
Then I learned about your parents

402
00:36:36,270 --> 00:36:39,550
还有他们对死后之事  这类东西的探索...
and their whole exploration into the afterlife and stuff...

403
00:36:41,860 --> 00:36:43,140
他们给了我希望
and they gave me hope.

404
00:36:44,570 --> 00:36:47,640
也许生命还是会继续的
That maybe life goes on somehow.

405
00:36:49,790 --> 00:36:50,890
也许
Maybe...

406
00:36:51,500 --> 00:36:54,650
我亲爱的爸爸还在某处
my darling dad is still out there somewhere.

407
00:36:56,130 --> 00:36:57,280
"亲爱的爸爸"
"Darling dad"?

408
00:36:57,670 --> 00:36:59,030
这是我们之间的称呼
It was a thing.

409
00:36:59,290 --> 00:37:02,660
他是亲爱的爸爸  我是亲爱的丹妮拉
He was darling dad, and I was darling Daniela...

410
00:37:03,300 --> 00:37:04,410
很蠢
Stupid.

411
00:37:06,180 --> 00:37:07,740
他还在某个地方的
He's still out there, you know.

412
00:37:09,140 --> 00:37:10,120
你这么认为吗
You think so?

413
00:37:10,850 --> 00:37:12,790
我爸爸妈妈也会说他在的
My parents would say he is, too.

414
00:37:33,350 --> 00:37:34,440
你要去哪里
Where are you going?

415
00:37:34,870 --> 00:37:35,860
我马上回来
Be right back.

416
00:37:48,590 --> 00:37:49,580
爸爸
Dad?

417
00:38:06,900 --> 00:38:08,140
丹妮拉
Daniela?

418
00:38:17,830 --> 00:38:18,900
丹妮拉
Daniela!

419
00:38:19,750 --> 00:38:20,730
她去哪里了
Where did she go?

420
00:38:22,840 --> 00:38:23,740
你在干什么
What are you doing?

421
00:38:24,130 --> 00:38:26,200
丹妮拉  你不能下去的
Daniela, you're not supposed to go down there!

422
00:38:28,340 --> 00:38:30,740
-你在干什么  -我以为我看到了什么
- What are you doing? - I thought I saw something.

423
00:38:33,890 --> 00:38:35,040
你看到了什么
What did you see?

424
00:38:38,190 --> 00:38:39,790
算了  不重要
Forget it. It doesn't matter.

425
00:40:19,660 --> 00:40:21,000
想我吗

426
00:41:12,340 --> 00:41:13,370
朱蒂
Judy?

427
00:41:21,930 --> 00:41:22,920
朱蒂
Judy?

428
00:41:27,900 --> 00:41:28,760
朱蒂
Judy?

429
00:41:37,280 --> 00:41:38,180
朱蒂
Judy?

430
00:41:42,830 --> 00:41:44,500
耶和华啊  我信任你
In thee, O Lord, do I put my trust.

431
00:41:44,500 --> 00:41:46,040
你凭你的公义
Let me never be put to confusion.

432
00:41:46,040 --> 00:41:47,750
搭救我
Deliver me into Thy righteousness

433
00:41:47,750 --> 00:41:49,460
救拔我  侧耳听...
and cause me to escape. Incline Thine ear...

434
00:41:49,460 --> 00:41:51,250
朱蒂  朱蒂
Hey! Hey, Judy! Judy.

435
00:41:51,250 --> 00:41:52,650
怎么回事  怎么了
What's going on? What's wrong?

436
00:41:54,760 --> 00:41:55,820
怎么回事
What's going on?

437
00:41:59,890 --> 00:42:01,120
出什么事了
What happened?

438
00:42:02,140 --> 00:42:03,160
没什么
Nothing.

439
00:42:03,640 --> 00:42:04,370
朱蒂
Judy...

440
00:42:07,140 --> 00:42:08,890
我就是害怕
I just got scared.

441
00:42:08,900 --> 00:42:10,880
害怕什么
Scared of what?

442
00:42:14,360 --> 00:42:16,050
有时候
Sometimes...

443
00:42:16,900 --> 00:42:18,240
我会看到一些东西
I see things.

444
00:42:18,240 --> 00:42:20,520
就像我妈妈会看到一些东西一样
Like how my mom sees things.

445
00:42:24,830 --> 00:42:27,310
你是说鬼魂之类的吗
You mean like ghosts?

446
00:42:32,170 --> 00:42:33,650
你是在哪里看到它们的
Where do you see them?

447
00:42:35,920 --> 00:42:37,660
我去哪儿都能看到
Everywhere I go.

448
00:42:43,850 --> 00:42:44,660
朱蒂
Judy...

449
00:42:46,600 --> 00:42:48,080
鬼魂也曾经是人
Ghosts used to be people.

450
00:42:48,980 --> 00:42:51,670
你遇到的每个人都不一定是坏人  所以
And not every person you meet is bad... so

451
00:42:53,190 --> 00:42:56,130
也许不一定每个鬼魂都是坏的
maybe not all ghosts are bad, either.

452
00:43:06,660 --> 00:43:07,690
丹妮拉
Daniela.

453
00:43:08,710 --> 00:43:10,250
-你得来看看这个  -什么
- You have to see this. - What?

454
00:43:10,250 --> 00:43:12,580
这是沃伦夫妇以前接手的一次调查
It's this case the Warrens investigated about this girl

455
00:43:12,580 --> 00:43:15,130
关于一个被摆渡人吓到的女孩
who was terrorized by something called the Ferryman.

456
00:43:15,130 --> 00:43:16,950
这是他杀死的那个女孩的照片
Here's a picture of the girl he killed.

457
00:43:16,960 --> 00:43:18,110
看上去眼熟吗
Look familiar?

458
00:43:18,130 --> 00:43:19,990
你们俩很可能是姐妹呢
I mean, you two could be sisters.

459
00:43:23,260 --> 00:43:26,370
如果你有兴趣的话  这是剩余的档案
Here's the rest of the file, if you want to take a look.

460
00:43:33,690 --> 00:43:35,470
看看这些东西
Look at all this stuff.

461
00:43:40,900 --> 00:43:42,470
真厉害
How cool.

462
00:43:42,860 --> 00:43:45,180
这是黑皮的档案
Okay, this is the file on the Black Shuck.

463
00:43:45,410 --> 00:43:46,620
黑皮
The Black Shuck?

464
00:43:46,620 --> 00:43:48,410
这是沃伦夫妇曾今去英格兰
It was a case the Warrens investigated

465
00:43:48,410 --> 00:43:50,900
调查一个人被一只猎犬附身的事
about a hellhound that possessed a man in England.

466
00:43:52,250 --> 00:43:54,650
整个镇子都被他吓坏了
He terrorized the shit out of this town.

467
00:43:52,290 --> 00:43:55,750
可能是猎犬
迷雾
圣玛丽教堂
公墓

468
00:44:04,390 --> 00:44:06,200
他们眼睛上的硬币是怎么回事
What's with the coins over their eyes?

469
00:44:07,220 --> 00:44:08,040
什么
What?

470
00:44:09,930 --> 00:44:11,390
我不知道  我没有了解得这么深
Oh, I don't know. I didn't get that far.

471
00:44:11,390 --> 00:44:13,270
人们以前都会在死人眼睛上放硬币
They used to put them over the eyes of the dead

472
00:44:13,270 --> 00:44:14,100
好让摆渡人
to pay the Ferryman,

473
00:44:14,100 --> 00:44:16,170
带他的灵魂前往阴间
so he could take their souls to the underworld.

474
00:44:16,730 --> 00:44:18,090
这是他的摆渡费
It was his toll.

475
00:44:18,110 --> 00:44:19,930
我们该离开这里了
Okay, we should go.

476
00:44:20,280 --> 00:44:22,640
没关系  我有时候也喜欢偷溜进来
It's okay. I sometimes like to snoop, too.

477
00:44:22,650 --> 00:44:24,470
你知道这是干什么的吗  朱蒂
Do you know what this does, Judy?

478
00:44:25,280 --> 00:44:28,020
我觉得这应该是吊唁者手镯
I think it's called a Mourner's Bracelet.

479
00:44:30,080 --> 00:44:33,110
这能让你联系你过世的爱着的人
It helps you contact your lost loved ones.

480
00:44:41,460 --> 00:44:42,450
那是什么
What's that?

481
00:44:43,430 --> 00:44:46,290
这是我爸爸妈妈最近在调查的事
It's a case my parents investigated recently.

482
00:44:46,800 --> 00:44:47,670
这件婚纱
The wedding dress.

483
00:44:47,670 --> 00:44:49,870
会缠上人
It haunts people.

484
00:44:52,060 --> 00:44:54,090
会让人变得很暴力
And it makes them violent.

485
00:44:55,400 --> 00:44:56,810
那这件婚纱现在在哪里
Where is the dress now?

486
00:44:56,810 --> 00:44:58,630
在走廊尽头的收藏室里
Down the hall in the artifact room.

487
00:45:01,400 --> 00:45:04,760
我是说  这种东西都在那房间里
I mean, that's where all this stuff is.

488
00:45:04,820 --> 00:45:05,890
对吧  朱蒂
Right, Judy?

489
00:45:05,950 --> 00:45:07,390
你之前就是这么说的
That's what you said earlier.

490
00:45:08,370 --> 00:45:09,410
嗯
Yeah.

491
00:45:09,410 --> 00:45:11,660
我爸爸说你那里面的所有东西
My dad says that everything in there

492
00:45:11,660 --> 00:45:15,020
不是遭到鬼魂影响  就是被诅咒了
is either haunted, cursed,

493
00:45:15,330 --> 00:45:17,610
或者用在某种仪式中
or used in some ritualistic practice.

494
00:45:18,630 --> 00:45:19,920
那里面的那个娃娃呢
What about the doll that's in there?

495
00:45:19,920 --> 00:45:21,630
因为我看过你爸爸的一篇采访
Because I read this interview with your dad...

496
00:45:21,630 --> 00:45:22,360
不
No.

497
00:45:25,180 --> 00:45:26,410
不要提她
Don't talk about her.

498
00:45:29,720 --> 00:45:30,660
为什么
Why not?

499
00:45:35,020 --> 00:45:37,130
她被关起来是有原因的
She's in a case for a reason.

500
00:45:38,650 --> 00:45:40,210
好吧  我们该离开这里
Okay, we should go.

501
00:45:40,360 --> 00:45:41,150
我想看看这里有什么
I wonder what's on this.

502
00:45:41,150 --> 00:45:42,720
不  丹妮拉  等等
No, Daniela! Wait!

503
00:45:44,820 --> 00:45:47,140
我命令你  不洁的灵魂
I command you, unclean spirit,

504
00:45:47,530 --> 00:45:49,310
和你的仆从一起
along with all your minions...

505
00:45:49,700 --> 00:45:50,950
我命令你
I command you

506
00:45:50,950 --> 00:45:53,230
听从我的每一个字
to obey me to the letter!

507
00:45:57,460 --> 00:45:58,420
好了  别闹了
Okay, show's over.

508
00:45:58,420 --> 00:46:00,070
我们去找点别的事做
Let's go do something else.

509
00:46:00,540 --> 00:46:03,530
找点合适的事
Do something that's actually appropriate.

510
00:46:03,630 --> 00:46:04,380
拜托
Come on,

511
00:46:04,380 --> 00:46:06,530
你至少想听听那武士装的故事吧
don't you at least wanna hear about the samurai?

512
00:46:13,140 --> 00:46:14,170
这个呢
What about this one?

513
00:46:13,310 --> 00:46:16,230
触觉配对

514
00:46:14,430 --> 00:46:16,130
我不记得我玩过这个了
I don't remember that one.

515
00:46:16,310 --> 00:46:17,500
怎么玩的
How do you play?

516
00:46:18,190 --> 00:46:20,000
试试看就知道了
Let's find out.

517
00:46:26,740 --> 00:46:28,950
好吧  你要抽一张卡片
Okay. Okay, so you draw a card

518
00:46:28,950 --> 00:46:30,320
你要通过你的触觉
and whatever picture it has on it

519
00:46:30,320 --> 00:46:31,490
在盒子里找到
is the object you try to find

520
00:46:31,490 --> 00:46:33,350
你卡片上的东西
by feeling around inside the box.

521
00:46:33,450 --> 00:46:35,160
如果你抽出来的东西就是卡片上的东西
If the object you pull out matches the picture,

522
00:46:35,160 --> 00:46:36,270
那你就能得一分
then you get a point.

523
00:46:39,250 --> 00:46:40,500
你先来
You go first.

524
00:46:40,500 --> 00:46:41,320
好吧
Okay.

525
00:47:14,950 --> 00:47:16,140
你要去应门吗
You gonna get that?

526
00:47:17,330 --> 00:47:18,310
嗯
Yeah.

527
00:47:18,830 --> 00:47:20,730
抱歉  你们继续玩
Sorry, you guys keep playing.

528
00:47:21,000 --> 00:47:22,150
得一分
Oh, got a point.

529
00:47:23,960 --> 00:47:24,820
不错
Nice.

530
00:47:47,400 --> 00:47:48,180
谁啊
Hello?

531
00:48:06,500 --> 00:48:07,860
你好  玛丽·艾伦
Hi, Mary Ellen.

532
00:48:08,170 --> 00:48:09,160
你好
Hi.

533
00:48:09,840 --> 00:48:11,550
你记不记得在超市里
Remember how, at the store,

534
00:48:11,550 --> 00:48:13,470
丹妮拉说你会来这里做保姆吗
Daniela said that you were babysitting here?

535
00:48:13,470 --> 00:48:14,430
嗯
Yeah. Yeah.

536
00:48:14,430 --> 00:48:15,370
我也记得
Me, too.

537
00:48:16,550 --> 00:48:18,540
不管怎么样  所以我才过来的
Anyways, that's why I'm here.

538
00:48:19,930 --> 00:48:24,480
鲍勃  他们不希望我带男孩来
Bob, they don't really want me having boys over.

539
00:48:24,480 --> 00:48:26,730
不  我不是这个意思  我不想进去
No, that's not what I meant. I don't wanna come in.

540
00:48:26,730 --> 00:48:27,840
我只是...
I just, uh...

541
00:48:28,230 --> 00:48:30,050
我是说  我也想  但是
I mean, I would, but...

542
00:48:30,320 --> 00:48:31,090
那个...
Well...

543
00:48:32,400 --> 00:48:34,100
我只是知道你会在这里
I just knew you were gonna be here,

544
00:48:34,450 --> 00:48:38,580
我只是想过来和你说说话
and I just wanted to come by and talk to you

545
00:48:38,580 --> 00:48:40,450
没有我那笨蛋老爹或者其他人来打扰
without my stupid dad or somebody interrupting.

546
00:48:40,450 --> 00:48:42,400
大胆鲍勃
Bob's-Got-Balls!

547
00:48:44,080 --> 00:48:45,360
不错啊
Nice.

548
00:48:45,540 --> 00:48:47,360
你们俩要一起吃披萨吗
You two sharing some pizza?

549
00:48:48,920 --> 00:48:50,360
我去拿钱
I should get the money.

550
00:48:53,010 --> 00:48:54,530
你们俩是...
Are you two, like...

551
00:48:54,930 --> 00:48:56,740
我...我也想呢
I... I wish.

552
00:48:57,140 --> 00:49:00,080
你知道你得唬唬她吧
You know you need to, like, woo her, right?

553
00:49:00,850 --> 00:49:01,960
唬唬她
Woo her?

554
00:49:02,060 --> 00:49:06,210
玛丽·艾伦这样的家伙得唬唬
Yeah. Guys like Mary Ellen, they need to be wooed.

555
00:49:07,270 --> 00:49:09,300
你是说玛丽·艾伦这样的女孩吗
You mean girls like Mary Ellen.

556
00:49:09,480 --> 00:49:10,590
我刚刚说了什么
What did I say?

557
00:49:10,820 --> 00:49:11,840
家伙
Guys.

558
00:49:13,240 --> 00:49:14,640
那我要怎么唬唬她
So, how do I woo her?

559
00:49:15,200 --> 00:49:17,010
唬唬只有一个办法
There's only one way to woo.

560
00:49:17,570 --> 00:49:18,770
很明显
It's obvious.

561
00:49:19,490 --> 00:49:20,890
摇滚
Rock and roll.

562
00:49:24,460 --> 00:49:25,730
给  不用找了
Here. Keep it.

563
00:49:25,750 --> 00:49:26,820
太好了
Sweet.

564
00:49:26,830 --> 00:49:29,610
谢谢  那也就是说这个可以给你了
Thanks, and that means you can keep this.

565
00:49:30,210 --> 00:49:31,900
少一片
Minus one slice.

566
00:49:32,260 --> 00:49:34,240
我在车里吃了
I enjoyed that in the car.

567
00:49:34,420 --> 00:49:35,780
回头见  大胆
See you later, Balls.

568
00:49:36,800 --> 00:49:39,300
我也想邀请你进来  但是我也说了...
I would invite you in, but like I said...

569
00:49:39,300 --> 00:49:40,800
不  没关系
No, yeah, it's cool.

570
00:49:40,810 --> 00:49:44,000
我想着只是来打个招呼  所以...
I thought I'd just stop by and say hi, I guess, so...

571
00:49:44,560 --> 00:49:45,750
我见到你很高兴
I'm glad you did.

572
00:49:46,640 --> 00:49:47,420
我也是
Me, too.

573
00:49:50,980 --> 00:49:52,800
鲍勃
Hey, Bob, um...

574
00:49:53,440 --> 00:49:54,930
他们为什么要这么叫你
How come they call you that?

575
00:49:57,780 --> 00:49:59,660
你知道我是篮球队的
Well, you know how I'm the equipments manager

576
00:49:59,660 --> 00:50:01,020
设备管理员吧
for the basketball team?

577
00:50:01,580 --> 00:50:03,040
-嗯  -这就是原因
- Yeah. - That's why.

578
00:50:03,040 --> 00:50:05,870
其实没有什么背后的故事什么的
There's not really, like, a story or anything behind it.

579
00:50:05,870 --> 00:50:07,210
就是"喂  我要球"
Just like, "Hey, I need balls."

580
00:50:07,210 --> 00:50:07,940
我就说
I'm, like,

581
00:50:08,290 --> 00:50:10,320
"球来了  接着"[胆子]
"I got it. Balls. Got 'em."

582
00:50:13,630 --> 00:50:14,840
唬头见
I'll see woo later.

583
00:50:14,840 --> 00:50:16,720
我是说  回头见
You. You. I'll see you later.

584
00:50:16,720 --> 00:50:17,830
我先走了
I'm gonna go.

585
00:50:19,090 --> 00:50:20,040
再见  鲍勃
Bye, Bob.

586
00:50:20,300 --> 00:50:21,200
再见
Bye.

587
00:50:32,730 --> 00:50:33,400
好了  卡洛琳
All right, Carolyn,

588
00:50:33,400 --> 00:50:35,230
连灵媒都不可能预言到
even a fortune teller couldn't have predicted

589
00:50:35,240 --> 00:50:36,990
我们为你和唐选择的约会对象
the place we picked for your date with Don.

590
00:50:36,990 --> 00:50:38,990
因为谁能想到
Because who could ever have dreamed up a place

591
00:50:38,990 --> 00:50:41,270
像内华达州的拉斯维加斯
as unbelievably fabulus as

592
00:50:41,280 --> 00:50:43,430
这么棒的地方
Las Vegas, Nevada?

593
00:50:45,120 --> 00:50:46,790
没错  就是这么棒
Yes, "amazing" is the word for it.

594
00:50:46,790 --> 00:50:48,160
你们将一路飞到
You'll be flying off for a fling

595
00:50:48,160 --> 00:50:50,330
拉斯维加斯的市中心
at the fabulous town of Las Vegas,

596
00:50:50,330 --> 00:50:52,710
在弗朗明哥大酒店下榻
to be guests of the fantastic Flamingo Hotel,

597
00:50:52,710 --> 00:50:54,840
那可是拉斯维加斯大道最受欢迎的地方
a favorite spot along the Vegas Strip.

598
00:50:54,840 --> 00:50:57,840
道恩 我们还为你准备了特殊的礼物
And, Dawn, as a little special gift for you...

599
00:50:57,840 --> 00:50:59,200
你能把手伸过来吗
Can you get your arms around there?

600
00:52:03,530 --> 00:52:04,850
玛丽·艾伦
Mary Ellen?

601
00:52:07,740 --> 00:52:09,100
丹妮拉
Daniela?

602
00:52:11,460 --> 00:52:15,280
祝你生日快乐*
*Happy birthday to you

603
00:52:15,380 --> 00:52:18,570
祝你生日快乐*
*Happy birthday to you

604
00:52:18,710 --> 00:52:22,280
祝你生日快乐  亲爱的朱蒂*
*Happy birthday, dear Judy

605
00:52:22,430 --> 00:52:25,450
祝你生日快乐*
*Happy birthday to you

606
00:52:30,390 --> 00:52:31,630
好了  朱蒂
Okay, Judy.

607
00:52:31,810 --> 00:52:32,920
准备好上床睡觉了吗
Ready for bed?

608
00:52:35,730 --> 00:52:36,920
这是给你的
This is for you.

609
00:52:36,940 --> 00:52:38,050
这是什么
What's this?

610
00:52:39,860 --> 00:52:41,030
你被邀请啦

611
00:52:41,240 --> 00:52:43,470
这是我生日派对的邀请函
It's an invitation to my birthday party.

612
00:52:41,280 --> 00:52:43,200
丹妮拉·莱欧斯
你被邀请前往维曼街3506号
参加生日宴会

613
00:52:45,030 --> 00:52:46,970
我觉得不会有多少人来
I don't think many people are gonna come...

614
00:52:48,240 --> 00:52:49,310
但你会来吗
but will you?

615
00:52:54,710 --> 00:52:56,030
看看我拿到了什么
You see what I got?

616
00:52:56,170 --> 00:52:57,650
我几周前就拿到了
I got mine weeks ago.

617
00:52:59,340 --> 00:53:00,360
那你会来吧
So, you'll come?

618
00:53:00,550 --> 00:53:01,820
我绝对不会错过的
I wouldn't miss it.

619
00:53:03,420 --> 00:53:06,330
你保护我不被伤害*
*You sheltered me from harm

620
00:53:07,220 --> 00:53:08,260
你让我温暖*
*You kept me warm

621
00:53:08,260 --> 00:53:09,410
什么声音
What's that?

622
00:53:10,390 --> 00:53:11,350
你让我温暖*
*You kept me warm

623
00:53:11,350 --> 00:53:12,710
天啊
Oh, my God.

624
00:53:13,640 --> 00:53:14,710
不是吧
It isn't.

625
00:53:15,270 --> 00:53:16,210
真的是
It is.

626
00:53:18,060 --> 00:53:20,880
你保护我不被伤害*
*You sheltered me from harm

627
00:53:21,980 --> 00:53:24,510
你让我温暖*
*You kept me warm

628
00:53:25,240 --> 00:53:26,600
你让我*
*You kept me

629
00:53:27,200 --> 00:53:30,390
温暖*
*warm

630
00:53:31,540 --> 00:53:34,310
-鲍勃  -*你让我的生命*
- Bob! - *You gave my life...

631
00:53:44,470 --> 00:53:48,830
没有人会知道*
*Nobody else will ever know

632
00:53:51,430 --> 00:53:54,830
我无法放弃的内心*
*The part of me That can't let go

633
00:53:54,930 --> 00:53:59,960
我愿意放弃我的一切*
*I would give anything I own

634
00:54:02,530 --> 00:54:03,650
鲍勃胆子真大
Bob's got balls.

635
00:54:03,650 --> 00:54:05,360
只为让你回到身边*
*Just to have you back again

636
00:54:05,360 --> 00:54:06,820
我看上去怎么样  我的吸入器呢
How do I look? Where's my inhaler?

637
00:54:06,820 --> 00:54:08,970
该死  不  在我车里  我该怎么办
Shit, no, it's in my car. What am I supposed to do?

638
00:54:09,280 --> 00:54:10,870
你没事的
You will be fine.

639
00:54:10,870 --> 00:54:11,980
只是鲍勃而已
It's only Bob.

640
00:54:12,830 --> 00:54:14,810
只为再次触碰你*
*Just to touch you once again

641
00:54:32,600 --> 00:54:33,540
该死
Shit!

642
00:54:33,640 --> 00:54:34,420
操
Fuck!

643
00:54:34,720 --> 00:54:35,750
该死
Shit!

644
00:54:37,770 --> 00:54:38,880
不
No!

645
00:54:45,360 --> 00:54:46,340
鲍勃
Bob?

646
00:54:51,320 --> 00:54:52,390
他走了
He left.

647
00:54:52,990 --> 00:54:54,770
希望他是回家练习去了
Hopefully he went home to practice.

648
00:54:55,040 --> 00:54:56,560
好了  回床上去
Okay. Back up to bed.

649
00:54:56,660 --> 00:54:57,770
丹妮拉
Daniela.

650
00:55:05,050 --> 00:55:06,910
如果你能让我留下来  我能更安心
I'd feel better if you let me stay.

651
00:55:07,050 --> 00:55:08,630
我可以早点起来  我们都不用告诉朱蒂
I can wake up early. We don't even have to tell Judy.

652
00:55:08,630 --> 00:55:10,240
不  不  没关系
No. No, it's fine.

653
00:55:10,380 --> 00:55:11,120
回家去吧
Go home.

654
00:55:12,800 --> 00:55:13,580
但是
But...

655
00:55:13,760 --> 00:55:14,750
什么但是
But what?

656
00:55:15,560 --> 00:55:16,670
谢谢你能来
Thank you for coming.

657
00:55:16,890 --> 00:55:18,880
我觉得你让朱蒂好受多了
I actually think it helped Judy a lot.

658
00:55:19,640 --> 00:55:20,980
很抱歉没让你看到什么蜘蛛网
Sorry you didn't get to see any cobwebs

659
00:55:20,980 --> 00:55:22,230
或听到什么可怕的音乐
or hear any creepy music.

660
00:55:22,230 --> 00:55:24,970
至少鲍勃那一出还是有点可怕的
Well, the Bob thing was kind of creepy, at least.

661
00:55:25,900 --> 00:55:28,740
但是如果鲍勃半夜来敲门
But if Bob comes knocking on this door late at night,

662
00:55:28,740 --> 00:55:30,850
你就放飞自我  让他进来吧
forget you're you for a minute and let him in.

663
00:55:33,620 --> 00:55:35,730
明天给我打电话  分享细节
Call me tomorrow and tell me the details.

664
00:55:36,370 --> 00:55:38,440
没什么好分享的细节
There will be no details to tell.

665
00:56:03,270 --> 00:56:04,510
该死
Shit.

666
00:57:29,070 --> 00:57:30,510
她的爸爸是怎么死的
How'd her dad die?

667
00:57:32,230 --> 00:57:34,600
我觉得不该把这当做睡前故事来讲
I don't know if that's the best bedtime story.

668
00:57:35,740 --> 00:57:37,470
你看看我爸妈是谁
Look who my parents are.

669
00:57:37,700 --> 00:57:39,100
我早就习惯了
I'm used to it.

670
00:57:40,410 --> 00:57:41,440
好吧
Well,

671
00:57:41,450 --> 00:57:45,310
简短的版本就是  他死于车祸
the short of it is that he died in a car accident.

672
00:57:45,670 --> 00:57:48,690
多说一两句就是...
And the long of it is that...

673
00:57:49,000 --> 00:57:50,650
当时开车的人是丹妮拉
Daniela was driving.

674
00:57:52,300 --> 00:57:53,910
是她的错吗
Was it her fault?

675
00:57:54,010 --> 00:57:54,780
不是
No.

676
00:57:55,510 --> 00:57:56,550
只有一个人
There's only one person

677
00:57:56,550 --> 00:57:58,450
觉得是她的错
who actually thinks it was her fault.

678
00:59:51,620 --> 00:59:52,570
好吧
Okay.

679
00:59:53,540 --> 00:59:54,940
我们再来试试
Let's try this again.

680
00:59:58,380 --> 01:00:00,320
如果这里有鬼...
If there is a presence here...

681
01:00:39,420 --> 01:00:40,360
爸爸
Dad?

682
01:01:49,580 --> 01:01:50,640
爸爸
Dad.

683
01:01:55,540 --> 01:01:57,230
是你害死我的
You did this to me!

684
01:01:57,630 --> 01:01:59,070
都是你的错
It's all your fault!

685
01:01:59,170 --> 01:02:00,530
回来
Get back here!

686
01:02:02,500 --> 01:02:07,430
危险
请勿触碰任何东西

687
01:02:02,800 --> 01:02:04,160
都是你害死我的
You did this to me!

688
01:02:44,710 --> 01:02:45,840
不不不  拜托
No, no, no. Please.

689
01:02:45,840 --> 01:02:47,870
拜托  不  别走  别走
Please, no, no. Don't go. Don't go.

690
01:02:55,810 --> 01:02:56,980
不不不  过来
No, no, no. No, come here.

691
01:02:56,980 --> 01:02:58,960
过来  过来  不  不
Come here, come here. No. No.

692
01:03:09,490 --> 01:03:10,600
对不起
I'm sorry.

693
01:05:07,020 --> 01:05:08,010
朱蒂
Judy?

694
01:05:56,280 --> 01:05:58,450
他是这样把她从橱子里抓走的吗
Is that why he picked her up from the closet?

695
01:05:58,450 --> 01:06:00,030
是的  肯定是这样的
Yes. That must have been it.

696
01:06:00,030 --> 01:06:02,200
他会把她从橱里抓走  对吗
He's not gonna pick her up in a closet, is he?

697
01:06:02,200 --> 01:06:04,810
你待在这里  不要出声
You stay here and don't make any noise.

698
01:08:05,950 --> 01:08:07,560
怎么回事
What is happening?

699
01:08:09,500 --> 01:08:11,190
怎么回事
What is happening?

700
01:08:18,380 --> 01:08:19,490
我的咖啡呢
Where's my coffee?

701
01:08:20,720 --> 01:08:21,670
早上好
Good morning.

702
01:08:21,680 --> 01:08:23,050
你遇到了超自然...
You've been experiencing supernatural...

703
01:08:23,050 --> 01:08:24,640
早上好  我的咖啡呢
Good morning. Where's my coffee?

704
01:08:24,640 --> 01:08:25,830
等一下
Just a second.

705
01:08:34,480 --> 01:08:36,340
他的眼睛上有银色的硬币
He had silver coins for his eyes.

706
01:08:37,020 --> 01:08:39,930
她说他的光能指引你前往死亡之地
She said his light shows you the way to the land of the dead.

707
01:08:40,320 --> 01:08:42,180
我只是想找到我的妹妹
I just wanna find my sister.

708
01:08:43,950 --> 01:08:45,520
她第一次看到他是什么时候
And when did she first see him?

709
01:08:45,700 --> 01:08:47,270
在他抓走她不久前
Not long before he took her.

710
01:08:48,200 --> 01:08:51,520
她说她醒来  他就在她的房间
She said she'd wake up, and he'd be in her room...

711
01:08:53,040 --> 01:08:54,440
看着她睡觉
watching her sleep.

712
01:08:56,040 --> 01:08:57,400
她不见的那晚
The night she went missing,

713
01:08:57,960 --> 01:08:59,650
我们都被一个声音吵醒了
we both woke up to a noise.

714
01:09:00,670 --> 01:09:03,160
听上去像是硬币掉到地板上的声音
It sounded like a coin falling on the floor.

715
01:09:05,430 --> 01:09:07,120
她要我在房间里等着
She told me to wait in her room.

716
01:09:08,970 --> 01:09:10,080
我就等着她
So I did.

717
01:09:12,020 --> 01:09:13,670
她再也没回来
She never came back.

718
01:09:15,190 --> 01:09:19,170
我就去找她  结果走到了一个长长的走廊上
I went to look for her and ended up in a long hallway.

719
01:09:20,690 --> 01:09:22,260
走廊里全是棺材
Filled with coffins.

720
01:09:24,030 --> 01:09:24,850
昨晚
Last night...

721
01:09:26,280 --> 01:09:27,810
我又被一个声音吵醒
I woke up to a noise.

722
01:09:28,660 --> 01:09:30,520
又是一枚硬币落地的声音
Another coin being dropped.

723
01:09:33,120 --> 01:09:34,690
他好像在
It was like he was...

724
01:09:35,420 --> 01:09:37,860
他好像在召唤我
Like he was calling me.

725
01:09:38,920 --> 01:09:40,700
你有没有见到过摆渡人
Have you ever seen the Ferryman?

726
01:09:42,460 --> 01:09:44,370
你不付他摆渡费
If you don't pay his toll,

727
01:09:44,970 --> 01:09:46,450
他就会夺走你的灵魂
he'll take your soul.

728
01:09:48,760 --> 01:09:51,580
你不付他摆渡费  他就会夺走你的灵魂
If you don't pay his toll, he'll take your soul.

729
01:09:52,850 --> 01:09:54,330
你不付他摆渡费
If you don't pay his toll,

730
01:09:54,520 --> 01:09:55,960
他就会夺走你的灵魂
he'll take your soul.

731
01:09:57,270 --> 01:10:00,260
你不付他摆渡费  他就会夺走你的灵魂
If you don't pay his toll, he'll take your soul.

732
01:10:01,530 --> 01:10:03,930
你不付他摆渡费  他就会夺走你的灵魂
If you don't pay his toll, he'll take your soul.

733
01:13:55,470 --> 01:13:57,620
该死  该死  不
Shit! Shit! Shit! No.

734
01:14:53,820 --> 01:14:56,010
朱蒂  朱蒂
Judy! Judy!

735
01:14:56,780 --> 01:14:57,890
朱蒂
Judy!

736
01:14:59,570 --> 01:15:00,560
朱蒂
Judy!

737
01:15:01,570 --> 01:15:03,390
朱蒂  开门  朱蒂
Judy! Open the door, Judy!

738
01:16:50,730 --> 01:16:53,130
我喜欢你的娃娃
I like your dolls.

739
01:17:00,110 --> 01:17:01,720
朱蒂  朱蒂
Judy! Judy!

740
01:17:10,450 --> 01:17:11,770
从后门出去
Go out the back!

741
01:17:19,050 --> 01:17:20,450
我们被困住了
We're trapped.

742
01:17:26,220 --> 01:17:27,680
-喂  -谢天谢地
- Hello? - Oh, thank God.

743
01:17:27,680 --> 01:17:29,210
-沃伦太太  -妈妈
- Mrs. Warren? - Mom?

744
01:17:29,260 --> 01:17:30,560
玛丽·艾伦  朱蒂
Mary Ellen? Judy?

745
01:17:30,560 --> 01:17:32,140
一切都还好吗  没事吧
Is everything okay? What's going on?

746
01:17:32,140 --> 01:17:33,210
朱蒂没事
Judy's fine.

747
01:17:34,230 --> 01:17:36,190
你的房子里发生了一些奇怪的事
Something is happening inside your house

748
01:17:36,190 --> 01:17:38,400
我觉得我们现在出去不安全
and I don't think it's safe to go outside.

749
01:17:38,400 --> 01:17:40,300
我们不知道该怎么办
We're not really sure what to do.

750
01:17:41,820 --> 01:17:43,680
能让我和安娜贝尔说说话吗
Can I speak to Annabelle?

751
01:17:47,820 --> 01:17:48,850
什么
I'm sorry?

752
01:17:49,370 --> 01:17:51,940
你要给她一个灵魂  亲爱的
You need to give her a soul, dear.

753
01:17:53,660 --> 01:17:57,480
-什么  -一个灵魂  她要她的灵魂
- What? - A soul. She wants her soul.

754
01:17:58,170 --> 01:17:59,780
给我她的灵魂
Give me her soul.

755
01:19:34,560 --> 01:19:35,710
等等  不要
Wait! Don't!

756
01:19:37,060 --> 01:19:38,000
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.

757
01:19:38,060 --> 01:19:39,170
你在这里干什么
What are you doing here?

758
01:19:53,990 --> 01:19:57,050
想我吗

759
01:20:00,000 --> 01:20:01,070
安娜贝尔
Annabelle.

760
01:20:01,540 --> 01:20:04,150
那个娃娃  这一切都是她干的
The doll. She's the one who's doing all of this.

761
01:20:04,960 --> 01:20:05,900
一个娃娃
A doll?

762
01:20:06,710 --> 01:20:08,910
她想要一个灵魂
She wants a soul.

763
01:20:16,260 --> 01:20:18,540
我只是想再见到他
I just wanted to see him again.

764
01:20:21,140 --> 01:20:22,460
你做了什么
What did you do?

765
01:20:23,980 --> 01:20:26,720
我想告诉他我很抱歉
I wanted to tell him I'm sorry.

766
01:20:27,480 --> 01:20:29,390
我知道那就是我的错
I know it was my fault.

767
01:20:30,280 --> 01:20:31,300
丹妮拉
Daniela...

768
01:20:32,490 --> 01:20:33,930
你做了什么
what did you do?

769
01:20:36,910 --> 01:20:38,480
我把她放了出来
I let her out.

770
01:20:39,620 --> 01:20:41,560
你还碰了什么东西
What else did you touch?

771
01:20:45,590 --> 01:20:46,990
所有东西
Everything.

772
01:20:53,890 --> 01:20:56,200
快跑  快跑
Run! Run! Go!

773
01:21:03,350 --> 01:21:04,300
玛丽·艾伦
Mary Ellen!

774
01:21:05,480 --> 01:21:07,720
是她的哮喘  她发作了
It's her asthma. She's having an attack.

775
01:21:07,860 --> 01:21:09,180
吸入器在她的车里
The inhaler's in her car.

776
01:21:09,860 --> 01:21:10,890
我去拿
I'll go get it.

777
01:21:12,650 --> 01:21:13,760
不  我去
No! Let me!

778
01:22:44,660 --> 01:22:46,150
朱蒂  快跑
Judy! Run!

779
01:23:07,140 --> 01:23:08,210
玛丽·艾伦
Mary Ellen!

780
01:23:09,850 --> 01:23:10,590
给
Here.

781
01:23:13,150 --> 01:23:14,090
你没事吧
Are you okay?

782
01:23:20,070 --> 01:23:22,680
丹妮拉呢  她本来在你后面的
Where's Daniela? She came after you.

783
01:23:23,580 --> 01:23:25,690
玛丽·艾伦  朱蒂
Mary Ellen? Judy?

784
01:23:25,870 --> 01:23:27,310
-我在这里  -不
- I'm up here. - No.

785
01:23:28,080 --> 01:23:29,360
那不是丹妮拉
That's not Daniela.

786
01:23:30,750 --> 01:23:33,030
有东西控制住她了  我能感觉到
Something has a hold of her. I can feel it.

787
01:23:38,380 --> 01:23:39,260
我们该怎么办
What do we do?

788
01:23:39,260 --> 01:23:40,700
我们要找到安娜贝尔
We have to find Annabelle.

789
01:23:41,930 --> 01:23:43,700
我们要把她放回到盒子里
We have to put her back in the case.

790
01:23:44,310 --> 01:23:45,460
你知道她在哪里吗
Do you know where she is?

791
01:23:48,730 --> 01:23:49,590
不知道
No.

792
01:24:17,710 --> 01:24:19,320
等等  朱蒂  别去
Wait, wait, Judy, don't.

793
01:24:25,640 --> 01:24:27,330
不是所有鬼都是坏的
Not all ghosts are bad.

794
01:24:28,890 --> 01:24:29,790
对吧
Right?

795
01:24:48,830 --> 01:24:50,150
不是所有鬼都是坏的
Not all ghosts are bad.

796
01:24:51,870 --> 01:24:52,900
不是所有鬼都是坏的
Not all ghosts are bad.

797
01:24:55,040 --> 01:24:56,240
不是所有鬼都是坏的
Not all ghosts are bad.

798
01:24:57,630 --> 01:24:58,700
不是所有鬼都是坏的
Not all ghosts are bad.

799
01:25:52,350 --> 01:25:53,580
你说什么
What did you say?

800
01:25:54,440 --> 01:25:55,710
我们走
Come on, let's go.

801
01:26:21,880 --> 01:26:22,650
快点
Come on.

802
01:26:38,060 --> 01:26:39,050
我去拿她
I'll get her.

803
01:26:45,030 --> 01:26:47,050
不不不  停下
No, no, no. No! Just stop!

804
01:26:50,120 --> 01:26:51,480
你父母把钥匙放在哪里
Where do your parents keep the key?

805
01:26:51,580 --> 01:26:53,350
我不知道  这上面从来没锁
I don't know. It's never locked.

806
01:27:17,810 --> 01:27:19,340
我知道钥匙在哪里
I know where the key is.

807
01:27:24,400 --> 01:27:26,390
-我来拿  -不  不要
- I'll get it. - No! No, don't.

808
01:27:27,570 --> 01:27:28,640
我来
I'll do it.

809
01:27:43,630 --> 01:27:44,440
朱蒂
Judy!

810
01:27:46,380 --> 01:27:47,410
我拿到了
I got it.

811
01:28:20,750 --> 01:28:25,650
我们在天的父  愿你的名被尊为圣
Our Father, who art in heaven hallowed be Thy name.

812
01:29:41,330 --> 01:29:42,940
我的天啊
Oh, my God.

813
01:30:24,750 --> 01:30:25,960
我们日用的饮食  今日赐给我们
Give us this day our daily bread,

814
01:30:25,960 --> 01:30:27,250
免我们的债
and forgive us for our trespasses

815
01:30:27,250 --> 01:30:29,150
如同我们免了人的债
as we forgive those who trespassed against us.

816
01:30:38,840 --> 01:30:40,000
玛丽·艾伦
Mary Ellen?

817
01:30:47,690 --> 01:30:48,590
快走
Go!

818
01:30:55,900 --> 01:30:56,850
丹妮拉
Daniela.

819
01:30:57,030 --> 01:30:58,220
丹妮拉  求你了
Daniela, please!

820
01:31:09,170 --> 01:31:10,940
丹妮拉  住手
Daniela, stop!

821
01:31:17,300 --> 01:31:18,160
住手
Stop!

822
01:31:30,520 --> 01:31:32,710
我命令你  不洁的灵魂
I command you, unclean spirit,

823
01:31:33,230 --> 01:31:35,050
和一同冒犯
along with all your minions,

824
01:31:35,190 --> 01:31:36,980
上帝仆从的仆从
now attacking this servant of God.

825
01:31:36,990 --> 01:31:39,760
-我命令你听从我的每一个字  -朱蒂  快跑
- I command you to obey me to the letter. - Judy, run!

826
01:31:40,070 --> 01:31:42,890
以祂之名  他们将用祂之手
In his name, they will take up serpents...

827
01:31:44,700 --> 01:31:46,310
铲除毒蛇  责罚邪恶
...with his hands and condemn all evil.

828
01:31:47,120 --> 01:31:49,480
我命令你  不洁的灵魂
I command you, unclean spirit,

829
01:31:50,210 --> 01:31:52,230
和你的仆从
along with all your minions,

830
01:31:53,000 --> 01:31:55,500
-听从我的每一个字  -不  不
- To obey me to the letter. - No, no.

831
01:31:55,500 --> 01:31:58,130
我  上帝的仆从
I, who am a servant of God...

832
01:31:58,130 --> 01:32:00,740
我命令你  不洁的灵魂
I command you, unclean spirit,

833
01:32:01,260 --> 01:32:03,470
和一同冒犯
along with all your minions,

834
01:32:03,470 --> 01:32:05,540
上帝的仆从的仆从
now attacking this servant of God...

835
01:32:30,460 --> 01:32:31,270
朱蒂
Judy!

836
01:32:48,890 --> 01:32:50,920
朱蒂  朱蒂  朱蒂
Judy! Judy. Judy.

837
01:32:51,020 --> 01:32:52,090
去拿娃娃
Get the doll!

838
01:32:59,900 --> 01:33:01,680
-关上门  -我在努力
- Close it! - I'm trying!

839
01:33:04,070 --> 01:33:05,180
快点
Hurry!

840
01:33:10,540 --> 01:33:13,270
我们在天上的父  愿人都尊你的名为圣
Our Father who art in heaven, hallowed be Thy name.

841
01:33:13,580 --> 01:33:15,120
愿你的国降临  愿你的旨意行在地上
Thy kingdom come, Thy will be done,

842
01:33:15,130 --> 01:33:16,460
如同行在天上
on earth as it is in heaven.

843
01:33:16,460 --> 01:33:17,530
把她放进去
Put her in!

844
01:33:17,920 --> 01:33:19,920
我们日用的饮食  今日赐给我们
Give us this day our daily bread,

845
01:33:19,920 --> 01:33:20,960
免我们的债
and forgive us for our trespasses,

846
01:33:20,960 --> 01:33:22,920
如同我们免了人的债
as we forgive those who trespassed against us,

847
01:33:22,930 --> 01:33:24,180
不叫我们遇见试探
lead us not into temptation,

848
01:33:24,180 --> 01:33:25,540
救我们脱离凶恶
but deliver us from evil...

849
01:33:30,350 --> 01:33:31,250
阿门
Amen.

850
01:33:39,610 --> 01:33:41,180
结束了吗
Is it over?

851
01:33:44,450 --> 01:33:46,260
邪恶已经被压抑了
The evil has been contained.

852
01:33:52,580 --> 01:33:53,480
鲍勃
Bob?

853
01:33:54,120 --> 01:33:56,780
-你们还好吗  -我们没事
- Are you guys okay? - Yeah. We're okay.

854
01:33:58,540 --> 01:33:59,920
-那你还好吗  -不好
- Are you okay? - No!

855
01:33:59,920 --> 01:34:01,490
外面有个狼人
There was a werewolf outside!

856
01:34:02,050 --> 01:34:03,530
你看到了狼人
You saw the werewolf?

857
01:34:04,380 --> 01:34:05,280
是的
Yeah.

858
01:34:05,970 --> 01:34:07,580
他还救了我
He saved me from it.

859
01:34:10,310 --> 01:34:11,250
真的吗
You did?

860
01:34:13,480 --> 01:34:16,340
算是吧
Yeah. Kind of.

861
01:34:16,690 --> 01:34:18,590
也许我们该去别的地方好好聊聊
Maybe we should talk about this somewhere else.

862
01:34:43,210 --> 01:34:47,380
早上好  各位  康涅狄格州
Good morning from the staff of wpkw-pv6

863
01:34:47,380 --> 01:34:49,240
哈特福德六台的观众
in Hartford, Connecticut.

864
01:34:49,930 --> 01:34:53,970
这里是康涅狄格州的哈特福德  这里...
This is Hartford, Connecticut, the land of steady habits...

865
01:34:53,970 --> 01:34:54,890
我爸妈
My parents.

866
01:34:54,890 --> 01:34:56,020
该死  你们不该让男孩进来的
Shit! You're not supposed to have boys over.

867
01:34:56,020 --> 01:34:57,690
我觉得这应该根本不是重点  鲍勃
I think that's the least of our concerns right now, Bob.

868
01:34:57,690 --> 01:34:59,670
对  但我还是该走了
Yeah, yeah. I should probably still get going.

869
01:34:59,690 --> 01:35:01,650
听着  快到返校节了
Hey, listen, um, so Homecoming is coming up

870
01:35:01,650 --> 01:35:03,630
-我想...  -好的  我愿意
- and I would really like... - Yes. I'll... I'll go.

871
01:35:03,650 --> 01:35:04,320
和我一起吗
With me?

872
01:35:04,320 --> 01:35:06,430
是的  如果沃伦夫妇没有先杀死我的话
Yes, if the Warrens don't kill me first.

873
01:35:08,490 --> 01:35:10,140
我们把一切都告诉他们
We tell them everything.

874
01:35:14,910 --> 01:35:15,650
妈妈
Mom!

875
01:35:15,790 --> 01:35:18,230
朱蒂  你怎么这么早就起来了
Judy! What are you doing up so early?

876
01:35:18,500 --> 01:35:19,610
别生气
Don't get mad...

877
01:35:20,040 --> 01:35:21,190
你的车怎么了
What happened to your car?

878
01:35:27,090 --> 01:35:28,120
来
Here we go.

879
01:35:28,590 --> 01:35:30,370
我们享受自己的派对
We'll have our own party, huh?

880
01:35:28,680 --> 01:35:39,800
生日快乐

881
01:35:37,310 --> 01:35:39,170
-怎么了  -你至少能把那个东西拿下来吗
- What? - Can you please take that off?

882
01:35:47,690 --> 01:35:50,310
不会一直这样的  我保证
It won't always be like this, I promise.

883
01:35:50,490 --> 01:35:51,660
你迟早会找到
You know, and sooner or later,

884
01:35:51,660 --> 01:35:53,850
理解你的人
you'll find people who understand.

885
01:35:54,450 --> 01:35:56,650
至于那个小安东尼
And as for young Anthony,

886
01:35:56,700 --> 01:35:58,960
他最好别让我逮到
he better hope I don't run into him anytime soon.

887
01:35:58,960 --> 01:35:59,980
爱德
Ed.

888
01:36:13,850 --> 01:36:15,250
生日快乐  朱蒂
Happy birthday, Judy.

889
01:36:16,520 --> 01:36:17,460
谢谢
Thank you.

890
01:36:17,850 --> 01:36:19,460
生日快乐
Happy birthday.

891
01:36:22,310 --> 01:36:25,340
我和我的弟弟聊了聊
I, uh, had a little talk with my brother.

892
01:36:25,900 --> 01:36:26,800
谢谢
Thanks.

893
01:36:27,440 --> 01:36:28,300
请进
Come in.

894
01:36:29,240 --> 01:36:31,640
我男朋友能进来吗
Is it okay if my boyfriend joins?

895
01:36:32,240 --> 01:36:33,260
当然了
Sure.

896
01:36:36,450 --> 01:36:38,140
谢谢你们邀请我们
Hi, uh, thanks for having us.

897
01:36:39,790 --> 01:36:41,040
大胆鲍勃
Bob's-Got-Balls.

898
01:36:41,040 --> 01:36:41,980
真大胆
No kidding.

899
01:36:42,670 --> 01:36:44,790
-朱蒂  -生日快乐  朱蒂
- Hi, Judy! - Happy birthday, Judy!

900
01:36:44,790 --> 01:36:46,360
-生日快乐  -生日快乐
- Happy birthday! - Happy birthday!

901
01:36:46,380 --> 01:36:48,110
-你好  朱蒂  生日快乐  -欢迎大家
- Hello, Judy, happy birthday. - Hey, guys, welcome.

902
01:36:49,260 --> 01:36:50,280
一直有人来
Keep comin'.

903
01:36:50,970 --> 01:36:52,120
生日快乐  朱蒂
Happy birthday, Judy.

904
01:36:52,510 --> 01:36:54,160
-安东尼  -我真的很抱歉
- Anthony? - I'm really sorry.

905
01:36:54,760 --> 01:36:56,250
我还能参加吗
Am I still invited?

906
01:36:58,520 --> 01:36:59,500
当然了
Sure.

907
01:37:05,150 --> 01:37:06,130
丹妮拉
Daniela?

908
01:37:07,110 --> 01:37:08,550
我有东西给你
I have something for you.

909
01:37:08,900 --> 01:37:09,840
给我吗
For me?

910
01:37:22,000 --> 01:37:23,770
你发现这个房间里
You found out the hard way

911
01:37:24,040 --> 01:37:26,440
有恶灵  也付出了惨痛的代价
that there is a lot of evil in this room.

912
01:37:27,540 --> 01:37:29,650
但是你知道我为什么喜欢这里吗
But you know what I actually like about it?

913
01:37:32,090 --> 01:37:35,240
这里的恶灵
All the evil in here...

914
01:37:36,140 --> 01:37:39,540
都让我能够想起外界的美好
reminds me of all the good that's out there.

915
01:37:55,780 --> 01:37:57,390
亲爱的丹妮拉
Darling Daniela.

916
01:38:02,790 --> 01:38:04,340
是朱蒂和你说的吗
Did Judy tell you that?

917
01:38:04,350 --> 01:38:06,520
不  是你爸爸说的
No. Your dad did.

918
01:38:11,380 --> 01:38:14,820
他还告诉我  他很想你
He also tells me that he misses you.

919
01:38:16,970 --> 01:38:19,330
不要再苛责你自己了
And to stop being so hard on yourself,

920
01:38:20,180 --> 01:38:22,120
因为那并不是你的错
'cause it was not your fault.

921
01:38:32,440 --> 01:38:33,340
谢谢你
Thank you.

922
01:38:37,450 --> 01:38:38,390
对不起
I'm sorry.

923
01:38:39,830 --> 01:38:40,810
没关系
It's okay.

924
01:38:41,160 --> 01:38:41,980
你还年轻
You're young.

925
01:38:47,120 --> 01:38:48,940
我在你这个年纪的时候
You know, when I was about your age,

926
01:38:49,250 --> 01:38:52,450
曾经和我的一任男友在没告诉我父母的情况下
I once ran off with a boyfriend for three days

927
01:38:52,550 --> 01:38:54,280
整整偷跑出去三天
without telling my parents.

928
01:38:57,130 --> 01:38:58,830
我释放出了一个恶魔
I unleashed a demon.

929
01:38:59,180 --> 01:39:00,660
所以这应该不是一码事
So not the same thing.

930
01:39:01,640 --> 01:39:03,580
好吧  没错
Well, okay. True.

931
01:39:09,810 --> 01:39:12,340
沃伦先生知道这一任男友吗
Does Mr. Warren know about this boyfriend?

932
01:39:13,150 --> 01:39:14,590
他就是那个男友
He was the boyfriend.

933
01:39:19,450 --> 01:39:20,850
有人想听歌吗
Anybody wanna hear a song?

934
01:39:25,080 --> 01:39:27,270
好了
All right, okay.

935
01:39:46,640 --> 01:39:55,550
纪念洛琳·沃伦

