1
00:01:37,700 --> 00:01:41,700
{\an8}"父有罪  子受过"
威廉·莎士比亚

2
00:01:44,910 --> 00:01:49,570
{\an8}"没人能像我爸爸一样"
碧昂斯

4
00:03:58,460 --> 00:04:00,210
{\an8}回家的地图

5
00:04:39,300 --> 00:04:43,480
{\an8}《爹来靠》

6
00:05:16,090 --> 00:05:19,970
爸爸  是我  诺瓦尔
Dad, it's me, Norval.

7
00:05:24,360 --> 00:05:27,020
我收到了你的信
Uh, I got your letter.

8
00:05:29,850 --> 00:05:32,980
上面说让我来找你
Your letter asking me to come and see you.

9
00:05:35,680 --> 00:05:36,680
于是
Well...

10
00:05:38,860 --> 00:05:39,900
我就来了
here I am.

11
00:05:41,950 --> 00:05:44,380
是我  诺瓦尔
It's me. Norval.

12
00:05:48,130 --> 00:05:50,740
好
Okay.

13
00:05:53,300 --> 00:05:55,700
老天
Jesus Christ.

14
00:05:57,610 --> 00:06:00,220
没想到还能见到你
I never thought I'd see you again.

15
00:06:13,540 --> 00:06:15,460
进屋吗
Well, you wanna come in?

16
00:06:16,150 --> 00:06:17,630
好的
Yes, please.

17
00:06:22,940 --> 00:06:24,990
欢迎来到我家
Welcome to my house.

18
00:06:27,380 --> 00:06:28,470
我喜欢这儿
I like it.

19
00:06:28,820 --> 00:06:29,990
你不喜欢
You don't.

20
00:06:30,780 --> 00:06:31,860
我喜欢
I do.

21
00:06:33,820 --> 00:06:34,820
为什么
Why?

22
00:06:36,480 --> 00:06:41,090
这儿像个六十年代的不明飞行物
Uh, it's like a UFO from the 1960's.

23
00:06:42,010 --> 00:06:45,490
六十年代的不明飞行物
A UFO from the 1960's.

24
00:06:45,530 --> 00:06:46,530
是的
Yeah.

25
00:06:48,580 --> 00:06:52,150
六十年代的不明飞行物
A UFO from the 1960's.

26
00:06:53,450 --> 00:06:54,500
没错
Exactly.

27
00:06:57,410 --> 00:06:58,670
真有才
That's brilliant.

28
00:07:00,720 --> 00:07:01,720
嗯
Yeah.

29
00:07:02,030 --> 00:07:04,380
上次见你是什么时候  儿子
When did I last see you, son?

30
00:07:06,510 --> 00:07:07,470
不知道
I don't know.

31
00:07:07,510 --> 00:07:08,860
说吧  多久了
Oh, come on. How long's it been?

32
00:07:11,030 --> 00:07:12,040
很久了
A long time.

33
00:07:13,520 --> 00:07:15,300
是很久了
A long time, yeah.

34
00:07:16,870 --> 00:07:17,870
太久了
Too long.

35
00:07:18,300 --> 00:07:21,390
真他妈久  该死
Too fucking long. God damn.

36
00:07:22,260 --> 00:07:24,790
是啊
Yeah.

37
00:07:26,090 --> 00:07:27,090
是的
Yeah.

38
00:07:35,930 --> 00:07:37,760
先去收拾你的行李吧
Let's get you unpacked.

39
00:07:44,400 --> 00:07:45,860
{\an8}《圣境预言书》

40
00:07:53,290 --> 00:07:54,340
喂
Hey.

41
00:07:55,470 --> 00:07:57,120
咱俩合张照吧
Let's get a picture of us.

42
00:07:58,390 --> 00:08:01,000
来张自拍
You know, a selfie photo?

43
00:08:03,650 --> 00:08:05,740
回家后可以给你妈看看
You can show it to your mom when you get home.

44
00:08:16,100 --> 00:08:19,710
不对  得把海照进去
No, no. You gotta get the sea in there.

45
00:08:21,060 --> 00:08:23,500
-来  这样  -小心
- Come on, here. - Careful.

46
00:08:23,540 --> 00:08:25,240
这是洛德设计的
That's a limited edition gold phone,

47
00:08:25,280 --> 00:08:26,410
限量版黄金手机
designed by Lorde.

48
00:08:26,460 --> 00:08:28,550
洛德  从没听说过
Lorde? Never heard of him.

49
00:08:28,590 --> 00:08:30,770
是真金的
It's real gold.

50
00:08:30,810 --> 00:08:33,030
好了  咋样
There we go. How about that, huh?

51
00:08:33,510 --> 00:08:36,210
好的  微笑
Okay. Smile.

52
00:08:36,250 --> 00:08:39,080
该死
Oh, shit.

53
00:08:42,950 --> 00:08:44,610
操
Fuck.

54
00:08:45,820 --> 00:08:48,780
早餐时不该开第二瓶啤酒
Well, I should've never had that second beer for breakfast.

55
00:08:49,390 --> 00:08:52,090
这款手机世界上只有20个
There are only twenty of those phones in the world.

56
00:08:53,570 --> 00:08:54,750
好吧
Yeah.

57
00:08:56,270 --> 00:08:58,400
不  现在只有19个了
No. Now there's nineteen.

58
00:09:08,150 --> 00:09:10,630
你妈妈怎么样
So, how's your mother?

59
00:09:13,030 --> 00:09:14,510
说实话  不太好
Not great, actually.

60
00:09:15,810 --> 00:09:16,810
是吗
Oh?

61
00:09:19,290 --> 00:09:20,990
她提过我吗
She ever talk about me?

62
00:09:22,820 --> 00:09:23,910
没怎么提过
Not really.

63
00:09:26,390 --> 00:09:27,650
你和她住在一起
You live with her?

64
00:09:27,690 --> 00:09:31,650
是的  暂且这样
Yeah, it's a temporary arrangement.

65
00:09:34,570 --> 00:09:36,610
不觉得尴尬吗
You don't feel embarrassed about that?

66
00:09:39,440 --> 00:09:42,230
和妈妈住在一起  都这么大了
Living with your mom? At your age?

67
00:09:43,010 --> 00:09:44,100
不知道
I don't know.

68
00:09:45,540 --> 00:09:47,450
我这几年过得不太顺利
I've had a rough few years.

69
00:09:48,230 --> 00:09:49,930
她帮我渡过了难关
She helped me get me back on my feet.

70
00:09:51,280 --> 00:09:52,590
很复杂
It's complicated.

71
00:09:55,680 --> 00:09:57,030
你和她一起睡吗
You sleep with her?

72
00:09:59,030 --> 00:10:00,160
什么
What?

73
00:10:00,200 --> 00:10:02,770
你和你妈妈睡在一个床上吗
Do you share a bed with your mom?

74
00:10:04,080 --> 00:10:05,160
不是
No.

76
00:10:22,920 --> 00:10:24,880
-来点酒  -不了  谢谢
- Wine? - No, thanks.

77
00:10:26,100 --> 00:10:29,010
来吧  和你老爹喝一杯
Oh, go on. Have a drink with your old man.

78
00:10:29,060 --> 00:10:30,190
我不喝酒
I... I don't drink.

79
00:10:32,240 --> 00:10:33,280
不喝酒
No?

80
00:10:35,850 --> 00:10:37,410
为什么
Why is that?

81
00:10:39,900 --> 00:10:43,200
我得过"酒精依赖症"
I've had what's called "Alcohol dependency issues".

82
00:10:44,600 --> 00:10:47,550
是吗  这真是
Yeah? And that is, uh...

83
00:10:48,160 --> 00:10:50,080
指的是对酒精上瘾
It's when you're dependent on alcohol.

84
00:10:55,560 --> 00:10:56,740
我差点
I nearly...

85
00:11:03,920 --> 00:11:06,920
我留了张字条  放了一缸水
I wrote a note, I ran a bath...

86
00:11:08,580 --> 00:11:09,790
我差点就
I came close.

87
00:11:11,190 --> 00:11:12,580
真的就差一点
Really fucking close.

88
00:11:22,240 --> 00:11:25,810
总之  我来了  活下来了
Anyway, here I am. I survived.

89
00:12:05,720 --> 00:12:06,720
想喝吗
Tempted?

90
00:12:08,240 --> 00:12:09,250
不想
No.

91
00:12:19,390 --> 00:12:20,740
爸爸
So, dad...

92
00:12:22,520 --> 00:12:23,690
你现在做什么
what do you do?

93
00:12:24,910 --> 00:12:25,960
什么工作
For work?

94
00:12:26,650 --> 00:12:28,000
我退休了
I'm retired.

95
00:12:29,090 --> 00:12:30,830
退休前做什么
What did you do before you retired?

96
00:12:31,880 --> 00:12:33,700
我发现自己对你一无所知
I realize I know nothing about you.

97
00:12:34,490 --> 00:12:38,840
儿子  看来你妈妈真没提过我
Boy. Your mom, she really doesn't talk about me, does she?

98
00:12:44,850 --> 00:12:46,500
我以前是个豪车司机
I was a limo driver.

99
00:12:47,850 --> 00:12:52,680
开着一辆黑色豪华大轿车
Yeah, I drove a big black limousine.

100
00:12:53,510 --> 00:12:55,030
里面有冰箱
With a fridge in the back...

101
00:12:56,600 --> 00:12:58,470
还有真皮座椅
real leather seats.

102
00:13:00,040 --> 00:13:03,040
那辆车备受好评
It was an award-winning limousine.

103
00:13:05,130 --> 00:13:07,000
我也坐过豪华轿车
I've been in a few limousines myself.

104
00:13:08,390 --> 00:13:09,740
我是玩音乐的
I'm in the music business.

105
00:13:10,050 --> 00:13:11,050
好吧
Okay.

106
00:13:12,350 --> 00:13:14,480
我在音乐圈混得风生水起
I'm fairly big in the music business.

107
00:13:14,830 --> 00:13:16,230
我想也是
Oh, I bet you are.

108
00:13:17,100 --> 00:13:17,890
你是干什么的
What are you?

109
00:13:17,910 --> 00:13:19,660
歌手还是什么的
A singer or something?

110
00:13:21,750 --> 00:13:24,890
说实在话  我这工作
Well... I'm not someone you can pigeonhole,

111
00:13:25,280 --> 00:13:26,800
说不清
if I'm completely honest.

112
00:13:28,110 --> 00:13:30,410
我是DJ吗  是的
Do I DJ? Yes.

113
00:13:31,330 --> 00:13:34,590
制作很燃的音乐吗  是的
Do I produce blazing beats? Yes.

114
00:13:35,510 --> 00:13:37,720
敲键盘吗  是的
Do I tinkle the ivories? Yes.

115
00:13:38,380 --> 00:13:41,250
组织热门的音乐活动
Do I promote high-profile events pertaining to music

116
00:13:41,290 --> 00:13:43,770
和音乐会吗  也对
and the performance of music? Yes.

117
00:13:45,910 --> 00:13:47,170
好
Okay.

118
00:13:49,610 --> 00:13:51,740
我和一些名人关系很好
I'm close to some pretty big names.

119
00:13:51,780 --> 00:13:53,650
超级大咖  实际上
Substantial names, actually.

120
00:13:54,350 --> 00:13:56,740
肯德里克·拉马尔和钱斯勒·班尼特
I count Kendrick Lamar and Chance the Rapper

121
00:13:54,350 --> 00:13:56,740
{\an8}二者皆为美国说唱歌手

122
00:13:56,790 --> 00:13:58,270
可以算是我的好朋友
among my closest allies.

123
00:13:59,140 --> 00:14:00,970
有没有谁我认识的
Anyone I've actually heard of?

124
00:14:03,530 --> 00:14:05,930
艾尔顿·约翰[英国音乐人]也是我的好朋友
Uh, Elton John is a close friend.

125
00:14:07,190 --> 00:14:09,540
他原名叫雷金纳德·肯尼思·德怀特
His real name is Reginald Kenneth Dwight.

126
00:14:11,450 --> 00:14:14,980
艾尔顿...  雷金纳德发掘了我
Elton... Reginald discovered me.

127
00:14:15,940 --> 00:14:17,980
我在夜店打碟时被他发掘
He saw me DJing at a nightclub.

128
00:14:18,500 --> 00:14:21,420
那是个庆祝会  我是那场的DJ
It was a gala event, and I was the DJ.

129
00:14:22,330 --> 00:14:24,210
他给了我一份独家协议
He signed me to an exclusive deal.

130
00:14:25,470 --> 00:14:27,170
我们当晚就签了合约
We inked the deal that same night.

131
00:14:28,170 --> 00:14:30,300
艾尔顿  雷金纳德
Elton... Uh, Reginald...

132
00:14:31,520 --> 00:14:32,650
他是个很棒的人
he's a great man.

133
00:14:34,220 --> 00:14:36,130
可以说他之于我  如同父亲
You could say he's like a father to me.

134
00:14:37,310 --> 00:14:38,480
无意冒犯
No offence.

135
00:14:40,270 --> 00:14:42,620
儿子  和你讲  世界真小
Boy, I'll tell you. It's a small world.

136
00:14:44,660 --> 00:14:49,970
我恰巧也是雷金纳德的好朋友
I just happen to be a close friend of Reginald's too.

137
00:14:54,670 --> 00:14:56,330
-你也是  -是啊
- You are? - Yeah.

138
00:14:57,670 --> 00:14:59,630
-你撒谎  -没有
- You're lying. - I'm not.

139
00:15:00,330 --> 00:15:02,640
-你就是撒谎  -真没有
- You are. - I'm really not.

140
00:15:03,900 --> 00:15:08,210
不  我和雷金纳德  是老交情了
No. Reginald and I, oh, we go way back.

141
00:15:08,900 --> 00:15:09,900
真的吗
Really?

142
00:15:10,430 --> 00:15:13,860
我当了他10年的私家豪车司机
I was his personal limo driver for 10 years.

143
00:15:16,350 --> 00:15:17,350
没错
Yeah.

144
00:15:19,870 --> 00:15:22,390
我们一起度过了10年
We spent a decade together.

145
00:15:23,790 --> 00:15:27,970
我和雷金纳德  开车  喝酒  谈天说地
Reginald and I, driving, drinking, talking.

146
00:15:29,450 --> 00:15:32,360
成了好朋友
We became close friends.

147
00:15:33,970 --> 00:15:36,710
现在  你和他也是好朋友
Now, what are the odds

148
00:15:36,760 --> 00:15:41,020
这也太巧了
that you would be close friends with him too?

149
00:15:45,030 --> 00:15:46,030
是
Yeah.

150
00:15:47,680 --> 00:15:49,380
世界真小
Small world.

151
00:15:51,120 --> 00:15:54,380
-总之  -我跟你讲
- So, anyway... - I'll tell you what...

152
00:15:56,170 --> 00:15:57,210
什么
What?

153
00:15:58,340 --> 00:15:59,430
咱们给他打个电话吧
Let's call him.

1
00:16:00,481 --> 00:16:02,396
-雷金纳德  -是啊
- Reginald? - Yeah.

2
00:16:03,049 --> 00:16:07,053
这会让他大吃一惊  开玩笑
It'll blow his fucking mind. Are you kidding?

3
00:16:08,097 --> 00:16:10,360
布莱恩和诺瓦尔  他的老伙计们
Brian and Norval, his old pals

4
00:16:10,404 --> 00:16:13,320
恰好是父子
just happen to be father and son.

5
00:16:13,363 --> 00:16:15,148
-难以置信  -我不知道  爸
- Incredible. - I don't know, Dad.

6
00:16:15,191 --> 00:16:18,064
现在  很晚了  他休息得很早
It... It's late. He goes to bed early.

7
00:16:18,412 --> 00:16:19,587
胡扯
Bullshit.

8
00:16:20,109 --> 00:16:23,112
他是如假包换的夜猫子  而且他对此津津乐道
He's a card-carrying night owl, and he never shuts up about it.

9
00:16:23,156 --> 00:16:25,071
他叫我八点后千万别再打他电话了
He told me to never call him after 8:00.

10
00:16:25,114 --> 00:16:27,812
他叫我随时打他电话  全天候
he told me to call him any time, night or day.

11
00:16:32,165 --> 00:16:34,776
爸  求你了  别打给他
Dad, please, don't call him.

12
00:16:37,605 --> 00:16:39,868
求你了  别打给他了  爸
Please. Don't call him, Dad.

13
00:16:43,698 --> 00:16:44,699
求你了
Please!

14
00:16:53,099 --> 00:16:55,666
你不是真的认识艾尔顿·约翰吧
You don't really know Elton John, do you?

15
00:16:59,975 --> 00:17:00,976
你认识吗
Do you?

17
00:17:09,985 --> 00:17:12,814
不  我  我不是真的认识艾尔顿·约翰
No. I... I don't really know Elton John.

18
00:17:17,340 --> 00:17:20,865
实际上  我也不认识
As a matter of fact, neither do I.

19
00:17:26,523 --> 00:17:28,743
不过我很高兴我们证实了
But I'm glad we've established

20
00:17:29,091 --> 00:17:30,832
你是屁话连篇
that you're full of shit.

21
00:17:59,556 --> 00:18:04,039
顺便告诉你  如果你想打动我
Just so you know, if you want to impress me,

22
00:18:05,127 --> 00:18:07,434
我喜欢斗殴事迹
I like fight stories.

23
00:18:11,960 --> 00:18:13,440
你打过架吗
You ever been in a fight?

24
00:18:14,093 --> 00:18:15,094
没有
No.

25
00:18:15,964 --> 00:18:16,965
我打过
I have.

26
00:18:20,186 --> 00:18:23,885
有次我踢掉了一个人的耳朵
I once accidentally kicked a guy's ear off.

27
00:18:24,233 --> 00:18:28,194
我不是有意的  反正那破耳朵就被踢飞了
I didn't mean to, but the fucker flew off.

28
00:18:29,064 --> 00:18:32,459
我能直接看到他的颅骨里面
I could see right into his skull.

29
00:18:37,594 --> 00:18:38,595
晚安
Night.

30
00:19:04,404 --> 00:19:05,405
杰思罗
Jethro.

31
00:19:06,841 --> 00:19:09,235
你想让我怎么做
what you want me to do?

32
00:19:11,106 --> 00:19:12,412
去你的
Fuck you.

33
00:19:13,195 --> 00:19:14,675
让我在这聊天
Let me talk here.

34
00:19:17,330 --> 00:19:18,983
不  得了吧  那不行
No, come on. That's not...

35
00:19:20,507 --> 00:19:23,118
你他妈知道我们可以拿他当筹码
You know we can use him as fucking leverage.

36
00:19:24,815 --> 00:19:26,469
我们有了把柄
We've got some collateral.

37
00:19:28,167 --> 00:19:30,212
我得到你的允许
I have your permission?

38
00:19:30,865 --> 00:19:32,083
好吧那么
Well then...

39
00:19:33,259 --> 00:19:35,522
糟了  等一下
Shit. Wait a minute.

40
00:20:27,487 --> 00:20:29,619
爸  我能问你个事吗
Dad, can I ask you something?

41
00:20:31,534 --> 00:20:33,232
你为什么叫我来这
Why did you ask me to come here?

42
00:20:35,321 --> 00:20:38,019
你给我写信要我来  但是
You sent me a letter asking me to come. But...

43
00:20:39,063 --> 00:20:42,676
我现在来了  可你好像宁愿我没来
Now I'm here and you seem like you'd rather I wasn't.

44
00:20:46,027 --> 00:20:47,811
就好像你后悔给我寄信了
It's like you regret sending that letter.

45
00:20:50,814 --> 00:20:51,946
也许是我多心了
Maybe I'm wrong.

46
00:20:55,645 --> 00:20:56,820
我多心了吗
Am I wrong?

47
00:21:05,525 --> 00:21:07,222
我得去拉屎了
I've got to take a crap.

48
00:21:08,092 --> 00:21:10,965
之后  我们去游泳
Then, let's go for a swim.

49
00:21:23,630 --> 00:21:25,762
妈
Mom.

50
00:21:28,112 --> 00:21:30,027
好的
Okay.

51
00:21:31,377 --> 00:21:32,421
你好吗
How are you?

52
00:21:35,163 --> 00:21:36,904
那太好了
that's great.

53
00:21:39,863 --> 00:21:41,474
我不知道
I don't know.

54
00:21:42,170 --> 00:21:43,693
比我想象的要难
It's harder than I thought.

55
00:21:44,912 --> 00:21:47,306
他不是我想象的样子
He's not how I imagined him.

56
00:21:51,135 --> 00:21:52,311
完全不一样
Not at all.

57
00:21:55,052 --> 00:21:57,316
我觉得他没什么社交
I don't think he sees many people.

58
00:22:03,365 --> 00:22:06,455
也许他不习惯和人相处
Maybe he's not used to having people around.

59
00:22:11,634 --> 00:22:13,114
我相信情况会好起来
I'm sure it will get easier.

60
00:22:16,160 --> 00:22:18,119
唉  谁知道呢
I mean, who knows.

61
00:22:20,164 --> 00:22:21,949
也许我们最后能做朋友
Maybe we'll end up being best friends.

62
00:22:56,331 --> 00:22:58,202
不  他死定了
No, he's fuckin' dead.

63
00:22:59,334 --> 00:23:00,466
他死定了
He's dead.

64
00:23:01,989 --> 00:23:04,034
他死定了
He's fuckin' dead.

65
00:23:08,561 --> 00:23:10,998
不  我不想再做该死的保姆了
No. I don't want to be a fucking babysitter.

67
00:23:35,196 --> 00:23:36,197
爸
Dad.

68
00:23:38,591 --> 00:23:39,592
爸
Dad?

70
00:23:42,899 --> 00:23:45,206
你为什么给我寄信
I need to know why you sent that letter.

71
00:23:47,295 --> 00:23:48,470
别再问了
Give it a rest.

72
00:23:48,992 --> 00:23:51,473
爸  我大老远跑来
Dad, I came all this way.

73
00:23:52,039 --> 00:23:53,040
不
No.

74
00:23:53,562 --> 00:23:56,870
我不想讨论这个
I don't want to discuss it.

75
00:23:59,742 --> 00:24:01,483
你以为我乐意吗
This is hard for me too.

76
00:24:01,527 --> 00:24:02,658
你他妈闭嘴吧
Fucking drop it.

77
00:24:07,315 --> 00:24:09,056
我他妈不想闭嘴
I don't want to fucking drop it.

78
00:24:12,407 --> 00:24:13,713
你说什么
What did you say to me?

79
00:24:14,061 --> 00:24:17,064
-我说  -你说什么
- I said... - You said?

80
00:24:17,847 --> 00:24:20,197
我说  我他妈不想闭嘴
I said, I don't want to fucking drop it.

81
00:24:21,503 --> 00:24:23,984
好好跟我说话  小子
You watch how you talk to me, boy.

82
00:24:24,027 --> 00:24:27,248
你要我过来  我来了
You asked me to come here. Here I am.

84
00:24:29,250 --> 00:24:30,556
-然后呢  -所以
- And? - And...

85
00:24:31,252 --> 00:24:32,819
你要告诉我原因吧
you have some explaining to do.

86
00:24:37,737 --> 00:24:38,737
什么原因
Like what?

87
00:24:39,173 --> 00:24:41,044
我五岁时  你弃我们而去
You walked out on us when I was five.

88
00:24:41,610 --> 00:24:43,699
三十年过去  你要我来看你
Thirty years later you ask me to come and see you.

89
00:24:43,743 --> 00:24:44,961
我来了
Here... here I am.

90
00:24:45,832 --> 00:24:48,008
我来是因为我以为
I came here because I assumed

91
00:24:48,051 --> 00:24:50,171
你哪天会向我交代清楚
that at some point you were going to explain yourself.

92
00:24:50,445 --> 00:24:54,667
我没必要向你交代
I don't have to explain myself to you.

93
00:24:55,450 --> 00:24:56,625
我不觉得
I disagree.

94
00:24:58,322 --> 00:24:59,322
是吗
Do you?

95
00:25:00,760 --> 00:25:01,935
是的
Yeah.

96
00:25:01,978 --> 00:25:04,024
你他妈的又能怎么样呢
What the fuck are you gonna do about it?

97
00:25:05,939 --> 00:25:08,724
你他妈的能怎么样呢
What the fuck are you gonna do about it?

99
00:25:12,075 --> 00:25:13,250
我知道怎么回事
I know what's happening.

100
00:25:13,294 --> 00:25:15,296
是吗  相信我
Yeah? Trust me.

101
00:25:15,644 --> 00:25:18,778
你他妈什么都不知道
You got no fucking idea what's happening here.

102
00:25:18,821 --> 00:25:20,083
我知道
I think I do.

103
00:25:20,127 --> 00:25:22,259
滚
Fuck off.

104
00:25:23,565 --> 00:25:25,306
你是喝醉了才写了那封信
You wrote that letter when you were drunk.

105
00:25:27,177 --> 00:25:28,918
你可能都不记得你寄出去过
You probably don't even remember sending it.

106
00:25:28,962 --> 00:25:30,311
滚
Fuck off.

107
00:25:31,312 --> 00:25:33,967
你是个酒鬼  这就是你
You're a drunk. That's all you are.

108
00:25:34,445 --> 00:25:36,056
一个无能的酒鬼
A useless drunk.

109
00:25:36,099 --> 00:25:39,973
-你控制不住酒瘾  -你不配当爹
- You can't handle your booze. - You can't handle being a dad.

111
00:25:41,627 --> 00:25:44,064
我竭尽所能来对你培养好感
I've been trying so fucking hard to like you...

112
00:25:44,760 --> 00:25:46,196
但毫无可能
but it's impossible.

113
00:25:46,675 --> 00:25:48,155
你不可理喻
You're impossible.

114
00:25:48,459 --> 00:25:49,591
滚
Fuck off.

115
00:25:50,418 --> 00:25:51,680
你滚
You fuck off.

116
00:25:52,681 --> 00:25:55,945
不  你滚
No! You fuck off!

117
00:25:57,643 --> 00:25:59,427
你这个操耗子的
You're a rat fucker.

118
00:25:59,819 --> 00:26:02,822
你拿耗子塞进逼里
You stuff rats up your vagina.

119
00:26:03,083 --> 00:26:07,478
穿得像个女人  穿得像个贱逼
You dress like a woman. You dress like a cunt.

120
00:26:07,783 --> 00:26:09,611
-请别那么说我  -为什么不
- Please, don't call me that. - Then why?

121
00:26:09,655 --> 00:26:11,134
你就是贱逼啊
You're very cunty.

122
00:26:11,178 --> 00:26:13,049
别那么说
Don't say that.

123
00:26:13,659 --> 00:26:18,228
我实话实说  贱逼就是贱逼
I call a spade a spade, and a cunt a cunt.

124
00:26:18,272 --> 00:26:22,885
而你  先生  是个实打实的贱逼
And you, sir, are a certified cunt.

125
00:26:23,843 --> 00:26:27,716
你还真以为我会有兴趣
Did you really think that I would be impressed

126
00:26:27,760 --> 00:26:31,285
听你说什么艾尔顿·约翰的故事吗
with your fucking Elton John story?

127
00:26:31,981 --> 00:26:36,029
只有贱逼会这么想  贱逼
Only a cunt would think that. Cunt!

128
00:26:36,769 --> 00:26:38,335
-贱逼  -请你别推我
- Cunt! - Please, don't push me.

129
00:26:38,379 --> 00:26:39,815
是吗  怎么着
Yeah, what?

130
00:26:41,861 --> 00:26:42,949
怎么着
What?

131
00:26:42,992 --> 00:26:44,472
-我要走了  -不
- I'll leave. - No.

132
00:26:44,515 --> 00:26:46,561
不行  你哪儿也不能去
No, you're not going anywhere.

133
00:26:46,605 --> 00:26:47,823
我觉得我也许该走了
I think I might just go.

135
00:26:49,129 --> 00:26:52,306
你会在森林里迷路死掉
You'd get lost in the woods and die.

136
00:26:53,089 --> 00:26:55,439
然后人们会发现一具老鼠骨架
And they'd find a rat skeleton

137
00:26:55,744 --> 00:26:59,661
塞在你盆骨里面阴道的位置
inside your pelvic bone where your vagina was.

138
00:27:01,968 --> 00:27:03,622
你希望那样  是吗  爸
You'd love that, wouldn't you, Dad?

139
00:27:03,883 --> 00:27:04,971
靠
Fuck.

140
00:27:05,014 --> 00:27:06,537
你希望我死掉
You'd love it if I was dead.

141
00:27:06,581 --> 00:27:08,714
老天  他妈的该死啊
God. Fucking damn it!

142
00:27:27,820 --> 00:27:29,909
爸  你他妈在干嘛
Dad! What the fuck are you doing?

143
00:27:29,952 --> 00:27:34,087
我觉得正确的说法是谋杀亲子
I believe the correct term is filicide.

144
00:27:35,175 --> 00:27:37,481
靠  靠  得了吧
Fuck. Fuck. Come on.

145
00:27:37,525 --> 00:27:39,745
过来  你这个操耗子的
Come here, you little rat fucker!

146
00:27:40,180 --> 00:27:43,574
-过来  来爸爸这儿  -求你了  别这样
- Come here. Come to Daddy! - Please, please don't do this.

147
00:27:43,618 --> 00:27:45,098
我道歉  我他妈道歉
I'm sorry. I'm so fucking sorry.

148
00:27:45,141 --> 00:27:47,274
感恩的心去哪了
Where's the fucking gratitude here?

149
00:27:47,622 --> 00:27:49,580
我以为你想死的
I thought you wanted to die.

1
00:27:49,624 --> 00:27:51,408
我没有  我不想  不  不要
I... I didn't. I don't. No, no.

2
00:27:51,452 --> 00:27:53,193
拜托爸爸  别这样
Please, Dad, don't do this.

3
00:27:53,236 --> 00:27:55,935
去死
Die!

4
00:27:58,720 --> 00:28:00,374
不
No.

5
00:28:00,417 --> 00:28:01,417
爸爸
Dad?

6
00:28:09,992 --> 00:28:11,124
爸爸
Dad?

7
00:28:25,791 --> 00:28:27,488
妈妈  是我
Mom, it's me.

8
00:28:30,099 --> 00:28:32,493
不是  你听我说
N... No. L... Listen to me.

9
00:28:33,712 --> 00:28:35,278
是爸爸  他  他
It's Dad. He... He's...

10
00:28:35,844 --> 00:28:37,498
我  我觉得他好像死了
I... I think he just died.

11
00:28:37,846 --> 00:28:39,761
他刚刚摔倒了
H... He just fell down.

12
00:28:39,805 --> 00:28:42,329
他刚刚摔倒  停止呼吸了
He just fell down and stopped breathing.

13
00:28:42,938 --> 00:28:47,334
我们  我们吵了一架  他就死了
We... we had an argument, and... and he just died.

14
00:28:49,336 --> 00:28:50,337
星期五吗
Friday?

15
00:28:50,685 --> 00:28:52,992
好  周五见
Okay. I'll see you Friday.

16
00:28:54,689 --> 00:28:57,431
好的  好  我会照做
Okay. Yep. Okay. I... I'll do that.

17
00:29:26,199 --> 00:29:27,722
麻烦转接验尸官办公室
Coroner's office, please.

18
00:29:33,075 --> 00:29:34,337
我爸爸刚刚死了
My dad's just died.

19
00:30:28,609 --> 00:30:32,091
死前有任何打斗吗
And there wasn't any, like, um, struggle and stuff?

20
00:30:33,919 --> 00:30:38,314
没有  我说了  他看上去很正常
No. No. Like I said, he... He seemed fine. And...

21
00:30:38,619 --> 00:30:41,578
然后他说胸痛  就倒下了
And he said his chest hurt. He fell down...

22
00:30:41,622 --> 00:30:43,319
你保证你说的都是事实吗
Do you promise you're telling me the truth?

23
00:30:47,106 --> 00:30:49,760
不行  你不能只点头
No. You can't just nod.

24
00:30:53,460 --> 00:30:55,288
你要大声地说出来
You've got to say it out loud.

25
00:30:56,332 --> 00:30:58,247
我保证我说的都是事实
I promise I'm telling the truth.

26
00:31:06,734 --> 00:31:07,996
你知道吗
You know something?

27
00:31:09,345 --> 00:31:10,694
我相信你
I believe you.

28
00:31:14,046 --> 00:31:15,612
你没有葡萄干眼
You don't have raisin eyes.

29
00:31:16,700 --> 00:31:18,441
-啊  -没错  我这话
-What? - Yeah, I'm kind of

30
00:31:18,485 --> 00:31:20,966
是有点出戏  但是
breaking the fourth wall here, but,

31
00:31:21,531 --> 00:31:23,055
我有一套理论
I got this theory.

32
00:31:23,925 --> 00:31:26,319
坏人有一双看起来像葡萄干的眼睛
Bad guys have eyes that look like raisins.

33
00:31:26,972 --> 00:31:28,756
又小又黑  你懂吗
You know, small and dark, you know?

34
00:31:29,539 --> 00:31:31,193
但你没有葡萄干眼
But you don't have raisin eyes.

35
00:31:33,674 --> 00:31:35,284
没  我没有
No. I... I don't.

37
00:31:46,643 --> 00:31:47,906
我告诉你
Tell you something, though.

38
00:31:48,210 --> 00:31:52,214
你爸爸  他有一双葡萄干眼
Your daddy... he did have raisin eyes.

39
00:31:59,787 --> 00:32:03,356
来爸爸这儿
Come to Daddy.

40
00:32:03,399 --> 00:32:06,663
这只是我关于
That's just my hallucinations on the subject

41
00:32:06,707 --> 00:32:08,535
坏人和他们眼睛的错觉
of bad guys and their eyes.

42
00:32:12,365 --> 00:32:14,367
验尸官会来接手
Coroner will take it from here.

43
00:32:16,108 --> 00:32:17,239
我
Yeah, I'm...

44
00:32:17,718 --> 00:32:20,068
我对于你爸爸的事感到很遗憾
I'm sorry about your dad and stuff, you know.

45
00:32:20,547 --> 00:32:23,028
放轻松吧  多喝水
Take it easy, I guess. Drink lots of water.

46
00:32:26,857 --> 00:32:28,947
如果能让你高兴的话  我可以
I can burp on command if that might

47
00:32:28,990 --> 00:32:29,991
听你指挥打嗝
cheer you up.

48
00:32:31,775 --> 00:32:34,039
不用了
No, that's okay.

49
00:32:41,307 --> 00:32:42,308
好吧
Okay.

50
00:32:49,793 --> 00:32:51,186
我觉得我不喜欢他
I don't think I liked him.

51
00:32:51,230 --> 00:32:52,448
是吗
Really?

52
00:32:52,927 --> 00:32:54,450
他骂我操老鼠
He called me a rat fucker.

53
00:32:55,277 --> 00:32:56,670
还有一些其它的
Amongst other things.

54
00:32:59,412 --> 00:33:00,717
幸好他死了
Good thing he's dead then.

55
00:33:02,763 --> 00:33:04,286
这么说真的不好吗
Is that a really bad thing to say?

56
00:33:05,331 --> 00:33:08,377
我不知道  可能吧
I don't know. Yeah?

57
00:33:11,424 --> 00:33:12,425
抱歉
Sorry.

57
00:33:18,425 --> 00:33:23,869
{\an8}验尸报告
死者：布莱恩·格林伍德  性别：男  职业：无
报案人：诺瓦尔·格林伍德  性别：男  职业：艺术家

58
00:33:23,871 --> 00:33:26,395
我要带走他  对他进行防腐处理
So, I'm gonna take him away, embalm him,

59
00:33:26,439 --> 00:33:29,485
把他体内的血抽干  给他注射防腐剂
drain the blood from his body, inject him with a preservative,

60
00:33:29,529 --> 00:33:31,922
这样他不会腐烂  然后再把他带回来
so he doesn't go off, and then bring him back here.

61
00:33:32,532 --> 00:33:33,533
什么
What?

62
00:33:34,316 --> 00:33:36,623
镇里现在没办法贮存
There is a storage issue in town at the moment

63
00:33:36,666 --> 00:33:37,711
洪水淹了太平间
from the flooding.

64
00:33:37,754 --> 00:33:39,191
你听说了吗
Did you hear about that?

65
00:33:39,234 --> 00:33:40,235
没有
No.

66
00:33:41,149 --> 00:33:43,934
在家属做出安排之前  他得待在这儿
He'll need to be here while your family makes arrangements.

67
00:33:45,023 --> 00:33:47,547
他会被装在黑袋子里  你不用看着他的
He'll be in a black bag. You won't have to look at him.

68
00:33:56,947 --> 00:33:58,645
有没有其他人告诉你
Has anyone ever told you...

69
00:34:00,299 --> 00:34:01,474
告诉我什么
Told me what?

70
00:34:03,780 --> 00:34:05,173
你有一双善良的眼睛
You have kind eyes.

71
00:34:07,915 --> 00:34:10,135
没有  没有人跟我说过
No. No one has ever said that to me.

72
00:34:10,439 --> 00:34:11,440
从来没有吗
Never?

73
00:34:12,137 --> 00:34:13,268
我不记得有
Not that I remember.

74
00:34:14,008 --> 00:34:15,314
你有
Well, you do.

75
00:34:15,966 --> 00:34:18,360
你有一双大眼睛  一双善良的眼睛
They're big and they're kind.

76
00:34:20,580 --> 00:34:23,887
那  那个警察告诉我  我没有葡萄干眼
The... the cop who came told me I... I didn't have raisin eyes.

77
00:34:24,410 --> 00:34:26,020
什么是葡萄干眼
What are raisin eyes?

78
00:34:27,674 --> 00:34:29,545
好傻啊  什么葡萄干眼
Fucking idiot. Raisin eyes?

79
00:34:29,589 --> 00:34:31,025
是啊
I know.

80
00:34:34,028 --> 00:34:37,205
有任何问题直接打电话给我
If you have any questions just call me.

81
00:34:40,861 --> 00:34:41,862
谢谢
Thanks.

81
00:34:52,881 --> 00:34:56,010
{\an8}格拉迪斯·克仑代克博士
首席副验尸官 

82
00:34:59,880 --> 00:35:01,011
是谁
Hello?

83
00:36:19,438 --> 00:36:20,830
你还好吗
How are you holding up?

84
00:36:22,267 --> 00:36:23,442
我还好
I'm fine.

85
00:36:26,140 --> 00:36:27,576
我从未真正的了解他
I never really knew him.

86
00:36:28,925 --> 00:36:30,971
所以也不觉得很伤心
So, it's hard to feel sad.

87
00:36:34,148 --> 00:36:37,238
至少不会伤心到真的哭出来
Sad enough to actually cry real emotional tears.

88
00:36:38,370 --> 00:36:39,371
但
But...

89
00:36:41,503 --> 00:36:43,375
他是我爸爸  所以
he is my dad, so...

90
00:36:45,638 --> 00:36:46,943
我有感觉
I feel something.

91
00:36:49,294 --> 00:36:50,643
我只是说不上是什么感觉
I just don't know what.

92
00:36:53,646 --> 00:36:55,300
总归要好受些
It does get easier.

93
00:36:57,432 --> 00:36:58,477
是啊
Yeah.

94
00:37:02,132 --> 00:37:04,657
我  我得回办公室咯
Look. I...I better get back to the office.

95
00:37:06,833 --> 00:37:07,834
好
Yeah.

96
00:37:10,315 --> 00:37:12,317
这可能听起来有些诡异  但
This might sound really weird, but...

97
00:37:12,795 --> 00:37:14,057
你应该跟他说说话
you should talk to him.

98
00:37:14,841 --> 00:37:15,841
什么
What?

98
00:37:16,341 --> 00:37:17,841
{\an8}霍普港郡
验尸官

99
00:37:17,931 --> 00:37:19,411
会有帮助的
It helps, you know?

100
00:37:20,107 --> 00:37:21,587
我丈夫过世的时候
When my husband died,

101
00:37:21,978 --> 00:37:25,373
我记得我对他吼了一个小时
I remember just yapping onto him for an hour.

102
00:37:25,417 --> 00:37:27,680
把所有他还在世时我想说的话
All the things I wanted to say when he was...

103
00:37:28,855 --> 00:37:29,856
都说了
was here.

104
00:37:31,336 --> 00:37:33,903
我相信你也有想对你爸爸说的话
I'm sure there's things you want to say to your dad, too.

105
00:37:36,341 --> 00:37:37,994
这不是我的职责范围内
Not that it's any of my business.

106
00:37:38,038 --> 00:37:39,953
如果你不想听  可以让我闭嘴
You can tell me to shut up, if you want.

107
00:37:39,996 --> 00:37:42,042
不  没事  真的
No. It's okay, really.

108
00:37:44,131 --> 00:37:45,393
我说话直白
I have no filter.

109
00:37:48,135 --> 00:37:49,179
我喜欢的
I like it.

110
00:37:52,879 --> 00:37:54,272
你一个人待着行吗
Are you gonna be okay here?

111
00:37:56,622 --> 00:37:57,797
希望行吧
I hope so.

112
00:37:59,538 --> 00:38:01,627
当然行的
Yeah, definitely.

113
00:38:04,456 --> 00:38:06,893
等你妈妈来了  我们再做进一步安排
When your mom gets here, we'll make further arrangements.

114
00:38:10,766 --> 00:38:12,246
照顾好自己  诺瓦尔
Take care, Norval.

114
00:38:15,966 --> 00:38:20,136
{\an8}验尸官

115
00:40:01,977 --> 00:40:07,852
{\an8}《圣境预言书》

115
00:40:23,377 --> 00:40:24,552
谁在那儿
Who's there?

116
00:40:26,424 --> 00:40:27,686
有人在那儿吗
Is someone there?

117
00:41:14,428 --> 00:41:15,473
喂
Hello?

118
00:41:18,824 --> 00:41:19,999
哪位
Who is this?

119
00:41:23,742 --> 00:41:25,483
妈妈  是你吗
Mom? Is that you?

120
00:42:05,871 --> 00:42:06,915
安静
Shut up.

121
00:42:10,528 --> 00:42:11,529
安静
Shut up!

122
00:42:16,925 --> 00:42:17,925
安静
Shut up!

124
00:44:07,209 --> 00:44:09,429
我听不见
I'm not listening!

125
00:44:21,876 --> 00:44:23,095
喂
Hello?

126
00:44:23,399 --> 00:44:24,618
格拉迪斯
Gladys?

127
00:44:26,620 --> 00:44:28,056
是我  哪位
Yes? Who is this?

128
00:44:28,100 --> 00:44:29,449
你猜
Guess.

129
00:44:30,406 --> 00:44:31,712
格林伍德先生吗
Mister Greenwood?

130
00:44:31,756 --> 00:44:32,931
答对了
Bingo.

131
00:44:33,366 --> 00:44:35,368
你父亲有什么问题吗
Is there a problem with your father?

132
00:44:35,411 --> 00:44:37,011
我父亲有很多问题
There's a lot of problems with my father,

133
00:44:37,370 --> 00:44:39,154
但这不是我打电话的原因
but that's not why I'm calling.

134
00:44:40,025 --> 00:44:41,635
我能为你做什么
What can I do for you?

135
00:44:42,288 --> 00:44:45,595
好问题  我需要你过来
Good question. I need you to come over.

136
00:44:45,639 --> 00:44:47,423
格林伍德先生  你是不是
Mr. Greenwood, are you...

137
00:44:47,467 --> 00:44:49,338
别思考  直接过来
Don't think. Just come over.

138
00:44:50,165 --> 00:44:51,950
你正在经历一段艰难的时期
You're going through a difficult time.

139
00:44:51,993 --> 00:44:53,691
-我们俩有感觉  -不  我们没有
- We had something. - No, we didn't.

140
00:44:53,734 --> 00:44:55,649
-我知道你也有感觉  -不  我没有
- I know you felt it too. - No, I didn't.

141
00:44:55,693 --> 00:44:57,303
我们有责任去探究
We owe it to ourselves to explore this.

142
00:44:57,346 --> 00:45:00,088
你现在能做的最聪明的事就是跳上车
The smartest thing you could do right now is jump in your car

143
00:45:00,132 --> 00:45:01,133
然后
and...

144
00:45:04,092 --> 00:45:05,093
拜托
Please.

145
00:45:06,225 --> 00:45:08,096
-拜托  请你过来  -不行
- Please, please just come over. - No.

146
00:45:08,140 --> 00:45:10,925
我  我不能一个人  我们  我们可以一起睡
I... I can't be here alone. We... We could just sleep together.

147
00:45:10,969 --> 00:45:12,840
-不行  -就靠在一起
- No. - Just next to each other.

148
00:45:12,884 --> 00:45:14,712
-不行  -如果你想  我们可以穿着衣服
- No. - Fully clothed if you wanted.

149
00:45:14,973 --> 00:45:17,149
我  我只是  我只是需要你过来
I... I just... I just need you here.

1
00:45:20,190 --> 00:45:21,190
你还在吗
Hello?

2
00:45:25,240 --> 00:45:27,330
对不起  我要挂电话了
I'm sorry, but I have to go.

3
00:45:27,370 --> 00:45:28,680
不  不  不
No, no, no.

4
00:45:28,720 --> 00:45:30,160
-别挂电话  -请不要在非工作时间
- Don't go. - Please don't call me

5
00:45:30,200 --> 00:45:31,250
打电话给我
outside of office hours.

6
00:45:31,290 --> 00:45:32,550
再见  格林伍德先生
Goodbye, Mr. Greenwood.

7
00:45:32,860 --> 00:45:33,940
操
Fuck!

8
00:45:37,510 --> 00:45:38,560
天呐
Oh, God.

9
00:45:49,180 --> 00:45:50,260
操
Oh, fuck.

10
00:45:51,870 --> 00:45:53,350
是谁在捣鬼
Who's doing this?

11
00:46:03,800 --> 00:46:06,110
是你在捣鬼吗  是你吗
Are you doing this? Are you?

12
00:46:06,850 --> 00:46:08,150
你觉得很好玩吗
You think it's funny?

13
00:46:09,370 --> 00:46:10,590
操你妈
Well, fuck you.

14
00:46:11,070 --> 00:46:13,810
你就是个懦夫  一个大懦夫
You're a coward, that's all you are.

15
00:46:14,460 --> 00:46:17,200
一个又干又糙的  死翘翘的懦夫
A dried-up, dead, leathery coward.

16
00:46:17,600 --> 00:46:19,030
你死了我更高兴
I'm glad you're dead.

17
00:46:20,560 --> 00:46:23,950
小时候你离开了我  然后你又想杀了我
You disappear when I was a kid,and then you try to kill me?

18
00:46:26,130 --> 00:46:29,780
现在你还没进坟墓  你就来闹鬼
And now you're fucking with me from beyond the grave?

19
00:46:30,480 --> 00:46:33,740
是不是  这倒是意料之中
Are you? I wouldn't be surprised.

20
00:46:38,920 --> 00:46:40,400
你觉得我是贱逼
You think I'm a cunt?

21
00:46:40,920 --> 00:46:44,060
真可笑啊
That's hilarious.

22
00:46:45,620 --> 00:46:47,100
你才是贱逼
You're the cunt here.

23
00:46:48,540 --> 00:46:50,890
操你妈的  听到没有
So, fuck you. You hear me?

24
00:46:51,890 --> 00:46:52,890
操你妈
Fuck you!

25
00:46:53,150 --> 00:46:54,630
操你妈
Fuck you!

26
00:46:55,020 --> 00:46:56,070
贱逼
Cunt!

27
00:47:28,840 --> 00:47:30,490
我得跟你说点事
I have to tell you something.

28
00:47:36,110 --> 00:47:38,940
这事说起来可能会让你觉得我是个坏蛋
I'm afraid it's gonna make me sound like a bad person.

29
00:47:48,030 --> 00:47:52,280
{\an8}瑞恩
安息

30
00:49:50,030 --> 00:49:51,030
妈妈
Mom.

31
00:50:09,610 --> 00:50:11,000
不不不不
No, no, no, no.

32
00:50:14,960 --> 00:50:16,880
不不不  不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no.

33
00:50:28,670 --> 00:50:30,670
不不不  不不不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.

34
00:50:59,790 --> 00:51:01,050
操
Oh, fuck.

35
00:51:20,510 --> 00:51:22,470
操  不不不
Oh, fuck. No, no, no.

36
00:52:44,420 --> 00:52:45,590
诺瓦尔
Norval?

37
00:52:54,950 --> 00:52:56,080
诺瓦尔
Norval.

38
00:53:00,690 --> 00:53:01,740
你是谁
Who are you?

39
00:53:01,780 --> 00:53:03,780
你来了  你真的来了
You came, you came.

40
00:53:05,960 --> 00:53:10,180
诺瓦尔  我的孩子  你真的来了
Norval, my boy, you actually came.

41
00:53:13,050 --> 00:53:15,360
快过来  快来  救我出去
Come over here. Come, come here, help me out.

42
00:53:15,400 --> 00:53:17,450
诺瓦尔
Norval.

43
00:53:17,490 --> 00:53:21,020
快点  救我出去
Come on. Get me out of here.

44
00:53:22,800 --> 00:53:24,410
那个傻逼去哪了
Where's that fucker gone?

45
00:53:25,980 --> 00:53:27,810
-他们来了  -谁  谁  谁来了
- They're here. - Who... who... who's here?

46
00:53:27,850 --> 00:53:29,070
快他妈的关门啊
Close the fucking door.

47
00:53:43,350 --> 00:53:44,780
看着我  我是你的爸爸
Look at me. I'm your dad.

48
00:53:44,830 --> 00:53:47,000
接下来的90秒将会改变你的一生
The next 90 seconds are gonna change your life forever.

49
00:53:47,040 --> 00:53:49,480
那群人会打我  你必须杀掉他们
They're coming to hurt me, and you're going to kill them.

50
00:53:50,530 --> 00:53:52,180
-我做不到啊  -你待会儿躲起来
- I can't. - You're going to hide.

51
00:53:52,220 --> 00:53:53,290
等他们下来之后
And when they're down here,

52
00:53:53,310 --> 00:53:54,700
你就把他们打死
you're going to beat them to death.

53
00:53:55,490 --> 00:53:56,750
地上有个哑铃
There's a dumbbell on the floor.

54
00:53:56,790 --> 00:53:58,530
快拿起来  当做武器
You take it, and use it as a weapon,

55
00:53:58,580 --> 00:54:00,020
使劲砸他们的脑袋
and you bash their fuckin' brains in.

56
00:54:00,060 --> 00:54:01,360
什么  不  不  请不要这样
What? No. No, no, no. Please.

57
00:54:01,410 --> 00:54:02,800
如果你不杀死他们  他们就会杀死咱俩
If you don't, they'll kill us both.

58
00:54:03,280 --> 00:54:05,060
快藏起来
Hide!

59
00:54:35,880 --> 00:54:38,970
还能坚持住吗  布莱恩
How's it hanging, Brian? Huh?

60
00:54:39,970 --> 00:54:43,410
气色不错  感觉挺好是吧
Looking good. Feeling good, huh?

61
00:54:48,110 --> 00:54:49,500
看看这个
Viddy this.

62
00:54:52,500 --> 00:54:53,680
这个  布莱恩
This, Brian...

63
00:54:59,070 --> 00:55:02,380
这是一支笔
this is a pen.

64
00:55:02,990 --> 00:55:08,130
不是普通的笔  这是一支涂满排谢物的笔
Not just any pen,it's a pen smeared in extrement.

65
00:55:11,130 --> 00:55:13,310
我的排谢物
My extrement.

66
00:55:13,350 --> 00:55:15,790
排谢物是屎的学名
Extrement is the scientific word for poo.

67
00:55:16,050 --> 00:55:19,220
是排泄物  不是排谢物
It's excrement, not extrement.

68
00:55:19,270 --> 00:55:20,880
我要拿这支笔捅你  布莱恩
I'm gonna stab you with this pen, Brian.

69
00:55:21,970 --> 00:55:23,530
很显然  会弄疼你
And obviously it's going to hurt.

70
00:55:24,750 --> 00:55:26,410
然后科学就开始起作用
But then the science kicks in.

71
00:55:27,280 --> 00:55:30,630
这笔上的排谢物
So, the extrement that's on the pen

72
00:55:30,670 --> 00:55:33,460
会渗到你的伤口里  然后你的伤口会感染
is gonna go into your wound and it's gonna give you

73
00:55:33,500 --> 00:55:35,940
让你痛不欲生
an infection that's gonna kill you

74
00:55:36,420 --> 00:55:38,850
如果你得不到及时的救助
if you don't get help quickly.

75
00:55:41,030 --> 00:55:43,600
慢慢被折磨的感觉如何  布莱恩
How's that for a ticking clock, Brian?

76
00:55:45,640 --> 00:55:47,380
你觉得兴奋吗  布莱恩
How's that for excitement, Brian?

77
00:55:47,430 --> 00:55:50,430
你兴奋吗  反正我很兴奋  布莱恩
Are you excited? Because I'm excited, Brian.

78
00:55:53,170 --> 00:55:54,260
现在
Now...

79
00:55:56,350 --> 00:55:59,440
快告诉我我想知道的一切
why don't you tell me what I want to know...

80
00:56:00,090 --> 00:56:03,750
你告诉我  我就带你去医院
And when this is all over, I'll get you to a hospital.

81
00:56:03,790 --> 00:56:05,400
我已经告诉戈登所有的事情了
I already told Gordon everything.

82
00:56:05,440 --> 00:56:07,360
事情已经结束了  彻底结束了
It's gone. All of it.

83
00:56:15,720 --> 00:56:18,590
是不是该告诉你  我是怎么知道你在说谎
Shall I tell you how I know you're lying?

84
00:56:18,630 --> 00:56:19,630
你怎么知道的
How?

85
00:56:20,460 --> 00:56:24,250
因为你在说话时  朝左手边看了一眼
Because when you said that, you looked up to your left.

86
00:56:24,590 --> 00:56:26,770
-哦  -这是人们撒谎时
- Oh. - And that's the number one

87
00:56:26,810 --> 00:56:28,900
最首要的迹象
indication when somebody's lying to you.

88
00:56:32,080 --> 00:56:34,080
我之所以懂这些
Yeah, I know these things

89
00:56:34,120 --> 00:56:36,430
是因为我读过有关肢体语言的文章
because I've read articles on body language.

90
00:56:37,300 --> 00:56:38,300
懂吗
All right?

91
00:56:39,300 --> 00:56:40,910
我也不忍心下手
This is difficult for me too.

92
00:56:43,130 --> 00:56:45,790
还不如直接切入主题
So what do you say we just get this over and done with

93
00:56:45,830 --> 00:56:47,620
速战速决  好吗
as quickly as possible, shall we?

94
00:56:47,660 --> 00:56:48,660
不  不  不
No, no, no.

95
00:56:48,970 --> 00:56:50,100
-好吗  -不要
- Shall we? - No.

96
00:56:50,360 --> 00:56:51,530
我要动手了  你准备好了吗
Here it comes. Are you ready?

97
00:56:51,580 --> 00:56:53,140
-不  别这样  -准备好
- No, no. Come on. -Oh, yeah, yeah.

98
00:56:53,190 --> 00:56:55,670
不  不  不  不
No, no, no, no.

99
00:56:56,020 --> 00:56:57,890
老天  该死
God damn it!

100
00:56:58,540 --> 00:56:59,980
很疼吧  第一下很疼吧
It stings. The first one stings,

101
00:57:00,020 --> 00:57:01,330
疼吗
doesn't it?

102
00:57:01,370 --> 00:57:02,720
你不介意啊  那再捅一次
Mind you, so does the second one.

103
00:57:02,760 --> 00:57:03,940
操  快  快杀了他
Fuck! Now! Fuckin' kill him!

104
00:57:04,240 --> 00:57:06,160
-快他妈杀了他  -什么
- Fucking kill him! - What?

105
00:57:09,460 --> 00:57:11,810
-还有其他人吗  布莱恩  -快  动手啊
- Are we not alone, Brian? - Come on! Do it!

106
00:57:22,560 --> 00:57:24,870
出来  出来  不管你在哪
Come out, come out. Wherever you are.

107
00:57:26,660 --> 00:57:28,000
你他妈怎么还活着
How the fuck are you still alive?

108
00:57:29,750 --> 00:57:31,660
快他妈杀了他
Fucking kill him!

109
00:57:40,890 --> 00:57:42,190
我日你麻痹
Fuck this shit.

110
00:57:49,240 --> 00:57:50,810
你刚刚应该杀了他
You were supposed to kill him.

111
00:58:03,610 --> 00:58:06,740
戈登  不
Gordon! Oh, no!

112
00:58:07,170 --> 00:58:09,700
不  不  不  戈登
No, no, no! Gordon!

113
00:58:10,610 --> 00:58:12,350
楼上的那个男人怎么了
What happened to the man who was up there?

114
00:58:14,140 --> 00:58:17,400
他本想捅死我  但他突发心脏病
He tried to stab me.But then he had a heart attack.

115
00:58:17,920 --> 00:58:18,930
他死了
He died.

116
00:58:21,930 --> 00:58:22,930
太棒了
Good.

117
00:58:24,630 --> 00:58:25,710
我会回来的
I'll be back.

118
00:58:25,980 --> 00:58:28,150
我会带着一位朋友回来
And I'll be back with a little friend

119
00:58:28,200 --> 00:58:30,680
让你们认识认识
that I want you both to meet!

120
00:58:33,030 --> 00:58:35,330
我猜他的朋友是丹迪
My guess is his little friend is Dandy.

121
00:58:36,330 --> 00:58:37,380
丹迪是谁
Who's Dandy?

122
00:58:38,030 --> 00:58:39,860
-一个驼背  -什么
- The hunchback. - The what?

123
00:58:39,900 --> 00:58:42,020
你必须帮我解锁  你撬过锁吗
You have to release me. You ever picked a lock before?

124
00:58:42,380 --> 00:58:43,690
撬过一次  在学校
Once, in school.

125
00:58:43,730 --> 00:58:44,730
怎么回事
What happened?

126
00:58:45,470 --> 00:58:46,690
我没撬开
I didn't get it unlocked.

127
00:58:47,480 --> 00:58:50,000
但我在书包里找到了钥匙  所以没啥事
But I... I found the key in my bag, so it was okay.

128
00:58:52,440 --> 00:58:56,310
踩碎那支臭笔
Oh. Uh, smash the shitty pen.

129
00:59:00,050 --> 00:59:01,050
继续
Go on.

130
00:59:04,880 --> 00:59:07,190
现在  把那块细长的部分拿起来
Yeah. Now, take that long thin bit.

131
00:59:11,760 --> 00:59:13,810
天呐
God.

132
00:59:16,370 --> 00:59:19,730
现在  把它捅进锁眼里
Now... Now, jam it into the lock.

133
00:59:20,510 --> 00:59:22,160
用它在锁眼里转小圈
Work it in small circles.

134
00:59:23,470 --> 00:59:24,770
刚才那个男人是谁
Who was that man?

135
00:59:24,820 --> 00:59:26,820
他叫杰思罗  是我最好的朋友
His name is Jethro. He's my best friend.

136
00:59:28,820 --> 00:59:30,780
那他为什么用有屎的笔捅你
Then why is he stabbing you with poo pens

137
00:59:30,820 --> 00:59:32,560
还把你锁在地下室里
and chaining you up in your basement?

138
00:59:33,220 --> 00:59:34,390
他有他的理由
He has his reasons.

139
00:59:35,830 --> 00:59:40,270
离开你妈之后  我在曼谷生活
After I left your mom, I ended up living in Bangkok.

140
00:59:41,010 --> 00:59:45,660
我  杰思罗  楼上你遇见的戈登  和丹迪
Me, Jethro, Gordon,who you've met, and Dandy.

141
00:59:46,010 --> 00:59:48,320
我们过去一直都是小偷小摸
We were misbehaving in a small-time fashion.

142
00:59:48,360 --> 00:59:51,540
最终决定干最后一票
Until we decided to do one last score.

143
00:59:52,320 --> 00:59:54,890
完美落幕
Sail off into the sunset, all that.

144
00:59:56,720 --> 00:59:57,810
你们做了什么
What did you do?

145
00:59:58,070 --> 01:00:00,550
我们绑架了
Oh, we kidnapped

146
01:00:00,590 --> 01:00:02,680
泰国首富的女儿
the daughter of Thailand's richest man.

147
01:00:03,730 --> 01:00:08,430
我们本该一起分赃赎金
We were supposed to split the ransom between us,

148
01:00:08,470 --> 01:00:09,780
但我偷走了赎金
but I stole it.

149
01:00:11,470 --> 01:00:13,040
我敲诈了自己的好朋友们
I ripped my best friends off.

150
01:00:14,170 --> 01:00:15,910
可以理解  他们想要自己的分成
Understandably, they want their share.

1
01:00:16,569 --> 01:00:18,397
他们认为我把钱藏起来了
They think I have stashed it somewhere.

2
01:00:18,876 --> 01:00:22,009
事实上  钱都没了
Fact is, it's all gone.

3
01:00:23,576 --> 01:00:24,925
一分都不剩
Every last cent.

4
01:00:26,318 --> 01:00:27,319
在哪里
Where?

5
01:00:29,713 --> 01:00:33,238
你有停下来思考为什么
You ever stop for a moment and wonder why

6
01:00:34,021 --> 01:00:36,067
你妈妈没有工作
you grew up in a Beverly Hills mansion

7
01:00:36,110 --> 01:00:37,546
你却能在比弗利山庄的别墅里长大吗
with an unemployed mother?

8
01:00:43,074 --> 01:00:45,554
我这些年生活的钱都来自
My entire life has been funded by...

9
01:00:45,598 --> 01:00:46,643
一起绑架案
A kidnapping.

10
01:00:52,213 --> 01:00:54,259
很抱歉转移话题  但这样下去不行
Sorry to change the subject, but this isn't working.

11
01:00:55,042 --> 01:00:57,175
恐怕你必须要把我的拇指
You're going to have to dislocate my thumb,

12
01:00:57,218 --> 01:00:58,218
弄脱臼了
I'm afraid.

13
01:00:59,612 --> 01:01:00,612
什么
What?

14
01:01:01,135 --> 01:01:04,095
你抓着我的大拇指  用力向后弯
You take my thumb and you bend it all the way back.

15
01:01:04,661 --> 01:01:06,967
快点  来呀
Quickly, come on.

16
01:01:07,794 --> 01:01:09,970
数到三  好吗
On the... The count of three, okay?

17
01:01:11,668 --> 01:01:12,669
好了
All right.

18
01:01:14,192 --> 01:01:19,197
一  二  三
One, two, three.

19
01:01:21,416 --> 01:01:22,679
他妈的用力
Just fucking do it.

20
01:01:24,681 --> 01:01:26,117
抱歉  抱歉
Oh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.

21
01:01:29,207 --> 01:01:30,599
奏效了吗
Did that work?

22
01:01:30,643 --> 01:01:33,951
天哪  天哪
Oh, God, Jesus.

23
01:01:33,994 --> 01:01:36,823
让我看看行不行
Okay. Let's see what we can do here.

24
01:01:41,132 --> 01:01:43,787
好吧
Right.

25
01:01:43,830 --> 01:01:45,179
光是拇指不够
Thumb wasn't enough.

26
01:01:45,223 --> 01:01:47,007
你得再试试食指
You're gonna have to try the index finger.

27
01:01:47,051 --> 01:01:48,095
什么
What?

28
01:01:48,400 --> 01:01:50,315
-快点  -不行  我不敢  真的
- Come on. - No. I... I can't. Please.

29
01:01:50,968 --> 01:01:54,188
你小时候我就抛弃了你  把这想作是复仇
I abandoned you as a child. Consider this your revenge.

30
01:01:55,886 --> 01:01:58,671
发泄你所有的怒气  来啊
Channel all that anger. Come on.

31
01:02:03,154 --> 01:02:04,155
我操
Oh, fuck!

32
01:02:04,982 --> 01:02:08,072
龟儿子的
Ooh, hoo, oh, hoo, baby.

33
01:02:08,420 --> 01:02:10,422
天哪
Oh, God.

34
01:02:15,209 --> 01:02:16,210
操
Fuck.

35
01:02:53,726 --> 01:02:54,945
你得背着我
You're gonna have to carry me.

36
01:02:55,206 --> 01:02:56,555
我们得离开
We have to get as far away

37
01:02:56,598 --> 01:02:57,967
这座该死的房子  越远越好
from this fuckin' house as possible.

38
01:02:57,991 --> 01:02:59,340
我不行
I'm not made for this.

39
01:02:59,384 --> 01:03:01,516
你想让我被一个驼子折磨至死吗
You want to be tortured to death by a hunchback?

40
01:03:09,568 --> 01:03:11,613
等等  等等  放  放  放
Wait! Wait! Put... put... put... put... put...

41
01:03:11,657 --> 01:03:14,529
放我下来  放我下来
Put me down. Put me down. Whoa, whoa.

42
01:03:15,226 --> 01:03:17,097
我要喝水  给我拿点水  好吗
I need some water. Get me some water, will you?

43
01:03:17,141 --> 01:03:19,056
-好  -快点
- Okay. - Okay, hurry up.

44
01:03:30,632 --> 01:03:31,677
你一只耳朵没了
You're missing an ear.

45
01:03:31,720 --> 01:03:33,070
-你知道吗  -知道
- You know that? - Mm-hmm.

46
01:03:33,679 --> 01:03:35,072
戈登打掉的
Gordon kicked it off.

47
01:03:35,768 --> 01:03:38,205
我们要找一下吗  医生可以缝上的
Well, shall we go find it? They... they can sew it back on.

48
01:03:38,249 --> 01:03:40,338
怕是不可能了
Not gonna be possible, I'm afraid.

49
01:03:40,381 --> 01:03:41,513
为什么
Why not?

50
01:03:41,556 --> 01:03:43,036
就是不行  好吗
It's just not, okay?

51
01:03:43,776 --> 01:03:44,777
为什么
Why?

52
01:03:47,780 --> 01:03:48,912
我吃了
I ate it.

53
01:03:49,956 --> 01:03:51,436
你  你  你吃了你的耳朵
You... you... You ate your own ear?

54
01:03:52,089 --> 01:03:53,568
他逼我的
He made me.

55
01:03:53,612 --> 01:03:56,049
他让我在我的耳朵和一小杯
He gave me a choice between my own ear or a shot-glass

56
01:03:56,093 --> 01:03:58,399
他的精液间作出选择  就像某种
of his semen... like some kind of

57
01:03:58,443 --> 01:04:00,227
日本游戏节目之类里的
Japanese game show or something.

58
01:04:00,271 --> 01:04:01,620
我选择了耳朵
And I chose the ear.

59
01:04:04,623 --> 01:04:05,929
他逼得我快饿死了
He was starving me!

60
01:04:06,712 --> 01:04:08,018
但精液相比耳朵来说
Um, but semen contains

61
01:04:08,061 --> 01:04:09,715
包含更多的蛋白质和营养
more protein and nutrients than an ear.

62
01:04:09,758 --> 01:04:11,282
-耳朵只有软骨  -听着
- Ears are just cartilage. - Look!

63
01:04:11,978 --> 01:04:13,458
精液是黄色的  好吗
The semen was yellow, okay?

64
01:04:13,980 --> 01:04:15,590
我才不会向你解释我选择的原因
I'm not defending my choice to you.

65
01:04:15,634 --> 01:04:17,114
他妈的快走
Let's fucking go!

66
01:04:19,246 --> 01:04:20,857
我能去下厕所吗
Can I go to the toilet?

67
01:04:22,119 --> 01:04:23,381
选一还是选二
Number one or number two?

68
01:04:23,424 --> 01:04:25,470
一  他妈的搞快点
One. Be really fucking quick.

69
01:04:27,820 --> 01:04:34,696
{\an9}*你真地教我如何玩这场游戏*
*You really showed me how to play the game*

70
01:04:38,178 --> 01:04:39,266
丹迪
Dandy!

71
01:04:40,833 --> 01:04:43,183
丹迪  你不准动我儿子
Dandy! Don't you touch my son!

72
01:04:43,488 --> 01:04:45,229
你他妈的不准动他
Don't you fucking touch him!

73
01:04:49,929 --> 01:04:50,929
诺瓦尔
Norval!

74
01:05:03,203 --> 01:05:04,639
起来  诺瓦尔
Come on, Norval!

75
01:05:15,737 --> 01:05:17,000
不是你死就是他死
It's you or him!

76
01:05:21,874 --> 01:05:23,745
做你该做的  儿子
Do what you have to do, son.

77
01:05:35,192 --> 01:05:37,542
杀死那个混蛋  杀死他
Kill the fucker! Kill him!

78
01:06:22,848 --> 01:06:23,849
儿子
Son.

79
01:06:26,895 --> 01:06:28,027
你没事吧
Are you okay?

80
01:06:32,814 --> 01:06:33,859
诺瓦尔
Norval?

81
01:06:37,558 --> 01:06:39,604
请告诉我你没事
Please tell me you're okay.

82
01:07:26,955 --> 01:07:28,479
刚刚发生的一切
What happened in there, you know...

83
01:07:29,306 --> 01:07:30,481
那  那
it's... it's...

84
01:07:31,786 --> 01:07:33,005
那总是
It's always...

85
01:07:34,441 --> 01:07:35,486
我是说
I mean...

86
01:07:37,140 --> 01:07:38,793
我想说  那
What I'm saying is it's...

87
01:07:43,320 --> 01:07:44,799
走吧  我们得走了
Come on. We've got to go.

88
01:07:45,191 --> 01:07:46,323
我们得走了
We've got to go!

89
01:07:56,202 --> 01:07:58,030
-谁是瑞恩  -什么
- Who was Ryan? - Huh?

90
01:07:59,292 --> 01:08:03,253
戈登脖子上有个文身
Gordon had a tattoo on his neck.

91
01:08:03,296 --> 01:08:04,602
"逝者安息  瑞恩"
"R.I.P Ryan".

92
01:08:04,645 --> 01:08:05,864
瑞恩
Oh, Ryan.

93
01:08:06,256 --> 01:08:07,866
那是戈登的儿子
That was Gordon's son.

94
01:08:08,258 --> 01:08:10,695
在浴室割腕自杀了
Slashed his wrists in the bath.

95
01:08:10,956 --> 01:08:13,828
太悲哀了  他是个好孩子
Sad story. He was a decent kid.

96
01:08:17,789 --> 01:08:18,833
隐蔽
Hide!

97
01:08:51,692 --> 01:08:54,347
我的小朋友迫不及待想见你们了
My little friend can't wait to meet you,

98
01:08:54,391 --> 01:08:56,915
你们俩该死的讨厌鬼
you fuckin' wank-stains!

99
01:08:58,569 --> 01:08:59,570
操
Shit.

100
01:09:01,659 --> 01:09:03,356
我们得离开这里
We have to get the fuck away from here.

101
01:09:05,053 --> 01:09:07,882
等等  爸爸  等等  我刚意识到一件事
Wait! Dad, wait! I just realized something.

102
01:09:07,926 --> 01:09:09,710
-什么  -我和妈妈的地址
- What? - Me and mom's address

103
01:09:09,754 --> 01:09:11,277
写在我的行李吊牌上
is written on my luggage tag.

104
01:09:11,321 --> 01:09:14,324
-如果他发现的话  -操
- If he finds it... - Fuck.

105
01:09:15,238 --> 01:09:16,413
我们怎么办
What do we do?

106
01:09:18,415 --> 01:09:19,503
操
Fuck!

107
01:09:25,204 --> 01:09:26,466
你得杀死他
You're gonna have to kill him.

108
01:09:28,207 --> 01:09:29,469
我又不是杀人犯
I'm not a murderer.

109
01:09:29,948 --> 01:09:32,603
五分钟前你就杀了个人
You just killed somebody literally five minutes ago.

110
01:09:33,256 --> 01:09:34,953
如果我能亲手杀死他我会很高兴
I'd gladly kill the fucker myself,

111
01:09:34,996 --> 01:09:36,172
但看看我现在这副样子
but look at me.

112
01:09:39,262 --> 01:09:41,220
如果你不去杀死他
If you don't go in there and kill him,

113
01:09:41,264 --> 01:09:44,049
我们就会永无宁日  你现在卷入这件事了
we'll never be safe. You're part of this now.

114
01:09:44,310 --> 01:09:45,442
你妈妈也是
So is your mother.

115
01:09:47,618 --> 01:09:50,273
他有一把火弩  我什么也没有
He has a flaming crossbow. I have nothing.

116
01:09:50,664 --> 01:09:52,100
在他手下我一秒都撑不了
I wouldn't last a second.

117
01:10:01,632 --> 01:10:03,416
你藏在他车的后备箱里
You hide in the trunk of his car.

118
01:10:03,460 --> 01:10:06,463
他去哪你都跟着  当他一个人的时候
You follow him everywhere. And then when he's alone,

119
01:10:07,159 --> 01:10:08,639
趁其不备
when he's vulnerable...

120
01:10:08,682 --> 01:10:09,770
丹迪
Dandy!

121
01:10:10,684 --> 01:10:11,903
怎么会这样
Not Dandy!

122
01:10:12,773 --> 01:10:14,819
你们他妈的也杀了丹迪
You fuckin' killed Dandy too.

123
01:10:15,646 --> 01:10:16,734
去
Go!

124
01:10:42,760 --> 01:10:44,979
这是对住在加利福尼亚州
This is an important announcement

125
01:10:45,284 --> 01:10:47,025
比弗利山庄  西林登大道
for Norval Greenwood

126
01:10:47,678 --> 01:10:51,812
91622号的诺瓦尔·格林伍德的
of 91622 West Linden Drive,

127
01:10:52,117 --> 01:10:54,685
严正声明
Beverly Hills, California!

128
01:10:54,728 --> 01:10:57,862
你和格林伍德家族的其他人
You and the rest of the Greenwood family

129
01:10:57,905 --> 01:11:00,256
现在正式完蛋了
are now officially fucked!

130
01:11:01,344 --> 01:11:03,041
这是官方声明
It's official!

131
01:11:32,723 --> 01:11:34,899
普蕾莎丝  对  对
Precious? Yeah, yeah.

132
01:11:34,942 --> 01:11:37,031
我叫杰思罗  我是丹迪的朋友
My name's Jethro. I'm a mate of Dandy's.

133
01:11:37,423 --> 01:11:39,686
对  我是坐在角落看着的那个人
Yeah. I was the guy sitting in the corner watching.

134
01:11:39,730 --> 01:11:40,730
对
Yeah.

135
01:11:40,948 --> 01:11:42,210
听着
Look, listen.

136
01:11:42,254 --> 01:11:43,971
你可以和我在旅馆见面聊会儿吗
Could you meet me at the hotel for a session?

137
01:11:43,995 --> 01:11:46,389
宝贝  我真的压力很大  求你了
Like, I'm really stressed. Please.

138
01:11:46,693 --> 01:11:47,825
尽快
As soon as you can.

139
01:11:49,174 --> 01:11:50,480
你真是太好了
Oh, you're an angel.

140
01:12:56,981 --> 01:12:57,982
操
Fuck.

141
01:13:03,944 --> 01:13:04,989
操
Shit.

142
01:13:27,403 --> 01:13:28,403
你好
Hi.

143
01:13:32,277 --> 01:13:34,322
-你是妓女吗  -什么
- Are you a prostitute? - Excuse me?

144
01:13:34,366 --> 01:13:36,194
无论他付多少  我付三倍
Whatever he pays, I'll triple it.

145
01:13:36,237 --> 01:13:38,196
你要做的就是  当你离开时
All you have to do is leave the door open

146
01:13:38,239 --> 01:13:39,371
把门开着留条缝
a little when you leave.

147
01:13:39,763 --> 01:13:41,678
听着  普蕾莎丝
Listen, Precious...

1
01:13:42,113 --> 01:13:43,897
你他妈怎么知道我的名字
How in the fuck do you know my name?

2
01:13:43,941 --> 01:13:47,161
在我动手之前滚
Get the fuck out of here before I tear your nuts off.

3
01:13:54,691 --> 01:13:55,866
噢  该死
Oh, shit.

4
01:14:01,393 --> 01:14:03,613
嘿  嘿  嘿  嘿...
Hey, hey. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.

5
01:14:03,656 --> 01:14:05,223
噢  你好
Oh. Okay.

6
01:14:05,745 --> 01:14:07,486
你需要点什么
How can I help you, sir?

7
01:14:07,530 --> 01:14:09,749
我想订个房间  谢谢
Uh, I'd like to rent a room, please.

8
01:14:09,793 --> 01:14:12,186
啊  不好意思  我们所有房间都满了
Ah, no, no, no, no. The whole motel is booked out,

9
01:14:12,230 --> 01:14:14,493
因为镇上有个地理学会
what with the geology conference in town.

10
01:14:15,451 --> 01:14:17,148
-地理学会  -是的
-Geology conference? - Yeah.

11
01:14:17,191 --> 01:14:19,455
事实上该叫滥交大会
It's really a swinger's convention.

12
01:14:19,498 --> 01:14:21,674
不是唬你  整个旅馆住满了
I shit you not. I have a whole motel full

13
01:14:21,718 --> 01:14:25,635
超饥渴的人  正在乱搞呢
of flabby sex people, just doing whatever they do.

14
01:14:25,678 --> 01:14:28,376
不过  我们还有一间家庭房
But, um, we do have one family unit available,

15
01:14:28,420 --> 01:14:30,161
但是还得过去一段路
but it's, uh, further down the road.

16
01:14:31,510 --> 01:14:33,512
-我更想住这里  -好的
-I'd prefer a room here. - Yeah.

17
01:14:33,556 --> 01:14:35,166
我猜你也更想住这里
I bet you would prefer a room here.

18
01:14:35,209 --> 01:14:37,516
但是我刚刚说过了  每一个房间
But as I already said, there are geologists

19
01:14:37,560 --> 01:14:39,387
都给地理学家们住了  每一个
in every room of the motel, bar none.

20
01:14:39,431 --> 01:14:41,564
现在只剩家庭房了
The one that is available is a family unit

21
01:14:41,607 --> 01:14:42,913
就在那边
some distance away.

22
01:14:42,956 --> 01:14:45,045
所以你是要订个家庭房
Now, would you like to rent said family unit?

23
01:14:45,089 --> 01:14:47,352
还是要一直在这里和我吵呢
Or do you want to keep doing what we're doing here?

24
01:14:48,396 --> 01:14:51,269
-我待会再来  -好 等你
-Maybe later. -Okay, maybe later.

25
01:14:51,791 --> 01:14:52,792
再见
Bye now.

26
01:15:10,941 --> 01:15:12,725
嘿
Hey.

27
01:15:15,119 --> 01:15:16,120
怎么了
Yes?

28
01:15:16,990 --> 01:15:21,081
我想我得让你知道有个可疑的女人
I thought I might let you know there's a suspicious woman

29
01:15:21,125 --> 01:15:22,779
一直在外边开车晃悠
lingering by a car out there.

30
01:15:24,084 --> 01:15:25,564
可疑的女人
A suspicious woman?

31
01:15:26,478 --> 01:15:29,176
相信我  她超正的
Trust me. Yeah. She's legit.

32
01:15:31,048 --> 01:15:34,878
好吧  很明显你有点性变态
Okay. So, you're clearly some kind of sex freak.

33
01:15:35,618 --> 01:15:38,185
但我确实感兴趣  不骗你
But I am intrigued, I'm not gonna lie.

34
01:15:38,838 --> 01:15:41,624
我认真的  她身材超棒
I'm serious. Incredible body.

35
01:15:42,538 --> 01:15:43,930
好  实话告诉你
All right. Full disclosure,

36
01:15:43,974 --> 01:15:45,671
我跟你摊牌吧
I'm gonna put all my cards on the table.

37
01:15:45,715 --> 01:15:48,761
我这种在医学上被称为爆乳狂热者
I'm what's known in medical circles as a titty-holic.

38
01:15:48,805 --> 01:15:49,805
懂吗
All right?

39
01:15:50,371 --> 01:15:52,306
所以  我下一个问题就是  她有没有
So, naturally my next questionto you is does she, like...

40
01:15:52,330 --> 01:15:54,593
听我说  如果这个女人
Let me stop you right there, and say that if this woman

41
01:15:54,637 --> 01:15:55,942
要去买胸罩
were shopping for bras,

42
01:15:55,986 --> 01:15:57,826
她一定得买两个D那么大的
she'd be found in the area designated Double D.

43
01:16:02,209 --> 01:16:04,951
好吧  先生  等我一下
Okay, well,sir, I will just be right back.

44
01:16:04,995 --> 01:16:07,084
给我几分钟  我要去查看一下
Give me a minute, I'll go and investigate.

45
01:16:07,127 --> 01:16:08,825
去弄个明白
I'll get to the bottom of this.

46
01:16:09,173 --> 01:16:10,173
好的
All right.

47
01:16:51,563 --> 01:16:54,087
喜欢这样吗
Huh? How do you like that shit,

48
01:16:54,522 --> 01:16:56,394
你个断屌欠操脸
you limp-dicked fuckface?

49
01:16:56,437 --> 01:16:58,614
现在真的爽  用力拉
Really get aggressive now. Really pull.

50
01:16:59,440 --> 01:17:01,312
-用力  -操你妈的
-Harder! - Fuck you.

51
01:18:25,483 --> 01:18:26,484
用红色的那个
Use the red one.

52
01:19:31,027 --> 01:19:33,072
过来
Come on.

53
01:19:33,116 --> 01:19:34,900
你喜欢这样吗
Oh. So, you like that, huh?

54
01:19:37,381 --> 01:19:38,512
我说过什么
What did I say?

55
01:19:39,339 --> 01:19:41,689
这是老子私事  滚出去
This is private business. Now, fuck off!

56
01:19:41,733 --> 01:19:45,345
听着  普蕾莎丝  我不是来找你事的
Uh, listen, Precious, my fight isn't with you.

57
01:19:45,389 --> 01:19:46,738
我不这么觉得
Agree to disagree.

58
01:19:58,054 --> 01:19:59,620
普蕾莎丝  给我抓紧他
Hold him tight for me, Precious.

59
01:20:03,015 --> 01:20:07,890
马上  你就要死在这里了
Now, you are going to die here.

60
01:20:10,980 --> 01:20:12,764
而我  要去洛杉矶
And I'm going to L.A.

61
01:20:13,460 --> 01:20:15,898
所以  还有什么话要对你妈妈说吗
So, do have any little message for your mommy?

62
01:20:16,637 --> 01:20:17,943
告诉她我爱她
Tell her I love her.

63
01:20:18,204 --> 01:20:20,772
那我要特地告诉她
I'm gonna specifically tell her

64
01:20:20,816 --> 01:20:22,426
你不爱她
that you don't love her.

65
01:20:23,253 --> 01:20:24,645
混蛋
Bastard!

66
01:20:37,615 --> 01:20:39,573
我
Get...

67
01:20:39,617 --> 01:20:41,662
去你妈的
fucking in!

68
01:20:47,146 --> 01:20:48,191
啊  该死
Oh, bugger.

69
01:20:48,234 --> 01:20:50,323
本来是想刺你耳朵的
That was supposed to go in your ear.

70
01:20:51,107 --> 01:20:53,152
-不好意思了  -啊
-Sorry about that. - Oh!

71
01:20:53,196 --> 01:20:55,633
不  不  不  啊  该死
Oh, no, no, no, no. Ah, shit.

72
01:20:59,028 --> 01:21:01,030
嘿  不要  不  不
Hey. No, no, no, no.

73
01:21:02,031 --> 01:21:03,119
嘿
Hey!

74
01:21:04,033 --> 01:21:05,512
你杀了他
I think you killed him.

75
01:21:06,905 --> 01:21:08,951
是你杀了他  你个大蠢逼
You killed him, you big tonk twat.

76
01:21:08,994 --> 01:21:11,083
你把他给勒死了
You just fuckin' squeezed the life clean out of him.

77
01:21:11,127 --> 01:21:12,171
我看见了
I watched you.

78
01:21:18,830 --> 01:21:20,092
你知道吗
Do you know something?

79
01:21:21,006 --> 01:21:23,835
去他妈的破事
Sod this fuckin' sad-sack situation.

80
01:21:23,879 --> 01:21:25,532
我要走了
I'm out of here like Vladimir.

81
01:21:27,143 --> 01:21:29,449
你这个冷血的变态
You are a cold-blooded psychopath.

82
01:21:30,842 --> 01:21:32,148
我是变态
I'm a psychopath?

83
01:21:33,540 --> 01:21:36,456
那你是靠向寂寞男人
You're a muscle-bound prozzie who gets lonely men

84
01:21:36,500 --> 01:21:38,763
卖肉赚钱的莽女人
into headlocks for cash!

85
01:21:38,806 --> 01:21:40,765
还有  甜心
And let me tell you something else, sweetheart,

86
01:21:40,808 --> 01:21:42,941
有一种东西叫除臭剂
there's been this invention called deodorant.

87
01:21:42,985 --> 01:21:45,465
有空试试  好吗
You should try it sometime. All right?

88
01:21:47,511 --> 01:21:48,512
天呐
Jesus!

89
01:21:53,778 --> 01:21:55,388
啊  操
Oh, fuck.

90
01:22:00,698 --> 01:22:02,047
搞什么
What the fuck?

91
01:22:04,702 --> 01:22:05,921
操
Fuck.

92
01:22:16,583 --> 01:22:20,196
*加利福利亚我来了*
*California, here I come*

93
01:22:20,544 --> 01:22:23,764
*回到最开始的地方*
*Right back where we started from*

94
01:22:23,808 --> 01:22:26,419
*我迷恋加利福利亚*
*I got that California itch*

95
01:22:26,463 --> 01:22:29,857
*我会杀了你妈再把弃尸阴沟*
*I'm gonna kill your momma and leave her in a ditch*

96
01:22:29,901 --> 01:22:31,511
没错
Yeah.

97
01:22:31,555 --> 01:22:34,297
*最好告诉她  杰思罗就要来了*
*Better go tell her Jethro's coming for her*

98
01:22:38,257 --> 01:22:39,389
没错
Yeah.

99
01:22:43,001 --> 01:22:44,698
我  我似乎是帮凶
I'm, like, an accessory to murder.

100
01:22:44,742 --> 01:22:47,397
这真是  啊  该死
This is... Oh, shit.

101
01:22:49,268 --> 01:22:52,402
我应该  我应该会被判无期徒刑
This is, like, oh... It's, like, a life sentence.

102
01:22:58,756 --> 01:22:59,757
嗨
Hi.

103
01:24:57,657 --> 01:24:59,659
听好了  诺瓦尔
Listen very carefully,Norval.

104
01:25:00,530 --> 01:25:02,184
这很重要
This is very important.

105
01:25:03,489 --> 01:25:05,796
你必须得听仔细了
So, it's vital that you listen carefully.

106
01:25:06,275 --> 01:25:07,493
怎么了
Right?

107
01:25:08,451 --> 01:25:10,148
你妈妈是个妓女
Your mother is a prostitute.

108
01:25:11,410 --> 01:25:15,545
你爸爸是常客  他们就这么认识的
That's how your father met her.He was a frequent flier.

109
01:25:18,243 --> 01:25:20,593
你以为她叫杰奎琳
You think her name is Jacqueline.

110
01:25:21,290 --> 01:25:23,118
其实她叫安妮
But her real name is Annie.

111
01:25:24,075 --> 01:25:25,207
我操过她
I fucked her.

112
01:25:26,033 --> 01:25:29,167
准确地说  我在一个废弃工厂里操过她
I fucked her in an abandoned factory to be precise.

113
01:25:30,516 --> 01:25:32,170
但是我早泄了
But I lost my erection.

114
01:25:33,432 --> 01:25:35,173
因为从某些角度
Because from certain angles,

115
01:25:35,434 --> 01:25:37,828
她让我想起迈克尔·赫塞尔廷
she reminded me of Michael Heseltine.

116
01:25:40,918 --> 01:25:42,311
迈克尔·赫塞尔廷
Michael Heseltine...

117
01:25:43,747 --> 01:25:44,835
你也许不知道
if you're wondering...

118
01:25:46,793 --> 01:25:50,057
她是英国80年代的政客
is a British politician from the 1980s.

119
01:26:14,560 --> 01:26:16,171
天哪
Arthur!

120
01:26:53,991 --> 01:26:57,647
亲爱的儿子  我是你的爸爸
Dear Son. It's me, your Dad.

121
01:26:58,430 --> 01:27:00,302
好久不见了  对吧
It's been a while, hasn't it?

122
01:27:00,998 --> 01:27:03,696
坦白来说  我不是世界上最好的父亲
It's fair to say, I've not been the world's best father.

123
01:27:05,132 --> 01:27:06,960
事实上  如果有人
In fact, if someone were to accuse me

124
01:27:07,004 --> 01:27:09,485
因此控诉我  那么
of being a shit excuse for one, well...

125
01:27:10,355 --> 01:27:12,836
我也没什么可辩驳的  对吗
I wouldn't have much of a defense, would I?

126
01:27:13,706 --> 01:27:16,361
但是我想改变
But I want that to change.

127
01:27:18,798 --> 01:27:20,757
也许你宁愿刮胡刀剃屁股
Maybe you'd rather shit a razor blade

128
01:27:20,800 --> 01:27:23,020
也不愿意我回到你的生活
than have your old man back in your life.

129
01:27:24,195 --> 01:27:27,851
但如果不是   你可以在这里来找我
But if not, here's where you can find me.

130
01:27:31,246 --> 01:27:33,204
期待快点见到你  儿子
I hope to see you soon, son.

131
01:27:34,597 --> 01:27:36,033
我还希望你能在心里找到一个
And I hope you can find it

132
01:27:36,076 --> 01:27:37,991
原谅我的理由
in your heart to forgive your old man.

133
01:27:39,254 --> 01:27:42,257
永远爱你  爸爸
With love, always, your father.

134
01:28:31,218 --> 01:28:33,046
我得告诉你一些事
I have to tell you something.

135
01:28:37,355 --> 01:28:39,357
恐怕你听了之后
But I'm afraid it makes me sound

136
01:28:39,401 --> 01:28:40,663
会觉得我是个坏人
like a bad person.

137
01:28:55,286 --> 01:28:57,723
我从没有让妈妈抛弃你
I never let Mom get over you.

138
01:29:09,126 --> 01:29:11,128
所有靠近她的男人
Every man that came along,

139
01:29:12,390 --> 01:29:13,957
都被我赶走了
I drove them away.

140
01:29:20,964 --> 01:29:25,403
她本可以过得很开心的
She had so many chances to be happy.

141
01:29:29,799 --> 01:29:31,453
是我拦住了她
And I never let her.

142
01:29:38,329 --> 01:29:40,331
我总觉得你会回来的
I always thought you'd come back.

143
01:29:43,334 --> 01:29:45,728
我们可以重新开始
And then we'd pick up where we left off.

144
01:29:56,478 --> 01:29:58,349
你为什么写信给我
Why did you write to me?

145
01:30:09,491 --> 01:30:10,535
爸爸
Dad?

146
01:30:13,756 --> 01:30:15,801
为什么  为什么写信给我
Why... why did you write to me?

147
01:35:14,883 --> 01:35:16,101
玩儿蛋去吧
Fuck this shit!

