1
00:00:04,000 --> 00:00:15,000
{\fad(500,500)\fn华文楷体\fs16\1c&H3CF1F3&\b0}--==本影片由 {\1c&HFF8000&\b1}CMCT 团队{\fn华文楷体\1c&H3CF1F3&\b0} 荣誉出品==--
更多精彩影视 请访问 {\fnCronos Pro Subhead\1c&HFF00FF&\b1}http://cmct.cc{\r}

2
00:00:16,000 --> 00:00:22,000
{\fad(500,500)\fn华文楷体\fs16\1c&H3CF1F3&\b0}影片压制:呆呆熊  字幕来源:伊甸园  调校:呆呆熊  招募Q号:76846146{\r}

3
00:00:26,810 --> 00:00:37,180
《孤儿怨》

4
00:00:50,760 --> 00:00:53,130
坚持住 我知道
Hang on. I know.

5
00:00:53,300 --> 00:00:55,180
嗯
Mm.

6
00:00:55,340 --> 00:00:57,510
你做得很好
You're doing so good.

7
00:00:57,680 --> 00:00:59,430
你做得很好 没事儿吧
You're doing so good. You all right'?

8
00:00:59,600 --> 00:01:01,220
- 没事 - 好的
- Yeah. - Okay.

9
00:01:01,390 --> 00:01:04,230
马修斯医生请到护士站
 Dr. Matthews to the nurses' station.

10
00:01:04,390 --> 00:01:05,980
请问
Excuse me.

11
00:01:06,150 --> 00:01:10,150
我太太快生了 我们预约了惠勒医生
My wife's in labor. We called ahead for Dr. Wheeler.

12
00:01:10,320 --> 00:01:12,320
请把表填下
I just need you to fill this out, please.

13
00:01:13,700 --> 00:01:15,820
- 谢谢 - 宝贝 坐下吧
- Thank you. - Have a seat, hon.

14
00:01:23,160 --> 00:01:24,500
- 我马上过来 - 好
- I'll be right up. - Yeah.

15
00:01:24,660 --> 00:01:27,670
- 没事吧 - 没事
- "Okay? " - Okay

16
00:01:28,710 --> 00:01:31,460
- 第一胎 - 不 不 第三胎了
- Is this your first? - No, no, it's our third.

17
00:01:32,050 --> 00:01:33,630
先生 请在这儿签名
Sir, can you sign here?

18
00:01:35,510 --> 00:01:38,510
我们准备叫她杰西卡
We're gonna name her Jessica.

19
00:02:09,000 --> 00:02:10,630
生命体征正常
Vitals look good.

20
00:02:13,880 --> 00:02:15,380
约翰在哪儿
Where's John?

21
00:02:15,550 --> 00:02:18,010
- 我老公呢 - 放松
- Where's my husband? - Just relax now.

22
00:02:18,180 --> 00:02:19,590
会很顺利的
Everything's gonna be okay.

23
00:02:26,310 --> 00:02:28,560
怎么了 你们在干什么
What's happening? What are you doing?

24
00:02:28,730 --> 00:02:30,100
很遗憾没保住
I'm so sorry for your loss.

25
00:02:30,270 --> 00:02:32,400
- 什么 - 胎儿死了
- What? - Your baby's dead.

26
00:02:32,570 --> 00:02:34,780
不 没死呀 活着的
No, it's not dead. It's alive.

27
00:02:34,940 --> 00:02:36,860
你在说什么呀 还在动呢
What are you talking about? It's moving.

28
00:02:37,030 --> 00:02:40,160
非常遗憾 我们很抱歉
It's a terrible loss. We're so sorry.

29
00:02:40,370 --> 00:02:43,790
- 放松吧 - 不
- Just relax. - No!

30
00:02:43,950 --> 00:02:46,830
什么不 不 不 给我打麻药 让我麻醉
What? No, no, no. Put me to sleep. I wanna be asleep.

31
00:02:47,000 --> 00:02:50,330
- 来不及了 - 不
It's too late for that. - No!

32
00:02:54,050 --> 00:02:55,590
没事的 宝贝 你做得很好
It's okay, you're doing great.

33
00:02:56,420 --> 00:02:58,420
你在干嘛 你在干嘛
What are you doing? What are you doing?

34
00:02:58,590 --> 00:03:00,220
你可能会因拉扯而有点痛
You might feel some tugging.

35
00:03:06,270 --> 00:03:08,890
上帝呀 这不是真的
Oh, my God. This isn't happening.

36
00:03:10,480 --> 00:03:13,980
恭喜你 科尔曼太太 是女孩
Congratulations, Mrs. Coleman. It's a girl.

37
00:04:29,640 --> 00:04:33,140
是的 凯特 日有所思夜有所梦
Yes, Kate, your dreams can be a manifestation of your emotions.

38
00:04:33,310 --> 00:04:35,480
这是你的身心面对压力
It's your body and mind's way of dealing...

39
00:04:35,650 --> 00:04:38,150
和曾经的痛苦的方式
...with the stress and grief of what happened.

40
00:04:38,320 --> 00:04:41,030
如果是与死产无关呢
What if this has nothing to do with the stillbirth?

41
00:04:41,190 --> 00:04:43,070
你觉得会是什么原因
What do you think it's about?

42
00:04:44,780 --> 00:04:47,700
这个周末我们将首次去见孩子们
We're seeing kids for the first time this weekend.

43
00:04:47,870 --> 00:04:51,330
也许这噩梦…
And maybe the nightmares...

44
00:04:55,040 --> 00:04:58,420
也许我还没准备好领养
Maybe I'm just not ready to adopt yet.

45
00:05:04,260 --> 00:05:07,970
前两天晚上我开车回家 路过酒铺
I drove by the wine shop on the way home the other night.

46
00:05:09,470 --> 00:05:10,720
你停车了吗
Did you stop?

47
00:05:10,890 --> 00:05:14,730
没 想停 有这个冲动
No. Wanted to. The thought went through my brain, you know?

48
00:05:14,890 --> 00:05:16,810
不是买给自己 不是…
It wasn't for myself. It wasn't...

49
00:05:16,980 --> 00:05:18,570
我只是觉得万一有客人来
I just thought it would be nice

50
00:05:18,580 --> 00:05:20,940
能以美酒款待 多好啊
to have a bottle handy, in case we had guests.

51
00:05:21,110 --> 00:05:22,360
但你没有进去
But you didn't go in.

52
00:05:24,990 --> 00:05:26,320
嗯嗯
Mm- mm.

53
00:05:26,490 --> 00:05:28,530
我的解释是…
The key, to me...

54
00:05:28,700 --> 00:05:31,120
不是你不想
...is not that you had the urge...

55
00:05:31,290 --> 00:05:32,950
但是你抵抗住了
...but that you resisted it.

56
00:05:33,120 --> 00:05:34,540
如果你没有做好准备
You wouldn't have made it

57
00:05:34,540 --> 00:05:37,040
你可是无法完成家庭作业的
through the home study if you weren't ready.

58
00:05:37,210 --> 00:05:38,670
但 最终…
But, ultimately...

59
00:05:38,840 --> 00:05:41,300
你得做出决定
...you have to decide.

60
00:06:04,610 --> 00:06:06,240
嗨
Hi.

61
00:06:07,280 --> 00:06:10,450
嗨 宝贝
Honey, hello.

62
00:06:10,620 --> 00:06:13,160
我看看 是你画的吗
Let me see. Ooh. Did you paint this?

63
00:06:13,400 --> 00:06:14,420
老师辅导的

64
00:06:14,540 --> 00:06:18,170
真是漂亮的蝴蝶 太棒了
It's a beautiful butterfly. It's fantastic.

65
00:06:18,330 --> 00:06:20,460
真是棒极了 真棒
Really wonderful. Good.

66
00:06:20,630 --> 00:06:23,630
走吧 好冷呀
Let's go. I'm cold.

67
00:06:52,410 --> 00:06:54,160
你没事吧
Are you okay?

68
00:08:13,160 --> 00:08:14,740
啊
Ah!

69
00:08:19,790 --> 00:08:21,040
麦克斯
Max!

70
00:08:21,210 --> 00:08:22,870
麦克斯
Max!

71
00:08:23,040 --> 00:08:24,750
别扔球了
Stop throwing!

72
00:08:24,920 --> 00:08:27,710
我在工作呢
I'm working.

73
00:08:28,240 --> 00:08:28,700
抱歉

74
00:08:28,750 --> 00:08:30,050
不 宝贝 对不起
No, honey, I'm sorry.

75
00:08:30,210 --> 00:08:32,760
稍微歇一会儿 好吗
Just take a break for a little while, okay?

76
00:08:32,930 --> 00:08:35,970
因为妈妈在弹琴 好吗
Because Mommy's trying to play. Okay?

77
00:08:40,270 --> 00:08:42,180
爸爸来了
Daddy's here.

78
00:08:45,770 --> 00:08:47,230
- 我的 - 嘿
- Mine. - Hey.

79
00:08:48,270 --> 00:08:50,940
- 嗨 - 抱歉 训练晚了点
- Hi. - Sorry, practice went a little late.

80
00:08:51,110 --> 00:08:53,570
没事
It's all right.

81
00:08:54,360 --> 00:08:57,280
- 好了 硬汉 给我 - 耍赖
- Okay, tough guy. Give me that.- Wicked.

82
00:08:58,660 --> 00:08:59,990
不 不
No, no.

83
00:09:00,160 --> 00:09:02,620
投篮 投篮 投 投 投
Shoot it, shoot it. Go, go, go, go.

84
00:09:02,790 --> 00:09:06,500
- 不 - 耶 击掌
- No. - Yes! Give me five.

85
00:09:06,670 --> 00:09:08,630
嘿 怎么样 丹尼尔
Hey, how did it go? Daniel.

86
00:09:08,790 --> 00:09:10,380
挺好的
Fine.

87
00:09:15,340 --> 00:09:17,260
嘿
Hey.

88
00:09:18,260 --> 00:09:19,310
好了
Okay.

89
00:09:19,470 --> 00:09:21,350
就玩五分钟 打到最后一关了
Five minutes. I'm at the last level.

90
00:09:21,520 --> 00:09:23,310
别玩电玩了 去刷牙
No more video games. Brush your teeth.

91
00:09:23,480 --> 00:09:26,150
太不公平了 没存档呢 老爸行行好 好吗
That's no fair. It won't save. Come on, Dad, please?

92
00:09:35,510 --> 00:09:37,480
今晚我们读点别的吧

93
00:09:40,040 --> 00:09:41,410
好吧

94
00:09:49,570 --> 00:09:52,390
我等了整整一夜…

95
00:09:53,140 --> 00:09:57,070
为了见我新生的小妹妹

96
00:10:00,020 --> 00:10:01,510
不过…

97
00:10:02,100 --> 00:10:04,160
当妈妈和爸爸回到家时

98
00:10:04,360 --> 00:10:06,560
妈妈告诉我说

99
00:10:07,150 --> 00:10:10,850
我的小妹妹去了天堂

100
00:10:17,110 --> 00:10:20,900
我为妹妹去了天堂而感到高兴

101
00:10:28,830 --> 00:10:33,430
但我真希望在此之前能先见她一面

102
00:10:38,790 --> 00:10:42,180
小杰西卡是天使么

103
00:10:45,210 --> 00:10:48,140
是的 是只漂亮的小天使

104
00:11:05,700 --> 00:11:09,790
我会拥有一个新姐妹么

105
00:11:17,160 --> 00:11:18,820
我不知道

106
00:11:53,080 --> 00:11:54,130
抱歉
Sorry.

107
00:11:54,290 --> 00:11:56,670
抱歉 抱歉 抱歉
Sorry, sorry, sorry.

108
00:11:56,840 --> 00:11:58,050
上帝呀
God.

109
00:12:03,430 --> 00:12:04,720
你闻起来真香
You smell good.

110
00:12:16,570 --> 00:12:18,150
好吧
Okay.

111
00:12:19,360 --> 00:12:21,400
好吧
All right.

112
00:12:24,990 --> 00:12:28,410
我不能再像这样了
I have to stop being like this.

113
00:12:28,580 --> 00:12:30,290
我知道
I get it.

114
00:12:38,460 --> 00:12:42,420
我很激动 很高兴
I'm very excited, I'm happy.

115
00:12:42,800 --> 00:12:44,930
还有些紧张
I get nervous.

116
00:12:45,800 --> 00:12:47,970
真得很害怕
I'm really scared.

117
00:12:50,980 --> 00:12:55,980
上次我失去孩子 也是这种感觉
Last time I felt all of this was right before I lost the baby.

118
00:12:56,150 --> 00:12:57,550
我不想让你觉得
I don't want you to feel like

119
00:12:57,560 --> 00:12:59,690
是为了我 才必须经历这些的
we have to go through with this for my sake.

120
00:12:59,860 --> 00:13:03,200
不只是…不是为了你
It's not just... It's not for you.

121
00:13:03,360 --> 00:13:05,450
我想弥补对杰西卡的爱
I wanna take the love we felt for Jessica...

122
00:13:05,610 --> 00:13:09,580
我想把这份爱给真正需要的人
...and I wanna give it to somebody who really needs it.

123
00:13:12,960 --> 00:13:14,920
你准备好了吗 宝贝
Are you sure, hon?

124
00:13:17,630 --> 00:13:19,300
是的
Yes.

125
00:13:40,570 --> 00:13:43,440
- 想堆雪人吗 - 好啊
- Wanna make a snowman? - Sure.

126
00:13:43,610 --> 00:13:45,030
外面好冷呀
It's really cold out here.

127
00:13:51,830 --> 00:13:53,450
嘿 别这样
Hey, stop it.

128
00:14:00,880 --> 00:14:02,590
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.

129
00:14:02,760 --> 00:14:04,050
很高兴你们来了
So glad you could make it.

130
00:14:04,210 --> 00:14:06,300
- 我们也很高兴 - 是呀 终于来了 对吧
- So are we. - Yeah, finally, right?

131
00:14:07,260 --> 00:14:10,470
- 很高兴见到你 - 感谢你们的到来
- So good to see you. - Thank you for coming.

132
00:14:11,850 --> 00:14:14,810
- 真不错 - 随便逛下吧
- This is really something. - So go take a look around.

133
00:14:15,350 --> 00:14:17,940
- 别惹麻烦哟 - 好 好
- Stay out of trouble. - Yeah, yeah.

134
00:14:21,320 --> 00:14:22,690
看 孤儿雪人
Look at the snow orphan.

135
00:14:22,860 --> 00:14:24,230
孤儿雪人
Snow orphan?

136
00:14:24,400 --> 00:14:26,860
孤雪人
Uh, snorphan?

137
00:14:37,000 --> 00:14:41,290
- 嘿 - 不 给玛丽修女看看
- Hey. - No, show it to Sister Mary.

138
00:15:04,020 --> 00:15:07,440
- 慢点 慢点 - 你抓不到我
- Slow down, slow down. - You can't catch me.

139
00:15:07,610 --> 00:15:08,740
谁说的
Yes, I can.

140
00:15:36,220 --> 00:15:37,980
你好
Hello?

141
00:15:42,440 --> 00:15:43,940
嗨
Hi.

142
00:15:57,910 --> 00:15:59,750
这些都是你画的
Are all these paintings yours?

143
00:15:59,910 --> 00:16:03,670
- 是的 喜欢吗 - 很棒
- Yes. Do you like them? - They're remarkable.

144
00:16:04,420 --> 00:16:05,840
谢谢
Thank you.

145
00:16:06,000 --> 00:16:08,840
我叫艾斯特 你呢
My name is Esther. What's yours?

146
00:16:09,420 --> 00:16:11,930
约翰 很高兴认识你
John. Nice to meet you.

147
00:16:13,300 --> 00:16:15,890
- 我能坐下来吗 - 当然
- Can I take a seat? - Of course.

148
00:16:17,760 --> 00:16:20,890
看孩子们欢聚一堂 永不会感到厌烦
I never get tired of watching these kids enjoy the party.

149
00:16:21,060 --> 00:16:23,560
的确 真后悔之前我们还犹豫不决
It really is. I'm so sorry we didn't do this sooner.

150
00:16:23,730 --> 00:16:25,560
怎么会 这可是重大决定
Don't be. It's a big leap.

151
00:16:25,730 --> 00:16:29,900
决定领养一个孩子 可不是件容易的事
Adopting an older child is not an easy decision to make.

152
00:16:31,450 --> 00:16:32,610
约翰去卫生间了
John's in the bathroom.

153
00:16:32,780 --> 00:16:35,160
他会找到我们吗 想去找找他吗
Think he'll find us? Do you wanna go look for him?

154
00:16:35,320 --> 00:16:38,000
这个灵感是从哪儿来的
Where did you get the idea for this one?

155
00:16:38,000 --> 00:16:40,160
我的画都是有故事的
My paintings always tell stories.

156
00:16:40,330 --> 00:16:43,670
这幅讲的是找不到幼狮的悲伤母狮
This one's about a sad mother lion who can't find her cubs.

157
00:16:43,830 --> 00:16:47,250
- 她在笑 - 她梦见了她的孩子
- She's smiling. - She's dreaming about her babies.

158
00:16:47,750 --> 00:16:49,710
这是唯一能让她高兴的事
It's the only thing that makes her happy.

159
00:16:49,880 --> 00:16:54,260
- 真希望她能找到孩子们 - 她会的 看
- I hope she finds them. - She will. Look.

160
00:16:57,470 --> 00:17:00,680
他们在森林里迷路了 他们很害怕…-
They were lost in the jungle, and they were so scared...

161
00:17:00,850 --> 00:17:02,980
因为妈妈不在身边
...because they didn't have a mother.

162
00:17:03,140 --> 00:17:05,560
就在他们以为将孤独一辈子时…
Just when they thought they'd be alone forever...

163
00:17:05,730 --> 00:17:09,360
他们发现妈妈就在树下睡觉
...they found their mother asleep under this tree.

164
00:17:09,530 --> 00:17:13,030
她醒来的时候 梦想就成真了
Now when she wakes up, her dream will have come true.

165
00:17:13,200 --> 00:17:14,790
母子团聚
She'll have her family again.

166
00:17:14,790 --> 00:17:16,740
真让人吃惊 你想出来的
Amazing. You came up with that story?

167
00:17:16,910 --> 00:17:19,410
- 我好像听到他的声音了 - 对
- I think I hear his voice down here. - Yes.

168
00:17:20,700 --> 00:17:24,210
嘿 我来介绍 这是我妻子 凯特
Hey. I want to introduce you. This is my wife, Kate.

169
00:17:24,370 --> 00:17:25,750
凯特 这是艾斯特
Kate, this is Esther.

170
00:17:27,170 --> 00:17:28,540
你好
Hello.

171
00:17:30,550 --> 00:17:33,380
你好吗 很高兴认识你
How are you? Nice to meet you.

172
00:17:34,420 --> 00:17:36,680
这些都是她画得
She painted all these.

173
00:17:36,840 --> 00:17:37,890
- 真的 - 是的
- Really? - Yeah.

174
00:17:38,050 --> 00:17:40,810
了不起呀 真是太棒了
These are fantastic. These are really wonderful.

175
00:17:40,970 --> 00:17:43,350
- 谢谢 - 你在哪儿学的
- Thank you. - Where did you learn how to do this?

176
00:17:43,520 --> 00:17:46,730
大概是因为我有大量的练习时间吧
I've just had lots of time to practice, I guess.

177
00:17:46,900 --> 00:17:49,690
这里真的有些无聊了
It's really boring here.

178
00:17:49,860 --> 00:17:51,860
这里无聊
It's boring here?

179
00:17:52,030 --> 00:17:54,700
如果你觉得无聊 为什么不参加派对呢
If you're so bored, why aren't you down at the party?

180
00:17:54,860 --> 00:17:57,360
毫无意义
I've never really seen the point of it.

181
00:17:57,360 --> 00:17:59,530
以前都没人搭理我
Nobody's ever talked to me before.

182
00:18:00,490 --> 00:18:01,580
可能我有些与众不同吧
I guess I'm different.

183
00:18:01,740 --> 00:18:03,950
与众不同也没什么不好
There's nothing wrong with being different.

184
00:18:04,120 --> 00:18:06,080
你俩倒是有很多共同点
Well, you two have a lot in common.

185
00:18:10,670 --> 00:18:12,590
我想人们会常说
I think people should always...

186
00:18:12,750 --> 00:18:15,220
过去的就让它过去…
...try to take the bad things that happen to them...

187
00:18:15,380 --> 00:18:17,760
努力创造美好的未来
...and turn them into something good.

188
00:18:17,930 --> 00:18:20,720
- 不是吗 - 是的
- Don't you? - Yeah.

189
00:18:20,890 --> 00:18:22,810
当然了
Absolutely.

190
00:18:29,480 --> 00:18:30,890
她原籍是俄罗斯
She's originally from Russia,

191
00:18:30,890 --> 00:18:32,980
但她英语出奇的好
but it's amazing how strong her English is.

192
00:18:33,150 --> 00:18:35,440
她来美国才几年时间
She's only been in the country a few years.

193
00:18:35,610 --> 00:18:37,650
你们收留其他国家的孩子
You get children from other countries?

194
00:18:37,820 --> 00:18:39,490
很少 一旦收留了
It's rare. But when we do,

195
00:18:39,490 --> 00:18:41,990
安置工作会比较麻烦
it's sometimes difficult to place them.

196
00:18:42,530 --> 00:18:46,330
和她一起来美国的家人死于火灾
The family that brought her to America died in a house fire.

197
00:18:46,500 --> 00:18:47,910
火灾
In a fire?

198
00:18:48,080 --> 00:18:49,500
上帝呀
My God.

199
00:18:49,670 --> 00:18:51,210
艾斯特刚好外出了
Esther barely got out.

200
00:18:51,960 --> 00:18:53,680
她经历了很多事
She's been through a lot,

201
00:18:53,680 --> 00:18:56,510
但她是个特别的小女孩
but this is an extraordinary little girl.

202
00:18:56,670 --> 00:18:59,640
她聪明伶俐 有着超出年龄的成熟
She's very bright. She's very mature for her age.

203
00:18:59,800 --> 00:19:01,640
彬彬有礼
And she's very well- mannered.

204
00:19:01,640 --> 00:19:03,930
倒有点像个公主
She's a bit of a princess, actually.

205
00:19:04,100 --> 00:19:07,890
在手腕和脖子上 总是戴着那些丝带
She wears those ribbons on her wrists and her neck all the time.

206
00:19:08,560 --> 00:19:09,600
我也是
Mine too.

207
00:19:09,770 --> 00:19:12,560
我们想给她取下来 但她不干
We had trouble with her when we tried to take them off.

208
00:19:12,730 --> 00:19:14,570
她和其他孩子相处的如何
How does she get along with other kids?

209
00:19:14,730 --> 00:19:16,990
需要和其他孩子互动时 她也做得很好
Oh, when she has to interact, she's great.

210
00:19:17,150 --> 00:19:19,280
亲爱的
Babe?

211
00:19:19,450 --> 00:19:22,660
- 她似乎对我们很放得开 - 对
- She really did seem to open up with us. - Yeah.

212
00:19:22,820 --> 00:19:25,620
我看她对你更放得开些
I thought she more than opened up with you.

213
00:19:25,790 --> 00:19:27,910
你们似乎沟通得很好
You seem to have made quite a connection.

214
00:19:28,080 --> 00:19:29,550
我可以把文件准备好
I could get the paperwork

215
00:19:29,550 --> 00:19:32,250
三周后你们再来吧
together and see you back here in three weeks.

216
00:19:38,550 --> 00:19:40,260
好的
All right.

217
00:19:50,140 --> 00:19:51,230
好的
Okey- dokey.

218
00:19:51,400 --> 00:19:53,440
有什么需要就给我电话吧
Call me if you need anything.

219
00:19:53,610 --> 00:19:55,360
再见 好的 谢谢你
Bye. Okay, thank you.

220
00:20:15,040 --> 00:20:17,550
那是T H
Oh, that's T- H.

221
00:20:17,710 --> 00:20:20,340
T H 对
T- H. Yeah.

222
00:20:20,510 --> 00:20:22,630
"麦克斯"是像这样吗
And "Max" Is like this?

223
00:20:22,800 --> 00:20:23,840
对
Yeah.

224
00:20:25,140 --> 00:20:26,720
很好
Good.

225
00:20:31,060 --> 00:20:35,440
- 那是你们的房子吗 - 现在也是你的了
- Is this your house? - Now it's your house too.

226
00:20:51,870 --> 00:20:55,750
嗨 甜心 嗨 看谁来了
Hi, sweetie. Hi. Look who's here.

227
00:21:00,800 --> 00:21:04,720
你好麦克斯 我的名字是艾斯特
Hello, Max. My name is Esther.

228
00:21:05,300 --> 00:21:07,640
她路上一直在练习
She's been practicing the whole way.

229
00:21:09,770 --> 00:21:11,810
- 她能听见吗 - 一点点
- Can she hear? - A little.

230
00:21:11,980 --> 00:21:13,770
她先天性失聪
She was born almost completely deaf.

231
00:21:13,940 --> 00:21:17,150
那个只是辅助她读唇语的
That just allows her to hear enough to read lips.

232
00:21:20,690 --> 00:21:23,200
没事的 我都拿上了
That's all right, I got it.

233
00:21:27,570 --> 00:21:30,040
这位是芭芭拉奶奶
I'd like to introduce you to Grandma Barbara.

234
00:21:30,200 --> 00:21:32,870
很高兴见到你
It's a pleasure to meet you.

235
00:21:33,040 --> 00:21:36,040
真可爱 我也很高兴见到你
That's precious. It's a pleasure to meet you too.

236
00:21:37,790 --> 00:21:39,710
丹尼
Danny.

237
00:21:39,880 --> 00:21:42,050
这是艾斯特
This is Esther.

238
00:21:44,170 --> 00:21:45,380
你好 丹尼尔
Hello, Daniel.

239
00:21:46,550 --> 00:21:48,300
嘿
Hey.

240
00:21:51,930 --> 00:21:53,810
为什么她穿成那样
Why does she dress like that?

241
00:21:53,980 --> 00:21:57,150
- 行了 别那样 - 问问而已
- Come on. Stop it. - I'm just asking a question.

242
00:21:57,310 --> 00:21:59,230
啊
Oh!

243
00:21:59,980 --> 00:22:02,980
- 你们有钢琴 - 对
- You have a piano? - Yeah.

244
00:22:03,150 --> 00:22:06,280
- 想学弹琴吗 - 很想学
- Would you like to learn how to play? - I would love to.

245
00:22:15,540 --> 00:22:16,580
喜欢吗
Do you like it?

246
00:22:16,750 --> 00:22:18,920
- 太完美了 - 那就好
- It's perfect. - Good.

247
00:22:26,420 --> 00:22:27,680
谢谢
Thank you.

248
00:22:27,840 --> 00:22:29,720
"谢谢"的手语怎么做
How do you say "Thank you"?

249
00:22:30,220 --> 00:22:31,680
谢谢
Thank you.

250
00:22:33,510 --> 00:22:35,170
不客气

251
00:22:41,150 --> 00:22:43,900
哇 看啊
Wow, look at that.

252
00:22:44,070 --> 00:22:47,070
怎么了 怎么了 怎么了
What? What? What?

253
00:22:47,240 --> 00:22:48,490
爸 看
Dad, look.

254
00:22:48,660 --> 00:22:50,200
- 爸 - 你在哪儿找到的
- Dad. - Where did you get that?

255
00:22:50,370 --> 00:22:53,370
- 爸 看 我正要击败特雷弗 - 真棒
- Dad, look, I'm killing Trevor. - Great.

256
00:22:53,540 --> 00:22:55,040
爽
Yes.

257
00:22:58,040 --> 00:22:59,330
谢谢
Thank you.

258
00:22:59,500 --> 00:23:01,960
快 爸 我的独奏快结束了 快看呀
Come on, Dad. My solo's gonna end. Hurry, look.

259
00:23:03,500 --> 00:23:05,460
哇 真酷
Wow, cool.

260
00:23:10,300 --> 00:23:12,970
- 特雷弗 你真逊 - 闭嘴
- Trevor, you suck. - Shut up.

261
00:23:14,510 --> 00:23:16,930
真是太棒了
That's fabulous.

262
00:23:17,560 --> 00:23:20,480
走吧 伙计们 太无趣了
Come on, guys. This is lame.

263
00:23:20,650 --> 00:23:22,900
我正要痛扁你
I was just about to beat you.

264
00:23:23,860 --> 00:23:26,190
你喜欢 我就高兴了 宝贝
I'm glad you like it, honey.

265
00:23:43,460 --> 00:23:44,710
快来 伙计们
Come on, guys.

266
00:23:50,220 --> 00:23:52,550
快 冻死我了
Hurry up, I'm freezing my ass off.

267
00:23:52,720 --> 00:23:57,470
- 兄弟 都在这里了 - 上帝呀 手冻僵了
- Dude, it's all in here. - Oh, God. My hands are freezing.

268
00:23:58,270 --> 00:23:59,730
呀 真性感呀
Oh, man, she's hot.

269
00:24:00,230 --> 00:24:03,230
- 让开 伙计 - 三十四页会爽翻你
- Move over, man. - Page 34 will change your life.

270
00:24:04,650 --> 00:24:06,440
哇啊
Whoa.

271
00:24:07,190 --> 00:24:08,900
看起来像你老母
This looks like your morn.

272
00:24:11,320 --> 00:24:12,660
不
No.

273
00:24:17,330 --> 00:24:19,620
艾斯特和玛克辛 看来相处得不错
Esther and Maxine seem to be getting along well.

274
00:24:19,790 --> 00:24:21,000
是呀
Yeah.

275
00:24:21,160 --> 00:24:22,870
她怎么样了 凯特
How's she doing, Kate?

276
00:24:23,040 --> 00:24:25,380
艾斯特正在融入进来
Esther's fitting right in.

277
00:24:25,540 --> 00:24:27,170
我是说玛克辛
I meant Maxine.

278
00:24:27,340 --> 00:24:29,970
她在池塘边玩耍 就像什么也没发生过一样
She's playing by the pond like nothing ever happened.

279
00:24:30,130 --> 00:24:31,800
她记不得了 对吧
She doesn't remember, does she?

280
00:24:31,970 --> 00:24:34,390
嗯 她没事
No. She's fine.

281
00:24:39,270 --> 00:24:42,940
那你有什么打算
So, what are your plans?

282
00:24:43,100 --> 00:24:46,150
让艾斯特先安顿好…
You know, probably get Esther settled...

283
00:24:46,980 --> 00:24:48,940
然后回去教书
...then go back to teaching.

284
00:24:49,110 --> 00:24:51,070
他们好像不打算让你回去了
Thought they weren't gonna take you back.

285
00:24:51,240 --> 00:24:52,740
不 我不是说耶鲁
No, I'm not talking about Yale.

286
00:24:52,900 --> 00:24:55,990
我是说 我可能在家里授课
I'll just... I'll probably give lessons from home.

287
00:24:56,160 --> 00:24:58,540
那可太糟了 多好的工作啊
That's too bad. That was a very good job.

288
00:24:58,700 --> 00:25:00,660
又不是我想辞职的
Well, I didn't quit because I wanted to.

289
00:25:00,830 --> 00:25:04,000
我知道 你当时需要戒除酒瘾
I know. You had to have your moment of clarity.

290
00:25:04,170 --> 00:25:06,710
又要提戒酒互助课程
That is an A.A. Term.

291
00:25:07,460 --> 00:25:09,750
而我没去参加戒酒互助会 一样停止了酗酒
And I didn't go to A.A. I just stopped drinking.

292
00:25:09,920 --> 00:25:13,510
大同小异 有时候我们都需要个醒钟
Same difference. We all need a wake-up call sometimes.

293
00:26:20,660 --> 00:26:22,240
嗨
Hi.

294
00:26:23,160 --> 00:26:26,250
- 嗨 - 过来
- Hi. - Come here.

295
00:26:44,350 --> 00:26:46,020
怎么了
Yeah?

296
00:26:47,770 --> 00:26:51,060
- 哦 嘿 - 我们被闪电吓到了
- Oh, hey. - We're scared of the lightning.

297
00:26:51,230 --> 00:26:52,940
快进来
Oh, come in.

298
00:26:53,730 --> 00:26:58,740
- 我想睡爸爸旁边 - 等一下
- I wanna sleep next to Daddy. - Hang on.

299
00:26:59,990 --> 00:27:01,780
好的
Okay.

300
00:27:10,710 --> 00:27:13,090
我待会儿打电话 看看是否一切都好
I'm gonna call later, make sure everything's okay.

301
00:27:13,250 --> 00:27:15,460
好 他们会喜欢你的设计的
Okay. They're gonna love your design.

302
00:27:15,630 --> 00:27:17,510
- 记得接我电话哦 - 嗯
- You gonna pick up the phone? - Yeah.

303
00:27:17,670 --> 00:27:19,260
好的
All right.

304
00:27:20,140 --> 00:27:21,970
艾斯特
Esther?

305
00:27:22,140 --> 00:27:23,850
艾斯特
Esther?

306
00:27:24,010 --> 00:27:25,720
快点
Come on.

307
00:27:25,890 --> 00:27:29,350
艾斯特 快点 要走啦
Esther, come on, we gotta go!

308
00:27:29,520 --> 00:27:32,810
我没看错吧
You gotta be kidding me.

309
00:27:33,110 --> 00:27:36,320
哇噢…
WOW. Uh...

310
00:27:37,110 --> 00:27:39,400
- 你们先上车好吗 - 走吧
- Will you please go wait in the car? - Come on.

311
00:27:43,280 --> 00:27:45,910
亲爱的 这可不是学生装
Sweetheart, this isn't really a school dress.

312
00:27:46,080 --> 00:27:48,620
但我喜欢啊 难道不漂亮吗
But I like it. Don't you think it's pretty?

313
00:27:48,790 --> 00:27:50,420
不错 确实很漂亮…
Yes, it's so beautiful...

314
00:27:50,580 --> 00:27:53,670
但穿起来也许不够舒适
...but I just don't think you're gonna be comfortable in it.

315
00:27:53,840 --> 00:27:54,960
你的牛仔裤呢
What about those jeans?

316
00:27:55,130 --> 00:27:58,010
你是担心其他孩子会笑话我吧
You're afraid the other children will laugh at me.

317
00:27:58,170 --> 00:27:59,770
我记得你说过
I thought you said there

318
00:27:59,770 --> 00:28:02,640
与众不同不是错
wasn't anything wrong with being different.

319
00:28:04,010 --> 00:28:06,350
是的 说过 我是说过
Yes, you're right. You're absolutely right.

320
00:28:06,510 --> 00:28:09,230
好吧 开心点
Okay. Have fun.

321
00:28:10,690 --> 00:28:13,270
请坐下 坐下
Take a seat, please. Take a seat.

322
00:28:13,440 --> 00:28:15,610
别让我说第二遍
Don't make me ask again, please.

323
00:28:16,520 --> 00:28:19,610
我们来了位新同学 名字叫艾斯特·科尔曼
Okay, this is our new student. Her name's Esther Coleman.

324
00:28:19,780 --> 00:28:22,910
希望大家能热情的欢迎她
And I'd like you all to make her feel very welcome today.

325
00:28:23,070 --> 00:28:26,490
噢 看啊 小牧羊女来短信了 她想要回她的衣服
Oh, look. Little Bo Peep texted me. She wants her outfit back.

326
00:28:30,210 --> 00:28:31,920
好吧 去找个位子
Okay, go take a seat.

327
00:28:33,750 --> 00:28:36,630
好吧 大家把书翻到27页…
Okay, if everybody could turn to Page 27...

328
00:28:41,510 --> 00:28:42,590
不
No!

329
00:28:42,760 --> 00:28:45,010
不 艾斯特 你在干嘛
No! Esther, what are you doing?

330
00:28:45,180 --> 00:28:48,010
快出来 出来
Get away from there! No!

331
00:28:48,180 --> 00:28:52,060
不准在冰上玩 告诉过你的
You don't play near the water! You know that!

332
00:28:52,230 --> 00:28:53,520
快点 出来
Come on, get out!

333
00:28:55,100 --> 00:28:56,770
麦克斯
Max.

334
00:29:14,120 --> 00:29:16,790
真棒 真准
Sweet. Bull's- eye.

335
00:29:18,250 --> 00:29:19,380
太准了
Got you.

336
00:29:52,910 --> 00:29:56,250
- 你开的枪 - 我没想到威力会这么大
- Did you kill it? - I didn't think it would hurt him.

337
00:30:05,970 --> 00:30:07,430
帮它解脱了
Put it out of its misery.

338
00:30:09,100 --> 00:30:11,940
它的痛苦 是你带来的
It's in pain, and it's your responsibility.

339
00:30:11,940 --> 00:30:13,560
这是个意外
It was just an accident.

340
00:30:13,730 --> 00:30:16,060
你现在走掉 它也会活活饿死
If you walk away now, it'll starve to death.

341
00:30:16,230 --> 00:30:17,770
难道你想这样
Is that what you want?

342
00:30:22,820 --> 00:30:24,820
我做不来
I'm not doing it.

343
00:30:30,830 --> 00:30:32,740
结束了
It's all right.

344
00:30:32,910 --> 00:30:35,620
- 它现在去天堂了 - 你有病吗
- It's in heaven now. - What's wrong with you?

345
00:30:43,460 --> 00:30:45,720
- 水够热吗 - 是的 谢谢
- Is the water warm enough? - Yes, thank you.

346
00:30:45,880 --> 00:30:48,090
那洗吧 有事就叫我
Okay. Call me if you need anything.

347
00:31:06,110 --> 00:31:07,900
艾斯特
Esther?

348
00:31:08,740 --> 00:31:10,660
艾斯特
Esther.

349
00:31:11,370 --> 00:31:12,830
这门得开着
Open this door.

350
00:31:16,750 --> 00:31:19,330
- 你在干嘛 - 我向来都锁门的
- What are you doing? - I always lock the door.

351
00:31:19,500 --> 00:31:21,330
但我们家都不会锁
No, we don't look doors in this house.

352
00:31:21,500 --> 00:31:23,590
那有人进来看见我怎么办
But what if someone comes in and sees me?

353
00:31:24,380 --> 00:31:25,510
没人会进来
Nobody's gonna come in.

354
00:31:25,670 --> 00:31:28,720
有必要的话 我就站在这等你
Look, I'm gonna stand right here, if that's what you want.

355
00:31:28,880 --> 00:31:30,430
那我唱歌给你听
I could sing for you.

356
00:31:30,590 --> 00:31:32,060
我以前常唱给修女听
I used to sing for the

357
00:31:32,060 --> 00:31:34,930
好让她们知道我没事
sisters so they would know I was all right.

358
00:31:37,430 --> 00:31:39,190
好吧
Okay.

359
00:31:39,690 --> 00:31:43,150
好吧 但是下不为例
All right. But you know what? This is just for tonight.

360
00:33:28,880 --> 00:33:32,720
你父母肯定费尽千辛万苦 才挑出了她
Your parents must have gone to a lot of retard camps to find her.

361
00:33:34,590 --> 00:33:36,220
看着路
Watch it.

362
00:33:37,600 --> 00:33:39,180
你没事吧
Are you okay?

363
00:33:44,770 --> 00:33:46,350
这是《圣经》吗
Is this a Bible?

364
00:33:48,400 --> 00:33:52,070
怪物今天带了本《圣经》来学校
Jesus Freak brought a Bible to school today.

365
00:33:56,780 --> 00:33:58,160
嘿 要一起来吗
Hey, wanna come over?

366
00:34:04,290 --> 00:34:06,920
- 很不错 - 你姐姐确实是个怪物
- Good one. - Your sister's a total spaz.

367
00:34:07,080 --> 00:34:08,580
她不是我姐姐
She's not my sister.

368
00:34:10,880 --> 00:34:12,670
你居然真的这样做了
I can't believe you did that.

369
00:34:12,840 --> 00:34:16,550
噢 狗狗 你戴的是项圈吗 小狗狗
Oh, little doggy. Is this your collar, little doggy?

370
00:34:32,400 --> 00:34:36,490
不是A 是AB
Not A. A, B.

371
00:34:42,660 --> 00:34:44,250
弹得非常好
You did really good.

372
00:34:44,410 --> 00:34:48,460
没有 不算好 弹错了11处
No, I didn't. I made like 11 mistakes.

373
00:34:49,830 --> 00:34:51,380
但下次我会更努力
I'll do better next time.

374
00:34:52,090 --> 00:34:54,960
老师把今天的事跟我说了
Your teacher told me what happened today.

375
00:34:56,590 --> 00:34:59,140
不想谈谈吗
Don't you want to talk about it?

376
00:34:59,300 --> 00:35:01,510
没什么好谈的
There's nothing to talk about.

377
00:35:02,100 --> 00:35:05,020
我会一直守护你的 你知道的吧
You know I'm here for you, right? You know that, right?

378
00:35:06,230 --> 00:35:09,020
有个东西要给你看看
I got something I wanna show you.

379
00:35:13,690 --> 00:35:15,990
我有个同样的小本用来写日记
I have one just like this that I use as a diary.

380
00:35:16,150 --> 00:35:20,030
而你呢 可以用这个…
And I thought that maybe you and I could use this one...

381
00:35:20,200 --> 00:35:21,820
做个剪贴薄
...for a scrapbook.

382
00:35:23,200 --> 00:35:25,700
这是爸妈在结婚那天照的
That's Mommy and Daddy on their wedding day.

383
00:35:27,080 --> 00:35:29,540
丹尼尔 摄于圣诞节早晨
That's Daniel, Christmas morning.

384
00:35:30,750 --> 00:35:32,670
小家伙 麦克斯
Here's Max.

385
00:35:35,380 --> 00:35:36,630
接着就是你
And there's you.

386
00:35:42,220 --> 00:35:44,260
杰西卡是谁
Who's Jessica?

387
00:35:45,510 --> 00:35:48,230
麦克斯提起过她
Max talks about her.

388
00:35:49,060 --> 00:35:52,060
我虽未曾拥有 但我早已感受
"I never held you, but I feel you.

389
00:35:52,230 --> 00:35:55,980
你还未曾笑语 而我却已聆取
You never spoke, but I hear you.

390
00:35:57,360 --> 00:36:02,160
即使命运让我们别离 但爱你如一
I never knew you, but I love you."

391
00:36:07,500 --> 00:36:09,120
她怎么了
What happened to her?

392
00:36:11,960 --> 00:36:14,540
她在我肚子里夭折了
She died while she was still in my tummy.

393
00:36:15,630 --> 00:36:17,800
我们把她的骨灰撒在这儿
But we scattered her ashes here.

394
00:36:18,380 --> 00:36:21,800
当这些花朵盛开的时候…
And as long as this plant grows...

395
00:36:21,970 --> 00:36:26,680
她就会与她们一同欢笑
...then part of her will be alive inside it.

396
00:36:34,690 --> 00:36:37,360
她本来会很幸福
She would have been lucky.

397
00:36:37,530 --> 00:36:39,360
因为你是最好的妈妈
You're a great mommy.

398
00:36:46,030 --> 00:36:47,620
谢谢你 宝贝
Thank you, sweetheart.

399
00:36:47,790 --> 00:36:50,540
谢谢你 我很欣慰
Thank you. It means a lot.

400
00:36:54,500 --> 00:36:57,170
- 你还好吗 - 不错啊
- How are you? - I'm good.

401
00:36:57,340 --> 00:37:01,670
很有趣 艾斯特今天敞开心扉了
It's very interesting. Esther started to open up today.

402
00:37:01,840 --> 00:37:03,050
是很有趣
That's very interesting.

403
00:37:03,220 --> 00:37:05,720
我有点感觉她像是我亲生的了
I'm starting to feel like there's a real connection.

404
00:37:05,890 --> 00:37:07,930
我也是
Me too.

405
00:37:10,810 --> 00:37:12,940
- 别 亲爱的 别在这嘛 - 嘘
- No, honey, not here. - Shh.

406
00:37:13,100 --> 00:37:14,600
他们睡着了
They're sleeping.

407
00:37:14,770 --> 00:37:18,650
宝贝 来吧 你会喜欢的
Baby, come here, you'll like it, believe me.

408
00:37:25,200 --> 00:37:27,450
- 好吧 切入正题 - 不 不 不
- Okay, let's get down to business. - No, no, no.

409
00:37:27,620 --> 00:37:30,660
那就 再多加点前戏
Okay, just for a second, then.

410
00:37:30,830 --> 00:37:32,460
哈哈
Yeah.

411
00:37:41,800 --> 00:37:43,380
- 不 不行 - 来嘛
- No, no, no. - Come on.

412
00:37:43,550 --> 00:37:46,840
我必须去… 等下 等等嘛
I have to. Wait, wait, wait.

413
00:37:54,440 --> 00:37:56,270
耶
Yeah.

414
00:38:23,300 --> 00:38:25,300
- 喔 噢 - 对不起
- Ow! - Oh, sorry.

415
00:38:40,360 --> 00:38:43,190
噢 天啊
Oh, Jesus.

416
00:38:43,820 --> 00:38:46,990
天啊 亲爱的 妈的
Jesus, honey. Damn it.

417
00:38:52,910 --> 00:38:54,580
艾斯特
Esther?

418
00:38:56,000 --> 00:38:58,330
我们得谈谈昨晚的事
We have to talk about last night.

419
00:38:58,500 --> 00:39:01,340
- 有必要吗 - 有的
- Do we? - Yes, we do.

420
00:39:03,800 --> 00:39:06,550
本来有些大人的事…
See, there are certain things that grown- ups do...

421
00:39:06,720 --> 00:39:09,800
是不该让小孩子看见的
...that children aren't supposed to see.

422
00:39:09,970 --> 00:39:14,010
比如…昨晚的事
And that was one of them.

423
00:39:18,230 --> 00:39:20,400
艾斯特 听我说
Esther, listen to me.

424
00:39:24,730 --> 00:39:27,900
当大人们非常非常爱恋对方时…
When grown- ups love each other very, very much...

425
00:39:29,150 --> 00:39:31,870
他们希望能让对方感受到爱意
...they wanna show each other that love. Express it.

426
00:39:32,030 --> 00:39:33,330
我懂 叫"操"
I know. They fuck.

427
00:39:37,580 --> 00:39:40,290
这词哪都会出现 比如学校里
She could've picked it up anywhere. Probably at school.

428
00:39:40,460 --> 00:39:42,450
她可不是骂脏话
This wasn't something she overheard.

429
00:39:42,450 --> 00:39:44,170
她就指的那事
I mean, she knew what it meant.

430
00:39:44,340 --> 00:39:45,550
呵
Huh.

431
00:39:45,710 --> 00:39:47,880
而且 她当时说话的样子…
And, babe, the way she said it is...

432
00:39:48,050 --> 00:39:51,890
完全不当回事
I don't even think she expected to get in trouble over it.

433
00:39:53,050 --> 00:39:56,640
好吧 晚上我们一起谈谈
Well, we'll talk to her about it tonight.

434
00:39:58,020 --> 00:39:59,600
好吧
Fine.

435
00:39:59,770 --> 00:40:01,810
那你有什么打算
Well, what did you have in mind?

436
00:40:02,480 --> 00:40:05,440
呃 带她去见见布朗宁医生
No, I thought we could take her to Dr. Browning.

437
00:40:06,190 --> 00:40:09,070
她还不至于看心理医生吧
I don't think we need to take her to the shrink quite yet.

438
00:40:09,240 --> 00:40:12,700
要知道 我们并不是很了解她
Well, you know, we just don't know that much about her.

439
00:40:12,870 --> 00:40:15,240
她以前的家人有可能是那种
The family she stayed with could've been like:

440
00:40:15,410 --> 00:40:19,370
张嘴闭嘴就"操你妈的" 对不对
"Pass the fucking potatoes" At dinnertime, you know?

441
00:40:19,540 --> 00:40:21,000
她当着我的面都敢说
If she's saying it to my face,

442
00:40:21,000 --> 00:40:22,960
那背着我们的时候呢
what is she saying when we're not there?

443
00:40:23,130 --> 00:40:26,250
我可不想她把麦克斯给带坏了
I don't want her exerting that kind of influence over Max.

444
00:40:27,420 --> 00:40:29,480
我只是不想
Anyway, I just don't want to

445
00:40:29,490 --> 00:40:32,800
为句脏话而兴师动众
make a big deal out of one little dirty word.

446
00:40:33,840 --> 00:40:37,060
好吧 那他妈的多陪陪她
Fine. Fucking spend some time with her, then.

447
00:40:37,220 --> 00:40:38,430
好的 臭婆娘
All right, bitch.

448
00:40:42,810 --> 00:40:45,230
来打雪仗吧
Let's have a snow fight!

449
00:40:46,110 --> 00:40:48,690
好了 不准扔雪球
Come on, no throwing snowballs.

450
00:40:59,240 --> 00:41:00,290
你好啊 邻居
Hey, neighbor.

451
00:41:02,370 --> 00:41:05,750
好啊 最近都见不到你
- Hey. - Haven't seen you around lately.

452
00:41:05,920 --> 00:41:07,750
这几天太忙了
I've been pretty busy.

453
00:41:07,920 --> 00:41:11,010
我不在的时候其他户主还是常聚会吗
Has the homeowners' association been soldiering on without me?

454
00:41:11,170 --> 00:41:13,090
但有你会不一样
It's not the same.

455
00:41:25,770 --> 00:41:29,150
呃 实际上 我想请你帮个忙
Um, actually, I had a favor to ask.

456
00:41:29,320 --> 00:41:32,070
我有张大椅子要搬到楼上去…
I have a chair that I need moved upstairs...

457
00:41:32,240 --> 00:41:33,940
不知你能否
...and I was hoping you

458
00:41:33,940 --> 00:41:37,280
抽空过来帮下我
could come by and help me with that sometime.

459
00:41:38,080 --> 00:41:39,540
行
Yeah.

460
00:41:39,700 --> 00:41:41,500
- 行 没问题 - 谢谢
- Yeah, sure. - Good.

461
00:41:41,660 --> 00:41:44,620
凯特和我说不定能帮上忙 告诉我们一声就行
Maybe Kate and I could help you out. Just let us know.

462
00:41:44,790 --> 00:41:46,420
那到时候叫你
I'll call you.

463
00:41:46,580 --> 00:41:48,500
走吧 宝贝
Let's go, honey.

464
00:41:50,840 --> 00:41:53,420
好的 我来看着你
Okay, I'm watching you.

465
00:44:07,020 --> 00:44:11,190
布伦达爸爸说是你推的她
Brenda's father says that you pushed her.

466
00:44:11,350 --> 00:44:12,860
不是的
That's not true.

467
00:44:13,020 --> 00:44:14,520
我们只是在玩
We were just playing.

468
00:44:14,690 --> 00:44:16,860
我发誓
I swear.

469
00:44:18,190 --> 00:44:20,450
- 好吧 - 你知道怎么回事吗
- Okay. - And did you see what happened?

470
00:44:22,020 --> 00:44:23,710
她滑倒了

471
00:44:55,190 --> 00:44:57,440
什么 妈妈 她说的什么
What? Mom, what's she saying?

472
00:44:57,610 --> 00:45:00,240
她要你把面包和黄油递给她
She wants you to pass the bread and butter.

473
00:45:02,150 --> 00:45:04,820
- 又没问你 - 嘿 别吵架哈
- Wasn't asking you. - Hey, now.

474
00:45:14,830 --> 00:45:16,880
你就不能正常的吃饭吗
Can you eat normal?

475
00:45:18,050 --> 00:45:19,550
正常人就像我这样吃饭
I am eating normal.

476
00:45:19,710 --> 00:45:21,380
估计只在你以前住的特兰西瓦尼亚
Yeah, maybe in Transylvania,

477
00:45:21,380 --> 00:45:22,720
或是其他国家才算正常吧
or whatever country you're from.

478
00:45:22,880 --> 00:45:24,930
那我顺便说一声 我来自俄罗斯
Incidentally, I'm from Russia.

479
00:45:25,090 --> 00:45:29,560
而且特兰西瓦尼亚不是个国家 早并入罗马尼亚了
Transylvania isn't even a country. It's a part of Romania.

480
00:45:29,720 --> 00:45:31,100
你真是个变态
You are such a freak.

481
00:45:31,270 --> 00:45:33,140
- 嘿 - 嘿 丹尼
- Hey. - Hey, Danny.

482
00:45:33,310 --> 00:45:35,150
不准再说这事了 明白吗
I don't want any more talk like that.

483
00:45:35,310 --> 00:45:37,770
她非得那个样子吗
But why does she have to act like that?

484
00:45:37,940 --> 00:45:40,110
我朋友全都因为她而取笑我
All my friends make fun of me because of her.

485
00:45:40,280 --> 00:45:42,030
那也许你该换朋友了
Maybe you need different friends.

486
00:45:42,190 --> 00:45:45,160
又也许你该把她送回孤儿院了
Maybe you should send her back to the retard camp.

487
00:45:45,320 --> 00:45:46,950
- 丹尼尔 - 丹尼尔
- Daniel. - Daniel.

488
00:45:47,120 --> 00:45:48,660
向你姐姐道歉
Apologize to your sister.

489
00:45:48,830 --> 00:45:52,540
她不是我该死的姐姐
She's not my fucking sister.

490
00:45:55,210 --> 00:45:56,500
我明白了
I got it.

491
00:45:58,630 --> 00:46:00,340
明白了
Okay.

492
00:46:02,880 --> 00:46:03,920
让我来管
That's me.

493
00:46:21,980 --> 00:46:24,240
道完歉才还你钥匙
You get the key back when you say you're sorry.

494
00:46:30,620 --> 00:46:33,660
今晚想吃点什么特别的吗
Is there anything special you want me to make tonight?

495
00:46:33,830 --> 00:46:35,330
有没有什么特别爱吃的
You have any favorites?

496
00:46:39,290 --> 00:46:40,590
喂
Hello.

497
00:46:40,750 --> 00:46:44,130
- 你们好吗 - 嗨 我们很开心 过的很好
- Well, how are you? - Hi, we're great. We're doing good.

498
00:46:44,300 --> 00:46:46,130
- 她怎么样 - 她就在这的 等等
- How is she? - She's here, hold on.

499
00:46:46,300 --> 00:46:49,050
嘿 是阿比盖尔修女 要打个招呼吗
Hey, Sister Abigail. Do you wanna say hello?

500
00:46:49,220 --> 00:46:53,220
- 快点 艾斯特 随便打个招呼 - 我说了 不打
- Come on. Esther, just quickly say hi. - I said, no.

501
00:46:56,850 --> 00:46:58,920
呃 宝贝
You know what, do you mind,

502
00:46:58,920 --> 00:47:01,980
能帮我挑五个苹果吗
darling, can you get five apples for me?

503
00:47:02,610 --> 00:47:05,320
对不起 她突然有点害羞
Sorry, she got shy all of a sudden.

504
00:47:05,490 --> 00:47:07,900
没事的 我打来是想告诉你…
It's all right. I'm just calling to remind you...

505
00:47:08,070 --> 00:47:10,320
我需要她的病理记录…
...that I'm gonna need her medical...

506
00:47:10,490 --> 00:47:13,200
和护牙记录来完成我的监护报告
...and dental charts for my supervision report.

507
00:47:13,550 --> 00:47:15,250
她在说啥

508
00:47:16,960 --> 00:47:18,920
她不怕看牙医
She's not thrilled about the dentist.

509
00:47:19,230 --> 00:47:21,960
在说你呢

510
00:47:23,460 --> 00:47:25,960
你们相处得如何 熟悉彼此了吗
How is everyone doing? Is she opening up to you?

511
00:47:26,130 --> 00:47:27,370
算是吧
I guess you can say that.

512
00:47:27,370 --> 00:47:29,590
几周前她还冲我吐脏话呢
She dropped the F-bomb on me a few weeks ago.

513
00:47:30,880 --> 00:47:32,540
什么是脏话

514
00:47:32,640 --> 00:47:34,350
可能她开始彻底放开了吧
I guess she's finally coming out of her shell.

515
00:47:35,930 --> 00:47:37,600
也许吧
Yeah.

516
00:47:37,770 --> 00:47:39,520
她还有犯其他错误吗
Any other glitches I should know of?

517
00:47:39,690 --> 00:47:41,230
最近出了个大事
We had a big one recently.

518
00:47:41,400 --> 00:47:43,440
是关于她同学布伦达的
It's a girl named Brenda at school.

519
00:47:43,920 --> 00:47:45,520
她们在说布伦达

520
00:47:45,780 --> 00:47:47,210
她们在玩操场的滑梯
They were at the playground,

521
00:47:47,210 --> 00:47:49,150
结果那姑娘摔下来了
there was a slide, well, she fell off.

522
00:47:49,320 --> 00:47:52,620
有人说是艾斯特推的
Esther may have pushed her down.

523
00:47:52,780 --> 00:47:55,370
但我没亲眼看到 那姑娘受伤了
I'm not getting the story straight, but she got hurt.

524
00:47:55,540 --> 00:47:56,580
严重吗
Is she all right?

525
00:47:56,750 --> 00:47:59,960
很幸运 伤了脚踝 其他地方还缝了六针
Luckily. She broke her ankle and had something like six stitches.

526
00:48:00,120 --> 00:48:01,750
那可不算幸运
That doesn't sound too lucky.

527
00:48:01,920 --> 00:48:04,250
很幸运她没摔断脖子
Well, she's lucky she didn't break her neck.

528
00:48:33,950 --> 00:48:36,660
你以前说你不会弹钢琴的
You told me you didn't know how to play.

529
00:48:36,830 --> 00:48:39,410
- 没 我没说过 - 有 你说过
- No, I didn't. - Yes, you did.

530
00:48:39,580 --> 00:48:42,500
是你想教我 我跟着学而已
You offered to teach me and I accepted.

531
00:48:42,670 --> 00:48:48,090
好吧 那你就一直假装不会弹吗
Okay. So then you were just pretending this whole time?

532
00:48:48,260 --> 00:48:50,220
我觉得你很想找个人教
I thought you would enjoy teaching me.

533
00:48:50,380 --> 00:48:51,900
对你这样热爱音乐的人来说
It must be frustrating for

534
00:48:51,900 --> 00:48:54,300
一个不懂音乐的儿子…
someone who loves music as much as you...

535
00:48:54,470 --> 00:48:55,850
和一个丧失听力的女儿
...to have a son who isn't

536
00:48:55,860 --> 00:48:58,310
肯定让你沮丧至极
interested and a daughter who can't even hear.

537
00:49:03,650 --> 00:49:05,730
等下 等等
Wait, wait, wait.

538
00:49:08,150 --> 00:49:10,780
我进屋的时候 她正熟练的弹着柴可夫斯基的曲子
I walk in on her playing Tchaikovsky without a mistake.

539
00:49:10,940 --> 00:49:13,240
那意味着她一直在骗我
I mean, she's been lying to me this whole time.

540
00:49:13,410 --> 00:49:16,280
她只是想多和你相处吧 不算欺骗
She just wants to spend time with you. It's hardly a lie.

541
00:49:16,450 --> 00:49:17,490
你不了解
You wouldn't know.

542
00:49:17,660 --> 00:49:20,250
她在你面前一直都很乖
You wouldn't. She's on her best behavior with you.

543
00:49:20,410 --> 00:49:23,500
而在我面前却好似另外一个人
She's completely different with me.

544
00:49:23,670 --> 00:49:25,420
那你有什么看法
So, what are you saying?

545
00:49:25,580 --> 00:49:27,960
不知道 她在教室里大声尖叫
I don't know. She threw a fit at school.

546
00:49:28,130 --> 00:49:29,920
在操场上推布伦达
She pushed Brenda at the playground.

547
00:49:30,090 --> 00:49:32,150
你是想说都是她的错
Now you're saying that was her fault?

548
00:49:32,160 --> 00:49:34,010
不知道 亲爱的 不知道了
I don't know. Honey, I don't know.

549
00:49:34,180 --> 00:49:36,470
我不在场 当时是你看着她的
I wasn't there. You were watching them.

550
00:49:36,640 --> 00:49:40,220
噢 算了吧 那只是个意外
Oh, come on. It was an accident.

551
00:49:40,390 --> 00:49:43,600
好吧 那我们不去责备她了
Okay, let's not blame her for anything, fine.

552
00:49:43,770 --> 00:49:45,440
我也去相信她说的每件事
I'll take her word for everything.

553
00:49:45,600 --> 00:49:48,730
也包括你和乔伊斯的事吗
Should I just believe what she said about you and Joyce too?

554
00:49:48,900 --> 00:49:50,820
她怎么说的
What did she say?

555
00:49:51,690 --> 00:49:55,570
- 她说你和她搞暧昧 - 什么
- She says that you were hitting on her. - What?

556
00:49:55,740 --> 00:49:59,370
噢 她肯定误会了 那只是…
Oh, come on. She must've misunderstood. It was, like...

557
00:49:59,530 --> 00:50:00,870
她有叫你去她家吗
Did she invite you over?

558
00:50:01,040 --> 00:50:04,210
她让我去她家帮忙搬椅子
She asked me to help her move a chair.

559
00:50:04,370 --> 00:50:08,420
- 她说过 - 是的 但我婉拒了
- She did? - Yeah. I blew her off.

560
00:50:08,590 --> 00:50:10,960
噢 天啊
Oh, God.

561
00:50:11,130 --> 00:50:12,340
为什么不告诉我
Why didn't you tell me?

562
00:50:12,510 --> 00:50:14,340
- 因为… - 我们本可一笑置之
- Because... - Why? We could've laughed about it.

563
00:50:14,510 --> 00:50:16,300
- 不 我担心… - 而你却瞒着我
- No, I knew how... - You were hiding it.

564
00:50:16,470 --> 00:50:18,890
我担心你会像现在这样
Honey, I knew how you'd react.

565
00:50:19,050 --> 00:50:21,260
凯特 凯特
Kate. Kate.

566
00:50:21,430 --> 00:50:24,270
你不能对我交谈的每个女生 都那么敏感
You can't get jealous of every woman that I talk to, right?

567
00:50:24,430 --> 00:50:26,770
- 八百年前的事儿了 - 你这话什么意思
- It's been like 10 years. - What does that mean?

568
00:50:26,940 --> 00:50:29,110
说得好像是我的错
You say that like it actually means something.

569
00:50:29,270 --> 00:50:31,650
我是最近两年才知道那事的
It's only been two years since you told me.

570
00:50:31,820 --> 00:50:33,550
你知道我有多抱歉
You know how sorry I am.

571
00:50:33,560 --> 00:50:36,700
而我现在觉得压根不信任我
I just feel like I've earned a little trust here.

572
00:50:36,860 --> 00:50:40,580
- 我也给过你机会 - 不公平 太不公平了
- I gave you a second chance. - That's not fair. That's not fair.

573
00:50:40,740 --> 00:50:41,960
说清楚点
Let me get this straight.

574
00:50:41,960 --> 00:50:43,950
是不是只能说我的错 而不准提你的
We can talk about my mistakes, not yours?

575
00:50:44,120 --> 00:50:47,620
我那是病 你这个想操别人的混蛋
I was sick! You were an asshole who wanted to fuck somebody else!

576
00:50:47,790 --> 00:50:50,130
你让我们的孩子命悬一线
You put our child's life in danger.

577
00:50:50,290 --> 00:50:53,300
我几个月前就可以离开你 而且不会有人怪我
I could've walked away months ago. Nobody would've blamed me.

578
00:50:53,460 --> 00:50:55,380
噢 过分了 你过分了
Oh, that's sharp. That's sharp.

579
00:50:55,390 --> 00:50:57,930
是你妈妈教你这样说的
Where did you get that from, your mother?

580
00:51:11,650 --> 00:51:15,320
丹尼 别玩那垃圾了 我得做事
Danny. Turn that crap down, please, I gotta work.

581
00:51:15,490 --> 00:51:16,530
- 好吧 - 谢谢
- Fine. - Thank you.

582
00:51:21,410 --> 00:51:23,120
我去吧
I'll get it.

583
00:51:28,620 --> 00:51:32,170
- 你好 艾斯特 - 你来这干嘛
- Hello, Esther. - What are you doing here?

584
00:51:32,340 --> 00:51:34,420
我能进去吗
May I come in?

585
00:51:34,590 --> 00:51:37,970
我可能搞错了一件事
I'm afraid I may have made a mistake.

586
00:51:38,130 --> 00:51:40,260
艾斯特好像有点问题
There could be something wrong with Esther.

587
00:51:40,430 --> 00:51:41,640
什么
What?

588
00:51:41,800 --> 00:51:44,890
什么意思 你说过她从来不惹麻烦
What? You told us that you'd never had any trouble with her.

589
00:51:45,060 --> 00:51:48,350
是的 但麻烦总找上她
I didn't. But trouble does have a way of finding her.

590
00:51:48,520 --> 00:51:49,560
什么样的麻烦
What kind of trouble?

591
00:51:51,060 --> 00:51:53,270
有一次两个女孩打架 她在场
Two girls get into a fight, there she is.

592
00:51:53,440 --> 00:51:56,110
有人偷东西被抓 她又在场
Someone gets caught stealing, there she is again.

593
00:51:56,280 --> 00:51:58,490
- 那又怎样 难道… - 先让她说完
- So? Does that mean... ? - Just let her finish.

594
00:51:58,650 --> 00:52:00,180
你告诉我滑梯事件后
After you told me about the

595
00:52:00,190 --> 00:52:02,910
我打去她以前的学校
girl in the playground, I called her old school.

596
00:52:03,070 --> 00:52:05,540
得知有次一个男孩…
While she was there, there was a boy...

597
00:52:05,700 --> 00:52:07,660
手握剪刀摔了一跤…
...who fell with scissors in his hand...

598
00:52:07,830 --> 00:52:10,460
不小心把手给扎了个大口子
...and accidentally stabbed himself through the jaw.

599
00:52:10,620 --> 00:52:12,130
艾斯特同样在场
And Esther was there again.

600
00:52:12,290 --> 00:52:15,670
我不明白了 你都说了是不小心
I don't understand. He accidentally stabbed himself.

601
00:52:16,300 --> 00:52:19,260
但最大的麻烦还是沙利文家房屋被烧
But the most troubling thing is the Sullivan house fire.

602
00:52:19,420 --> 00:52:22,470
我深入了解了一下 那是纵火案
I checked into it further. It was arson.

603
00:52:23,510 --> 00:52:25,890
犯人一直没找到
They have never found the person who did it.

604
00:52:26,060 --> 00:52:28,060
你到底想说什么呢
What are you suggesting here?

605
00:52:28,220 --> 00:52:30,560
这些事她都有份参与
That she had anything to do with any of this?

606
00:52:30,730 --> 00:52:32,020
太荒谬了
It's ridiculous.

607
00:52:32,190 --> 00:52:34,190
我也不愿相信这些事…
That a child could commit such crimes...

608
00:52:34,360 --> 00:52:36,230
会出自一个孩子之手
...it flies in the face of everything I believe.

609
00:52:36,400 --> 00:52:37,860
是啊 不会的
Well, yeah.

610
00:52:42,950 --> 00:52:47,370
家里来了个刻薄的女人 她想带我走
There's a mean lady here. She's come to take me away.

611
00:52:47,540 --> 00:52:49,500
你能帮帮我吗
Will you help me?

612
00:52:49,660 --> 00:52:53,290
她有些行为是不好 但…
We've had some behavioral problems, but...

613
00:52:53,460 --> 00:52:56,130
但还不至于到那种地步 对吧
Yeah, nothing like that. I mean, right?

614
00:52:56,290 --> 00:52:59,010
- 有 有的 - 真的吗 再想想
- Yes, we have. - Really, hon, think about it.

615
00:52:59,170 --> 00:53:02,880
我有试过联系她在俄罗斯的孤儿院
I've tried to reach the Russian orphanage where she was raised.

616
00:53:03,050 --> 00:53:05,640
我觉得有必要搞清楚她的背景
I think we need to know what we're dealing with.

617
00:53:05,800 --> 00:53:08,310
好吧 我来告诉你
Well, I'll tell you what we're dealing with.

618
00:53:08,470 --> 00:53:10,560
- 等一下 - 别说话 听着
- No, you know what? - Stop it. Listen.

619
00:53:10,730 --> 00:53:13,900
她就只是一个九岁大的 父母双亡的小女孩
We're dealing with a 9-year-old girl who's an orphan, okay?

620
00:53:14,060 --> 00:53:15,550
我们得带她去见见布朗宁医生
We're taking her to Dr. Browning.

621
00:53:15,550 --> 00:53:18,110
那就带她去见见布朗宁医生
We can take her to Dr. Browning.

622
00:53:22,230 --> 00:53:24,560
去找树屋的钥匙

623
00:54:15,500 --> 00:54:17,130
要玩玩吗
Do you want to play?

624
00:54:24,380 --> 00:54:27,050
一有新发现我就马上通知你
I'll call you as soon as I find anything else out.

625
00:54:27,220 --> 00:54:29,800
- 好的 您保重 - 好的 非常感谢
- Right. Take care. - Okay. Thank you very much.

626
00:54:29,970 --> 00:54:31,640
晚点再玩
Maybe later.

627
00:54:52,580 --> 00:54:53,620
不会有事的
It's going to be fine.

628
00:54:53,790 --> 00:54:57,120
我们只是吓吓她好让她别再来了
We'll scare her so bad she'll never come back here.

629
00:55:05,420 --> 00:55:06,470
她来了
Here she comes.

630
00:55:06,630 --> 00:55:08,680
去招手让她停车
Wave your arms and make her stop.

631
00:55:08,840 --> 00:55:10,050
麦克斯 去吧
Max, go.

632
00:55:39,710 --> 00:55:42,420
你没事吧 麦克斯
You all right'? Max?

633
00:55:42,590 --> 00:55:44,340
麦克斯
Max?

634
00:55:44,920 --> 00:55:45,960
没事吧
You Okay?

635
00:55:59,440 --> 00:56:01,440
别哭了
Stop crying-

636
00:56:01,600 --> 00:56:06,110
抓住脚 帮我把她弄到路边去
Grab a foot and help me get her off the road.

637
00:56:06,280 --> 00:56:07,860
快去
Now.

638
00:57:16,850 --> 00:57:20,220
帮我把她藏起来
Help me hide her.

639
00:57:57,070 --> 00:57:58,430
你耍了我

640
00:57:58,550 --> 00:58:00,060
那不重要
That doesn't matter.

641
00:58:00,220 --> 00:58:03,810
就因为你帮我藏尸体 他们也会把你关进监狱
They'll send you to jail just for helping me hide her.

642
00:58:03,980 --> 00:58:07,810
她要告发我 我只能杀了她
I had to kill her because she was going to tell on me.

643
00:58:09,360 --> 00:58:14,320
你不会告发我的 对吧
You're not going to tell on me. Are you?

644
00:58:23,710 --> 00:58:25,000
别担心
Don't worry.

645
00:58:25,160 --> 00:58:27,330
你是我妹妹
You're my little sister.

646
00:58:27,500 --> 00:58:30,630
我不会让你有事的
I won't let anything happen to you.

647
00:58:30,800 --> 00:58:32,300
我爱你
I love you.

648
00:59:42,830 --> 00:59:45,080
告诉我你都看见些什么
Tell me what you saw.

649
00:59:45,240 --> 00:59:48,040
- 你在干嘛 - 你看见些什么
- What are you doing? - What did you see?

650
00:59:48,210 --> 00:59:50,370
我看见你和麦克斯在树屋里
I saw you and Max in the tree house.

651
00:59:50,540 --> 00:59:51,960
其他呢
What else?

652
00:59:52,130 --> 00:59:54,460
- 其他还看见什么 - 什么其他啊
- What do you mean? - What else did you see?

653
00:59:54,630 --> 00:59:56,300
什么都没看见了 我发誓
I didn't see anything. I swear.

654
00:59:56,460 --> 00:59:58,380
- 你有告诉别人吗 - 没有
- Did you tell anyone? - No.

655
00:59:59,220 --> 01:00:00,550
我没告诉任何人
I didn't tell anyone.

656
01:00:02,220 --> 01:00:03,390
求你别…
Please...

657
01:00:03,550 --> 01:00:05,320
如果你骗我
If I find out that you're lying,

658
01:00:05,320 --> 01:00:07,640
我会切掉你那还没长毛的小鸡鸡…
I'll cut your hairless little prick off...

659
01:00:07,810 --> 01:00:10,600
让你来不及体会它的真正用处
...before you even figure out what it's for.

660
01:00:11,650 --> 01:00:14,570
- 听懂了吗 - 懂了
- Do you understand me? - Yes.

661
01:00:17,990 --> 01:00:19,610
你尿床了
You pissed yourself.

662
01:00:31,370 --> 01:00:33,840
和你聊得很开心 艾丽丝 希望我们能做朋友
It was nice talking to you, Alice. I hope we can be friends.

663
01:00:34,000 --> 01:00:36,050
非常愿意
I'd like that.

664
01:00:36,920 --> 01:00:39,800
- 我们马上出来 宝贝 - 你们可以进来了
- We'll be right out, honey. - You can come on in.

665
01:00:47,430 --> 01:00:50,480
我的第一直觉是…
My initial instinct is that...

666
01:00:50,640 --> 01:00:54,440
艾斯特的过去没什么 根深蒂固的大问题
...there's not a deeply-rooted problem in Esther's past.

667
01:00:55,150 --> 01:00:59,190
- 那她现在没问题 - 也不是
- So there's nothing wrong with her? - No.

668
01:01:02,360 --> 01:01:05,240
问题还是有 我们需要去关注一下…
It's not all good news. I think what needs to be examined...

669
01:01:05,410 --> 01:01:08,950
艾斯特和她周围人之间的关系
...is Esther's relationship with those around her.

670
01:01:09,120 --> 01:01:10,830
特别是和你 凯特
Specifically with you, Kate.

671
01:01:11,000 --> 01:01:12,370
你们之间的关系
It seems she feels there's

672
01:01:12,370 --> 01:01:14,790
似乎很紧张
been some real tension between the two of you.

673
01:01:14,960 --> 01:01:18,130
- 是么 - 她已经尽力讨好你…
- Okay. - She's doing her best to please you...

674
01:01:18,300 --> 01:01:20,760
你却不领情
...but you're blocking her attempts to bond.

675
01:01:22,260 --> 01:01:26,550
不是那样的 根本不是那么回事 该做的我都做了
That's not true. That's not true at all. I've done everything.

676
01:01:26,720 --> 01:01:29,430
- 是吧 - 让她说完
- Right? - Just let her finish.

677
01:01:29,600 --> 01:01:32,480
有些事导致她产生这样的感觉
Something's happening to cause Esther to feel this way.

678
01:01:32,640 --> 01:01:37,020
也许是你对酗酒或对麦克斯感到内疚
Perhaps it's your guilt about drinking or what happened to Max.

679
01:01:37,190 --> 01:01:39,900
也许是你自认不是个合格的母亲的情绪…
Maybe some of your feelings of inadequacy as a mother...

680
01:01:40,070 --> 01:01:43,400
在与艾斯特相处时不自觉的流露
...are manifesting themselves in your relationship with Esther.

681
01:01:43,570 --> 01:01:45,740
我不认为我不合适啊
I don't feel inadequate.

682
01:01:49,080 --> 01:01:50,790
她跟你说了什么啊
What did she tell you?

683
01:01:50,950 --> 01:01:54,080
她没察觉 她没发现
She didn't see. She doesn't know.

684
01:01:55,290 --> 01:01:57,340
她很白痴
She's so stupid.

685
01:01:57,500 --> 01:02:01,170
艾斯特是个很害羞 缄默…
Esther's a very shy, reserved...

686
01:02:01,340 --> 01:02:02,660
和敏感的小女孩
...sensitive little girl

687
01:02:02,660 --> 01:02:04,970
她正处于最困难的时期
going through an extremely difficult time.

688
01:02:11,680 --> 01:02:15,190
她特别的聪明 善于表达
She's exceptionally bright and highly articulate.

689
01:02:18,270 --> 01:02:21,650
只需要多点耐心 多点理解
She just needs a little patience and understanding.

690
01:02:39,670 --> 01:02:41,750
多谢你的"支持"
Thanks for your support back there.

691
01:02:42,670 --> 01:02:44,880
这可是你的主意
That was your idea.

692
01:02:48,260 --> 01:02:50,220
凯特 等等
Kate, wait, wait, wait.

693
01:02:50,390 --> 01:02:53,720
虽然我不是心理医师 但我觉得她说得有些道理
I'm not a psychiatrist, but a lot of what she said made sense.

694
01:02:53,890 --> 01:02:55,810
要接么
Do you wanna get that?

695
01:02:59,980 --> 01:03:02,150
- 你好 - 你好 是科尔曼夫人么
- Hello? - Hello, is this Mrs. Coleman?

696
01:03:02,320 --> 01:03:03,400
我是 您是
Yes. Who's this?

697
01:03:03,570 --> 01:03:05,530
我是圣玛丽亚孤儿院的修女朱迪丝
This is Sister Judith from St. Mariana's.

698
01:03:05,700 --> 01:03:07,860
抱歉打扰你 我就是想问下…
I'm sorry to bother you, but I need to know...

699
01:03:08,030 --> 01:03:10,910
阿比盖尔修女有没有去你那
...if Sister Abigail made it to her appointment with you.

700
01:03:11,080 --> 01:03:13,240
来过了 怎么了
Yes. Why?

701
01:03:13,410 --> 01:03:15,290
她从昨天就一直没回来…
She hasn't returned since yesterday...

702
01:03:15,450 --> 01:03:18,540
我有点担心她了
...and I'm just starting to get really worried.

703
01:03:44,400 --> 01:03:46,320
好了 我问完了
Okay, I think we're done.

704
01:03:47,860 --> 01:03:51,320
警官 有线索或是疑犯了么
Detective, do you have any leads or suspects?

705
01:03:51,490 --> 01:03:55,330
- 还没有 - 为什么…
- No, not yet. - I just don't understand...

706
01:03:55,490 --> 01:03:58,040
发生这事 谁能干出这事 太….
...this kind of thing. Who would do this? It's...

707
01:03:58,210 --> 01:03:59,250
恐怖了
Awful.

708
01:03:59,420 --> 01:04:01,710
如果你们有其它线索 电话我们
You think of anything else, you give us a call.

709
01:04:01,880 --> 01:04:03,380
嗯 一定
Yes. Absolutely.

710
01:04:04,250 --> 01:04:05,840
走了
Let's go.

711
01:05:02,400 --> 01:05:05,560
这些正是阿比盖尔修女说的 看
This is what Sister Abigail was talking about. Look.

712
01:05:05,730 --> 01:05:09,440
"性格障碍儿童" 看这些症状
"Character-disturbed children." Look at the symptoms.

713
01:05:09,610 --> 01:05:11,460
"看起来可爱
"Superficially charming.

714
01:05:11,460 --> 01:05:14,700
难交朋友以及维系友谊"
Difficulty at making and keeping friends."

715
01:05:15,450 --> 01:05:17,200
我觉得修女未必是这个意思
I'm not sure this is what she meant.

716
01:05:17,370 --> 01:05:21,330
她可以拣布朗宁医生想听的说
She could've told Dr. Browning whatever she wanted to hear. Look.

717
01:05:23,920 --> 01:05:26,000
"他们善于操纵…
They "Are adroit manipulators...

718
01:05:26,170 --> 01:05:27,370
常常挑拨
...oftentimes playing

719
01:05:27,370 --> 01:05:30,010
他人敌对达到自己目的"
people off one another to get what they want."

720
01:05:30,170 --> 01:05:32,430
你打算让布朗宁医生也看看
Well, you gonna show this to Dr. Browning?

721
01:05:32,590 --> 01:05:34,930
我不打算给她看这些
I'm not showing her anything.

722
01:05:35,470 --> 01:05:37,140
我以后都不见她了
I'm not seeing her anymore.

723
01:05:37,300 --> 01:05:40,270
- 你什么时候决定的 - 你觉得呢
- When did you decide that? - When do you think?

724
01:05:40,430 --> 01:05:42,310
你不信任布朗宁医生了
You're gonna discount Dr. Browning?

725
01:05:42,480 --> 01:05:43,850
为什么你不怀疑
Why does everyone get the

726
01:05:43,850 --> 01:05:46,270
其他人有问题 单单只怀疑我呢
benefit of the doubt from you except for me?

727
01:05:56,200 --> 01:05:59,290
如果需要帮手照顾孩子们 我们可以找一位
If you need help with the kids, we can arrange that.

728
01:05:59,450 --> 01:06:01,700
我不需要
I don't need help.

729
01:06:10,710 --> 01:06:12,550
只是想了解她多一点
I just wanna know more about her.

730
01:06:12,720 --> 01:06:16,680
她从哪来 她是谁
I wanna know where she came from, and I wanna know who she is.

731
01:06:16,840 --> 01:06:19,050
假如阿比盖尔修女是对的
What if Sister Abigail was right?

732
01:06:19,220 --> 01:06:22,020
如果有人身处危险 我们自己的孩子…
I mean, if someone was in danger, our own children...

733
01:06:22,180 --> 01:06:24,890
- 难道你不想搞清楚 - 我当然想
- ...wouldn't you wanna know? - Of course I would.

734
01:06:25,060 --> 01:06:28,810
我会和她以前的俄罗斯孤儿院联系
I'll contact the orphanage she came from in Russia. All right?

735
01:06:28,980 --> 01:06:30,520
这是初步打算
I mean, it's a start.

736
01:06:40,910 --> 01:06:43,540
- 怎么了 - 嘿
- What? - Hey.

737
01:06:49,960 --> 01:06:51,460
好吧
Fine.

738
01:06:51,630 --> 01:06:52,820
我想知道你是否
I was wondering if you'd

739
01:06:52,820 --> 01:06:54,970
有收到来自Sludyanka孤儿院的消息
heard from anyone at the Sludyanka Shelter.

740
01:06:55,130 --> 01:06:57,840
阿比盖尔修女曾提过 她要…
Sister Abigail had mentioned that she would...

741
01:06:58,390 --> 01:06:59,600
你查了
Oh, you did.

742
01:07:02,720 --> 01:07:03,650
我不明白
I don't understand.

743
01:07:03,650 --> 01:07:05,940
为什么没有她在那的记录呢
How can they have no record of her being there?

744
01:07:07,690 --> 01:07:08,980
好的 谢谢
Yes, please.

745
01:07:09,150 --> 01:07:10,620
如果你一有消息
Could you just call me as

746
01:07:10,620 --> 01:07:13,280
请马上电话我 谢谢
soon as you know anything, please? Thank you.

747
01:07:45,270 --> 01:07:46,850
艾斯特 该走了
Esther, we gotta go.

748
01:07:53,520 --> 01:07:55,230
艾斯特
Esther?

749
01:07:59,240 --> 01:08:00,990
艾斯特
Esther?

750
01:08:02,410 --> 01:08:03,740
被你吓到了
You got me.

751
01:08:06,660 --> 01:08:09,460
- 怎么了 - 我不想去看牙医
- What? - I don't want to go to the dentist.

752
01:08:09,620 --> 01:08:12,250
- 为什么呢 - 就是不想去
- Why not? - I just don't want to go.

753
01:08:12,420 --> 01:08:14,670
- 害怕了 - 不是
- What, are you scared? - No.

754
01:08:16,550 --> 01:08:18,420
那就下次吧
We're gonna reschedule, though.

755
01:08:18,590 --> 01:08:20,120
如果你乖乖的
Tell you what, I'll let you

756
01:08:20,120 --> 01:08:22,850
和我一起画画 你今天就可以翘课了
play hooky if you want to come and draw with me.

757
01:08:23,010 --> 01:08:24,930
好吧
All right.

758
01:08:28,600 --> 01:08:30,310
等会 丹尼尔
Wait, Daniel.

759
01:08:30,480 --> 01:08:33,940
你们和艾斯特处得如何
How are you two getting along with Esther?

760
01:08:36,440 --> 01:08:37,610
还不错
Fine, I guess.

761
01:08:37,780 --> 01:08:39,110
- 是么 - 嗯 妈妈
- Yeah? - Yeah, Mom.

762
01:08:41,410 --> 01:08:45,450
她有没有让你们感到不安…
But has she ever made you feel, I don't know, uncomfortable...

763
01:08:45,620 --> 01:08:48,620
或者有没有做什么不该做的事
...or has she done anything that she's not supposed to do?

764
01:08:49,620 --> 01:08:53,750
- 没有 - 比如 有没有伤害过你们
- No. - Like, has she ever hurt any of you?

765
01:08:54,880 --> 01:08:56,500
没有
No.

766
01:09:00,050 --> 01:09:01,430
确定
You sure?

767
01:09:04,890 --> 01:09:08,020
好吧
Okay. All right.

768
01:09:09,600 --> 01:09:12,230
只有我们俩真好
I like it when it's just the two of us.

769
01:09:12,390 --> 01:09:16,480
你都想不到我等了多久才等到 像你这样的父亲
You don't know how long I've waited for a daddy just like you.

770
01:09:16,650 --> 01:09:18,110
还有母亲 对不
Mommy too, right?

771
01:09:20,110 --> 01:09:21,990
我觉得妈妈不太喜欢我
I don't think Mommy likes me very much.

772
01:09:23,740 --> 01:09:26,280
- 错了 妈妈爱你的 - 没什么的
- That is not true. Mommy loves you. - it's all right.

773
01:09:26,450 --> 01:09:29,580
爱领养孩子当然不可能像爱自己孩子一样多
It must be hard to love an adopted child as much as your own.

774
01:09:29,750 --> 01:09:31,270
宝贝 你同丹尼和麦克斯一样
Sweetheart, you're just as

775
01:09:31,270 --> 01:09:34,210
都是这个家的一部分 明白么
much a part of this family as Danny and Max. Okay?

776
01:09:35,290 --> 01:09:38,550
为妈妈做点什么 让她知道你爱她
Do something nice for Mommy. Show her how much you love her.

777
01:09:38,710 --> 01:09:41,260
真是个好主意
That's a wonderful idea.

778
01:10:00,860 --> 01:10:03,030
我有个惊喜要送给你 妈妈
I have a special surprise for you, Mommy.

779
01:10:03,990 --> 01:10:05,410
真的
You do?

780
01:10:07,030 --> 01:10:09,790
我为你摘了这些花
I picked these flowers just for you.

781
01:10:12,750 --> 01:10:18,710
- 艾斯特 你做了什么呀 天哪 - 我的胳膊
- Esther, what did you do? God. - My arm!

782
01:10:18,880 --> 01:10:20,250
- 你为什么要这样做 - 爸爸 我的胳膊
- Why did you do this? - Daddy, my arm!

783
01:10:21,960 --> 01:10:23,130
- 约翰 - 嘿
- John! - Hey.

784
01:10:23,300 --> 01:10:26,300
- 为什么要这样做 - 嘿 停手 停手
- What did you do? - Hey. Stop, stop.

785
01:10:26,470 --> 01:10:27,550
为什么要这样做
Why did you do this?

786
01:10:27,720 --> 01:10:30,810
- 天呐 她故意的 - 不是
- Oh, God. God, she did this on purpose. - No, no, no.

787
01:10:30,970 --> 01:10:32,430
- 就是的 - 亲爱的 不是
- Yes, she did. - Hey. Honey, no.

788
01:10:32,600 --> 01:10:35,020
她明明清楚这些玫瑰对我意味着什么
She knew what these roses meant to me.

789
01:10:35,190 --> 01:10:38,520
我的错 亲爱的 不该让她讨好你
It's my fault, hon. I told her to do something nice for you.

790
01:10:38,690 --> 01:10:40,400
真不敢相信
I can't believe this.

791
01:12:22,580 --> 01:12:24,880
爸爸
Daddy!

792
01:12:25,590 --> 01:12:27,880
爸爸
Daddy!

793
01:12:29,010 --> 01:12:31,510
爸爸 爸爸
Daddy, Daddy!

794
01:12:31,680 --> 01:12:32,760
怎么了 宝贝
What is it, honey?

795
01:12:33,390 --> 01:12:35,560
我的手好痛啊
My arm still hurts.

796
01:12:40,480 --> 01:12:43,940
看看好吗 你会没事的
Can I have a look at it? You're okay.

797
01:12:44,110 --> 01:12:46,570
我会轻轻的 没事的 宝贝
I'll be gentle. It's all right, honey.

798
01:12:46,730 --> 01:12:48,490
天呀
Oh, my God.

799
01:12:50,360 --> 01:12:52,870
得马上送你去医院
We need to take you to the hospital.

800
01:12:57,450 --> 01:12:59,870
你是个非常勇敢的女孩 知道么
You're a brave little girl, you know that?

801
01:13:00,040 --> 01:13:02,830
医生说你很快就能痊愈了
Doctor said you're gonna heal real fast, okay?

802
01:13:19,350 --> 01:13:20,560
你拉断了她的胳膊
You broke her arm.

803
01:13:24,650 --> 01:13:26,820
不可能 我根本没用力拉她
It's impossible. I didn't grab her that hard.

804
01:13:26,980 --> 01:13:29,560
她今晚想睡这
She wants to sleep in here tonight.

805
01:13:29,560 --> 01:13:32,070
也许你该睡楼下去
Maybe you should sleep downstairs.

806
01:13:52,010 --> 01:13:54,430
今晚来客人了
I'm having guests for dinner.

807
01:13:58,560 --> 01:14:01,270
不用找了 谢谢
You know, you can have it. Thanks.

808
01:15:04,660 --> 01:15:06,920
过得开心
Have a good day.

809
01:15:14,800 --> 01:15:16,430
丹尼尔
Daniel.

810
01:15:16,590 --> 01:15:18,300
你的书
Your books.

811
01:15:21,810 --> 01:15:25,100
- 怎么回事 让我看看你的书包 - 我也不知道
- What happened? Let me see your bag. - I don't know.

812
01:15:27,350 --> 01:15:30,860
才买的啊 把书捡起来 要不都湿了
We just bought this. Pick it up, it's gonna get wet.

813
01:15:37,450 --> 01:15:39,110
妈妈
Mom!

814
01:15:41,280 --> 01:15:44,540
麦克斯 不 救命
Max! No! Help!

815
01:15:46,040 --> 01:15:47,830
麦克斯
Max!

816
01:15:49,620 --> 01:15:51,170
麦克斯
Max!

817
01:16:03,510 --> 01:16:05,100
麦克斯
Max!

818
01:16:12,610 --> 01:16:14,480
麦克斯
Max!

819
01:16:14,650 --> 01:16:16,400
你还好吗
Are you okay?

820
01:16:16,570 --> 01:16:19,950
我在这 妈妈在这 没事了 宝贝
I'm here. Mommy's here. You're okay, honey. Come on.

821
01:16:20,110 --> 01:16:25,080
抱着你了 宝贝 没事了 对不起
I got you. Yeah. Oh, baby, it's okay. I'm so sorry.

822
01:16:27,120 --> 01:16:29,620
我明明挂在停车档 还拉了手闸
I remember I put it in park and I set the brake.

823
01:16:29,790 --> 01:16:32,500
麦克斯没说艾斯特做了什么
Max didn't indicate that Esther did anything.

824
01:16:32,670 --> 01:16:34,910
麦克斯在包庇她
Well, Max is covering for her.

825
01:16:34,910 --> 01:16:37,760
而且不止这一次
And I don't think it's the first time.

826
01:16:37,920 --> 01:16:39,330
这也不是第一次
It also wouldn't be the first

827
01:16:39,330 --> 01:16:41,470
你把自己犯的错 推到艾斯特头上
time you blamed Esther for your own mistake.

828
01:16:45,010 --> 01:16:47,470
我不希望她继续待在这里
You know what? I want her out of this house.

829
01:16:47,640 --> 01:16:49,890
你打算让人把她领走了
You're ready for somebody to come and take her?

830
01:16:50,060 --> 01:16:52,520
是的 我不在乎
I am. I don't care.

831
01:16:52,690 --> 01:16:56,530
我会不惜一切代价保护我的孩子
I will do whatever it takes to protect my children.

832
01:16:56,690 --> 01:16:58,360
女孩们早上发现了这个
The girls found this this morning.

833
01:16:59,320 --> 01:17:02,030
女孩们发现 你是说艾斯特发现的吧
The girls found it. You mean Esther found it.

834
01:17:02,200 --> 01:17:04,830
是艾斯特 有区别么 她说谎了
Yes, Esther. Does it make any difference? Is she lying?

835
01:17:04,990 --> 01:17:06,120
你需要帮助
You need help.

836
01:17:06,280 --> 01:17:09,330
我们在康复中心为你做了预定…
We've reserved a place for you in a rehabilitation facility...

837
01:17:09,500 --> 01:17:11,830
离这仅45分钟路程
...about 45 minutes from here.

838
01:17:12,000 --> 01:17:13,380
我没喝
I didn't drink it.

839
01:17:13,540 --> 01:17:16,960
买了两瓶 往水池子里倒了一瓶
I bought two bottles. I poured one of them down the sink.

840
01:17:17,130 --> 01:17:18,880
- 不是这个 - 不是
- But not this one? - No.

841
01:17:19,050 --> 01:17:22,840
约翰 我快一年滴酒未沾了
John, I haven't had a drink in almost a year.

842
01:17:23,010 --> 01:17:25,470
我们是想帮你 如果你还在欺骗自己…
We wanna help you, but there's nothing we can do...

843
01:17:25,640 --> 01:17:27,520
我们就没办法了
...until you stop lying to yourself.

844
01:17:27,520 --> 01:17:29,720
我没说谎 我是想喝
I'm not lying. I wanted to drink it.

845
01:17:29,890 --> 01:17:31,140
你都不知道
You have no fucking idea

846
01:17:31,140 --> 01:17:33,480
我有多想喝 但我没喝
how badly I wanted to drink it, but I didn't.

847
01:17:33,650 --> 01:17:36,020
- 我没喝 - 假如麦克斯受伤了….
- I didn't drink it. - If Max had gotten hurt...

848
01:17:36,190 --> 01:17:39,780
今天早上的事跟这个没有一点关系
What happened this morning has nothing to do with this.

849
01:17:39,940 --> 01:17:41,570
没法信你
I find that hard to believe.

850
01:17:42,320 --> 01:17:46,490
我滴酒不沾的唯一原因就是为了麦克斯和丹尼尔
The only reason that I'm sober is because of Max and Daniel.

851
01:17:47,580 --> 01:17:51,120
一想到你若因我酗酒而离开 且酿成大祸…
I think about what would have happened had you not been there...

852
01:17:51,290 --> 01:17:53,330
我会杀了我自己的
...and it makes me wanna kill myself.

853
01:17:53,500 --> 01:17:55,250
我不会做任何事…
I would never do anything...

854
01:17:55,420 --> 01:17:58,500
让这种情况发生 不会
...to let something like that ever happen again. I wouldn't.

855
01:17:58,670 --> 01:18:00,960
太煽情了
That is so manipulative.

856
01:18:01,130 --> 01:18:02,270
我知道没有理由
I know I haven't given

857
01:18:02,280 --> 01:18:04,510
让你相信我 我知道我没有
you reason to believe me, I know I haven't.

858
01:18:04,680 --> 01:18:07,010
我对你说谎了 我该告诉你的
I lied to you. I should have told you about this.

859
01:18:07,180 --> 01:18:09,260
我会接受治疗 我会去该死的戒酒互助会
I'll go to therapy, I'll go to fucking A.A.

860
01:18:09,260 --> 01:18:10,520
如果这是你希望的…
If that's what you want...

861
01:18:10,680 --> 01:18:13,060
- 但你一定要相信我 - 我不信
- ...but you have to believe me. - I don't.

862
01:18:13,230 --> 01:18:16,060
你必须相信我 约翰 这事你必须信我
You have to believe me. John, you have to trust me on this.

863
01:18:16,230 --> 01:18:18,650
你有一周的时间考虑是去康复中心…
I'll give you a week to go to rehab...

864
01:18:18,820 --> 01:18:21,360
还是我带孩子们走
...or I'm leaving and I'm taking the kids with me.

865
01:18:21,530 --> 01:18:23,740
这样很公平 是吧
I think that's fair, okay?

866
01:18:23,900 --> 01:18:26,450
我会尽力帮你 让你尽快恢复
I'll help you as much as I can, make it really easy.

867
01:18:26,620 --> 01:18:28,410
妈妈下午会过来
Mom's gonna come in the afternoon.

868
01:18:28,580 --> 01:18:30,890
好吗 我很愿意
All right? I'm willing to do this.

869
01:18:30,890 --> 01:18:33,540
愿意帮你度过难关
I'm willing to try and figure this out.

870
01:18:33,710 --> 01:18:37,500
- 都看你了 - 如果你敢讲出去我就枪毙了你妈妈
- But it's up to you. - I'll shoot Mommy if you tell.

871
01:18:58,440 --> 01:19:01,150
麦克斯 麦克斯 你没事吧
Max. Max, are you okay?

872
01:19:02,320 --> 01:19:05,820
她做了什么 是她动了手脚导致车祸的
What did she do? Did she do something to make the car crash?

873
01:19:07,490 --> 01:19:09,900
你看见了 就要帮我
If you saw her, you have to help me,

874
01:19:09,900 --> 01:19:11,910
这样爸妈才可以保护我们
so Mom and Dad can protect us.

875
01:19:12,340 --> 01:19:13,830
他们无能为力的

876
01:19:14,910 --> 01:19:16,120
为什么
Why not?

877
01:19:25,300 --> 01:19:27,380
这是阿比盖尔修女
Is that Sister Abigail?

878
01:19:34,520 --> 01:19:37,440
麦克斯 她在我树屋里干嘛
Max. What did she do in my tree house?

879
01:19:38,300 --> 01:19:40,100
她把不好的东西放进去了

880
01:19:40,270 --> 01:19:41,980
那些不好的东西还在么
Are the bad things still there?

881
01:19:45,320 --> 01:19:47,280
一切都会没事的
Everything's gonna be okay.

882
01:19:47,450 --> 01:19:50,060
我会把那些东西从树屋取出来
I'll get the stuff from the tree house.

883
01:19:50,060 --> 01:19:52,200
这样他们就会信我们了
Then they'll have to believe us.

884
01:20:39,330 --> 01:20:42,580
- 要去哪啊 凯特 - 你在这做什么
- Going somewhere, Kate? - What are you doing here?

885
01:20:42,750 --> 01:20:45,250
她很好 别吵醒她
She's fine. Let's not wake her.

886
01:20:45,420 --> 01:20:46,590
回你自己房间去
Go to your room.

887
01:20:46,760 --> 01:20:50,300
不用再假扮了 对么
Honestly, we're past that now. Aren't we?

888
01:20:50,470 --> 01:20:52,550
我知道你想干什么
I know what you're doing.

889
01:20:53,720 --> 01:20:55,600
我不会让你伤害我孩子一丝一毫的
I will not let you hurt my children.

890
01:20:55,760 --> 01:20:56,970
我
Me?

891
01:20:57,140 --> 01:20:58,430
我又不是那个喝得醉醺醺的
I'm not the one who passed

892
01:20:58,430 --> 01:21:00,770
害麦克斯在池塘溺水的人
out drunk and let Max almost drown in the pond.

893
01:21:00,940 --> 01:21:02,350
要不是约翰…
If it wasn't for John...

894
01:21:02,520 --> 01:21:06,320
她就死了 而你也该在牢里待着了
...she'd be dead, and you'd probably still be in jail.

895
01:21:08,280 --> 01:21:09,360
谁告诉你的
Who told you that?

896
01:21:12,070 --> 01:21:13,280
非常隐私
It's very intimate.

897
01:21:14,200 --> 01:21:15,870
- 让我了解了很多 - 还给我
- I learned so much. - Give it to me.

898
01:21:16,030 --> 01:21:19,580
- 杰西卡 还有背叛你的丈夫 - 艾斯特 还给我
- Jessica. Your cheating husband. - Esther, give it to me.

899
01:21:19,750 --> 01:21:21,540
酒瓶藏在哪了
Where you hide your wine bottles.

900
01:21:21,710 --> 01:21:24,040
我… 我警告你
I'm... I'm warning you right now.

901
01:21:24,210 --> 01:21:26,540
"医生宣布噩耗时 她还在踢我…
"She was still kicking when the doctor told me...

902
01:21:26,710 --> 01:21:29,420
而那只是幻觉…
...it was something called phantom...

903
01:21:29,590 --> 01:21:31,050
胎动的幻觉
...fetal movement.

904
01:21:31,220 --> 01:21:34,890
- 16天来 我怀着已经夭折的孩子" - 住嘴 艾斯特
- For 16 days, I carried my dead baby." - Stop it. Esther.

905
01:21:35,050 --> 01:21:38,310
"是我能想象到的最残忍的折磨"
"It was the cruelest torture I could imagine."

906
01:21:38,470 --> 01:21:40,890
闭嘴 你给我闭嘴
Stop it. You stop it.

907
01:21:41,060 --> 01:21:43,190
你到底怎么了
What's wrong with you?

908
01:21:43,350 --> 01:21:46,150
凯特 太晚了 都是你的错
Kate, it's too late. It's your own fault.

909
01:21:46,310 --> 01:21:47,980
你把这个家庭当成理所当然的
You took your family for granted.

910
01:21:48,570 --> 01:21:51,690
- 你什么意思 - 你想干吗
- What do you mean? - What are you going to do?

911
01:21:53,360 --> 01:21:55,070
打我
Hit me'?

912
01:22:00,830 --> 01:22:03,870
我们是从你们那领养的 你居然说你们完全不了解她
We adopted her from you. How could you not know anything?

913
01:22:04,040 --> 01:22:06,330
沙利文家有可能是非法收养她
The Sullivans could have adopted her illegally.

914
01:22:06,500 --> 01:22:09,460
她记不起任何对我们有帮助的事情了
She doesn't remember anything that could help us?

915
01:22:11,340 --> 01:22:12,840
我会再打的
I'm gonna call you back.

916
01:23:30,250 --> 01:23:33,130
"Saarne机构"
"Saarne institute."

917
01:23:52,230 --> 01:23:56,030
你好 你会说英语吗
Hello. Do you speak English?

918
01:23:57,900 --> 01:23:59,570
你会说英语吗
Do you speak English?

919
01:23:59,740 --> 01:24:01,740
不好意思 有没有人会说英语
Is there anyone who speaks English there?

920
01:24:01,910 --> 01:24:03,870
事情紧急
This is very important.

921
01:24:07,960 --> 01:24:09,290
不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're saying.

922
01:24:22,640 --> 01:24:24,970
- 喂 - 是Saarne机构吗
- Hello? - Is this the Saarne Institute?

923
01:24:25,140 --> 01:24:26,680
是的
Yes.

924
01:24:26,850 --> 01:24:30,310
我想询问你们机构一个孩子的情况
Yes. I need to talk to somebody about one of your children.

925
01:24:30,480 --> 01:24:33,110
她被一户美国家庭所收养 是女孩
She was adopted by an American family. It's a girl.

926
01:24:33,270 --> 01:24:36,400
她不可能是这儿的
She is not come from here.

927
01:24:36,570 --> 01:24:38,700
我还没说她的名字呢
Well, I haven't even told you her name yet.

928
01:24:38,860 --> 01:24:41,740
你不明白 Saarne机构不是孤儿院
You do not understand. Saarne Institute is not an orphanage.

929
01:24:41,910 --> 01:24:43,280
而是精神病院
It is a mental hospital.

930
01:25:11,310 --> 01:25:13,270
你是在找这个吗
Are you looking for this?

931
01:25:15,480 --> 01:25:16,860
可怜的阿比盖尔修女
Poor Sister Abigail.

932
01:25:18,070 --> 01:25:20,160
这种事儿我一个人可做不来
I couldn't have done it myself,

933
01:25:20,160 --> 01:25:22,860
麦克斯和我一样有罪
you know. Max is just as guilty as I am.

934
01:25:23,030 --> 01:25:26,700
- 不管麦克斯做了什么 都是你逼她的 - 想想看
- Whatever Max did, you made her do it. - Think about it.

935
01:25:26,870 --> 01:25:29,370
她怎么可能知道东西藏在这里
How did she even know what was up here?

936
01:25:30,000 --> 01:25:33,170
证据还是烧了好
It's always better to burn the evidence.

937
01:25:33,330 --> 01:25:38,210
如果被找到 他们不仅会追究我
If they find these things, they won't just be coming for me.

938
01:25:38,380 --> 01:25:40,130
也会追究麦克斯
They'll be coming for Max too.

939
01:25:41,590 --> 01:25:43,510
- 你真想这样 - 等等
- Is that really what you want? - Wait.

940
01:25:45,300 --> 01:25:46,640
你做什么啊
What are you doing?

941
01:25:47,850 --> 01:25:49,430
你疯了吗
Are you crazy?

942
01:25:56,110 --> 01:25:57,440
放我出去
Let me out!

943
01:25:57,610 --> 01:25:59,440
放我出去
Let me out of here!

944
01:26:09,790 --> 01:26:12,790
妈妈
Mom!

945
01:26:13,290 --> 01:26:18,340
是Saarne机构 S-A-A-R-N-E Saarne
It's called the Saarne Institute. S- A- A- R- N- E, Saarne.

946
01:26:18,500 --> 01:26:19,750
在爱沙尼亚
It's in Estonia.

947
01:26:19,920 --> 01:26:22,120
爱沙尼亚 不可能
Estonia? No, this can't be right.

948
01:26:22,120 --> 01:26:24,510
她的资料都来自于俄国
All of her paperwork is from Russia.

949
01:26:24,680 --> 01:26:27,100
我正给他们传照片
I'm sending them a picture of her right now.

950
01:26:27,260 --> 01:26:30,010
或许她的生母是那儿的病人
Maybe her birth mother was a patient there.

951
01:26:30,180 --> 01:26:32,770
或许她还出生在那儿
I don't know. Maybe she was even born there.

952
01:26:38,110 --> 01:26:40,150
妈妈
Mom!

953
01:26:40,940 --> 01:26:43,820
救命
Help!

954
01:26:59,960 --> 01:27:02,210
妈妈 爸爸
Mom! Dad!

955
01:27:09,600 --> 01:27:11,100
天哪
Oh, God!

956
01:27:20,360 --> 01:27:22,530
天哪 打911
Oh, God. Call 911!

957
01:27:34,410 --> 01:27:36,960
别担心 你要上天堂了
Don't worry. You're going to heaven.

958
01:27:39,670 --> 01:27:41,420
天哪
Oh, God!

959
01:27:43,760 --> 01:27:48,220
天哪 丹尼尔
Oh, my God! Daniel!

960
01:27:48,840 --> 01:27:51,260
快走开 别靠近大火
Move away! Move away from the fire!

961
01:27:51,430 --> 01:27:52,510
丹尼尔
Daniel?

962
01:27:52,680 --> 01:27:56,980
上帝啊 丹尼尔 妈妈来了 你能听见吗
Oh, God, no. Daniel? Mommy's right here. Can you hear me?

963
01:27:57,140 --> 01:28:00,150
快醒醒 亲爱的 妈妈就在这儿
Please wake up. Honey, Mommy's right here, okay?

964
01:28:00,310 --> 01:28:02,520
你会没事的
You're gonna be all right.

965
01:28:12,910 --> 01:28:14,940
腹部出血已止住
We stopped the abdominal bleeding,

966
01:28:14,940 --> 01:28:17,210
但他颈部受伤严重
but he has a very serious neck injury.

967
01:28:17,370 --> 01:28:18,840
目前情况稳定
He's stabilized for now.

968
01:28:18,840 --> 01:28:21,420
你们应该很庆幸
You should consider yourselves very lucky.

969
01:28:21,580 --> 01:28:23,960
- 我们能见见他吗 - 再过会儿
- Can we see him? - In a little while.

970
01:28:24,130 --> 01:28:26,090
他正在重症监护室
He's resting in the ICU.

971
01:28:26,260 --> 01:28:29,720
他能告诉我们事情经过吗
Okay. And will he be able to tell us what happened?

972
01:28:29,880 --> 01:28:31,430
有可能
It's possible.

973
01:28:31,590 --> 01:28:34,720
要等他醒来才能知道 他是否记得发生的事情
No way of knowing for sure what he'll remember until he wakes up.

974
01:28:35,470 --> 01:28:37,060
失陪
Excuse me.

975
01:28:39,850 --> 01:28:41,690
会没事的
It's gonna be okay.

976
01:28:45,440 --> 01:28:49,570
我知道你心力交瘁 我也是
I know you're exhausted and upset, and so am I.

977
01:28:49,740 --> 01:28:51,660
肯定有其他什么解释
There has to be some other explanation.

978
01:28:51,660 --> 01:28:53,530
她不会来自精神病院
She didn't come from an insane asylum.

979
01:28:53,700 --> 01:28:58,040
你所认为的孤儿院对她一无所知
The orphanage you thought she came from has never heard of her.

980
01:28:58,200 --> 01:28:59,960
她的一切可能就是个谎言 一切
Everything about her could be a lie. Everything.

981
01:29:00,120 --> 01:29:03,130
我们有她的护照 出生证明 学校档案 医档案
We have her passport. We have school records, medical records.

982
01:29:03,290 --> 01:29:05,420
她来自于半个地球以外的国家
These are papers from around the world.

983
01:29:05,590 --> 01:29:07,630
这是什么 就是一张纸
What is this? It's a piece of paper.

984
01:29:07,800 --> 01:29:09,790
这次你妈也在场
Your own mother was there this time.

985
01:29:09,790 --> 01:29:12,050
不是我胡乱猜测 你妈也在
It wasn't just me. Your mother was there.

986
01:29:12,680 --> 01:29:15,600
纵火的要么是艾斯特要么是丹尼尔
It's either Esther or Daniel who started the fire.

987
01:29:15,760 --> 01:29:18,520
- 你认为是谁 - 我不知道
- Who do you think it was? - I don't know.

988
01:29:18,680 --> 01:29:21,350
我受够了 不会再帮你串接这些疑点
I'm so done. I'm done connecting these dots for you.

989
01:29:21,520 --> 01:29:23,980
你爱怎么想我怎么想
You know, you can think whatever you want about me.

990
01:29:24,150 --> 01:29:25,190
如果你想
I will leave tonight.

991
01:29:25,190 --> 01:29:27,480
我今晚就可以离开
If that's what you want, I will leave tonight.

992
01:29:27,650 --> 01:29:29,900
但有一个条件 艾斯特也必须离开
On one condition. Esther goes too.

993
01:29:33,870 --> 01:29:36,080
能给我一美元去买汽水吗
Can I have a dollar for the soda machine?

994
01:29:36,580 --> 01:29:39,450
你妈让你待在这儿
Your mother wants you to stay right there.

995
01:29:45,840 --> 01:29:49,210
给你 别去太久
There you go. Don't be too long.

996
01:30:20,410 --> 01:30:22,400
我去找艾斯特

997
01:30:22,660 --> 01:30:24,170
好
Okay.

998
01:31:14,470 --> 01:31:15,930
怎么了 亲爱的
What? What is it, sweetie?

999
01:31:25,940 --> 01:31:28,100
重症监护室 心脏停跳
Code 99, ICU.

1000
01:31:28,270 --> 01:31:30,690
重症监护室 心脏停跳
Code 99, ICU.

1001
01:31:31,190 --> 01:31:33,480
- 让开 让开 - 妈 看着麦克斯
- Coming through, coming through. - Mom, take Max.

1002
01:31:33,650 --> 01:31:36,990
快去304房 急救车 让让
Let's go, Room 304! Crash cart coming through! Move, people!

1003
01:31:37,490 --> 01:31:39,530
- 丹尼尔 - 疏散走廊人群
- Daniel? - Clear the hall! Clear the hall!

1004
01:31:39,700 --> 01:31:42,910
你在外面等着 他心脏停跳 别进来
You have to stay out here. He's in cardiac arrest. Stay out here.

1005
01:31:43,080 --> 01:31:44,120
丹尼尔
Daniel!

1006
01:31:46,410 --> 01:31:47,620
- 开始 - 输液
- Here we go. - Start a drip.

1007
01:31:47,790 --> 01:31:49,750
- 检查血压 - 检查换气功能
- Check BP, please. - Check ventilation.

1008
01:31:49,920 --> 01:31:51,340
上帝啊
Oh, God.

1009
01:31:51,500 --> 01:31:54,130
有脉搏了
We got a pulse. We got a pulse.

1010
01:31:57,010 --> 01:31:58,050
凯特
Kate.

1011
01:31:59,090 --> 01:32:00,720
凯特
Kate.

1012
01:32:02,140 --> 01:32:05,520
你做了什么 你对他做了什么 贱货
What did you do? What did you do to him, you bitch?

1013
01:32:05,680 --> 01:32:06,770
住手
Stop, stop!

1014
01:32:06,930 --> 01:32:09,810
- 保安 保安 - 她要杀死我的孩子
- Orderlies! - She's trying to kill my baby!

1015
01:32:09,980 --> 01:32:11,440
- 爸爸 - 拉住她
- Daddy! - Hold her!

1016
01:32:11,610 --> 01:32:13,690
她想杀死我的孩子
She's trying to kill my baby!

1017
01:32:14,900 --> 01:32:16,190
拉住她
Hold her still.

1018
01:32:16,860 --> 01:32:18,530
放开我
Get off me.

1019
01:32:19,820 --> 01:32:21,950
拉住她 拉住她
Hold her still. Hold her still.

1020
01:32:22,530 --> 01:32:25,040
好了 别激动
Okay. Easy, easy.

1021
01:32:25,200 --> 01:32:27,460
- 你还好吗 - 没事了
- You okay? - There you go.

1022
01:32:31,990 --> 01:32:33,280
一个未接来电

1023
01:32:47,430 --> 01:32:50,520
- 凯特 - 丹尼尔
- Kate. - Daniel.

1024
01:32:50,690 --> 01:32:53,190
他们还在检查 明天才能知道结果
They're running tests. We should know more tomorrow.

1025
01:32:53,360 --> 01:32:55,570
别担心丹尼尔 他会没事的
Don't worry about Daniel. He'll be okay.

1026
01:32:56,820 --> 01:32:58,400
过几天就能回家了
He'll be home in a few days.

1027
01:32:58,570 --> 01:33:00,450
你要留在这里好好休息
You need to stay here, get some rest.

1028
01:33:00,610 --> 01:33:02,620
我带麦克斯和艾斯特回家
I'm gonna take Max and Esther home.

1029
01:33:02,780 --> 01:33:04,700
约翰
Johnny.

1030
01:33:06,290 --> 01:33:08,910
请别让她靠近麦克斯
Please don't let her near Max.

1031
01:33:11,960 --> 01:33:13,460
我爱你
I love you.

1032
01:33:36,470 --> 01:33:38,230
我爱你

1033
01:33:38,970 --> 01:33:40,030
丹尼会没事的

1034
01:33:53,160 --> 01:33:54,590
好梦

1035
01:34:12,160 --> 01:34:13,190
闭上眼睛

1036
01:35:46,360 --> 01:35:48,320
嗨 爸爸
Hello, Daddy.

1037
01:35:50,410 --> 01:35:52,950
- 你怎么穿成这样子 - 你喜欢吗
- What are you wearing? - Do you like it?

1038
01:35:54,910 --> 01:35:57,580
上帝啊
Oh, Jesus.

1039
01:36:03,210 --> 01:36:07,220
瞧瞧你 脸怎么抹成这样 这是干嘛
Look at you. What have you done to your face? What is this?

1040
01:36:10,050 --> 01:36:12,850
我不想一个人待着 我害怕
I don't want to be alone. I'm scared.

1041
01:36:20,100 --> 01:36:22,520
我爱你 爸爸
I love you, Daddy.

1042
01:36:22,690 --> 01:36:24,730
我也是 亲爱的
You too, hon.

1043
01:36:24,900 --> 01:36:26,360
我真的好爱你
I really love you.

1044
01:36:28,950 --> 01:36:30,660
我知道
I know.

1045
01:36:31,200 --> 01:36:32,240
我知道
I know.

1046
01:36:35,370 --> 01:36:37,830
约翰 让我照顾你
John, let me take care of you.

1047
01:36:38,330 --> 01:36:40,420
你在干嘛 干嘛呢
What are you doing? What are you doing?

1048
01:36:42,750 --> 01:36:47,550
你哪根筋不对了 这是做什么
What's gotten into you, huh? What's going on?

1049
01:36:51,970 --> 01:36:54,560
你说你爱我
You said you loved me.

1050
01:37:00,230 --> 01:37:03,440
你完全搞错了
You are so confused.

1051
01:37:04,320 --> 01:37:07,230
我对你不是那种爱
You know what? I don't love you like that.

1052
01:37:07,400 --> 01:37:10,700
那是凯特和我相爱的方式
That's the way Kate and I love each other.

1053
01:37:13,280 --> 01:37:14,870
明白吗
You understand?

1054
01:37:15,910 --> 01:37:17,660
没看出来
I don't see that.

1055
01:37:19,200 --> 01:37:21,710
- 你得尊重你妈 - 我尊重的
- You have to respect your mother. - I do.

1056
01:37:21,870 --> 01:37:25,380
我只是觉得只有我一人尊重你
I just feel like I'm alone sometimes in respecting you.

1057
01:37:25,540 --> 01:37:29,760
从没有其他人能体会你的感受
I don't think anyone ever thinks about what you might be feeling.

1058
01:37:29,920 --> 01:37:32,720
我真的很在乎你 约翰
I really care about you, John.

1059
01:37:32,890 --> 01:37:35,510
我知道 艾斯特
Yeah, I know, Esther.

1060
01:37:38,560 --> 01:37:41,190
我只是… 累了
I'm just... I'm tired.

1061
01:37:42,270 --> 01:37:45,020
非常累
I'm very tired.

1062
01:37:45,190 --> 01:37:47,270
我不知道该怎么做 太难了
And I don't know what to do. It's difficult.

1063
01:37:47,440 --> 01:37:50,070
一切都崩塌了
I mean, everything is just falling apart...

1064
01:37:50,240 --> 01:37:54,910
上帝啊 我好担心丹尼尔
...and, oh, my God, I'm so worried for Daniel.

1065
01:37:58,370 --> 01:38:00,410
上帝啊
Oh, God.

1066
01:38:00,910 --> 01:38:03,420
你是个好人 约翰
You're a good person, John.

1067
01:38:03,580 --> 01:38:05,880
是个好爸爸
You're a great father.

1068
01:38:07,340 --> 01:38:09,420
还是个帅气的男人
And a handsome man.

1069
01:38:12,800 --> 01:38:14,680
上帝啊
Jesus Christ!

1070
01:38:14,840 --> 01:38:16,600
天哪 快别这样
My God, stop, stop, stop!

1071
01:38:16,760 --> 01:38:19,430
什么都别说 上楼去 回你的房间
Just stop talking and go upstairs! Go to your room!

1072
01:38:19,600 --> 01:38:21,440
别把我当做小孩
Stop talking to me like I'm a child.

1073
01:38:21,440 --> 01:38:23,190
我明天就给朱迪丝修女打电话
I'm calling Sister Judith tomorrow.

1074
01:38:23,350 --> 01:38:26,270
讨论一下你的将来 我受不了
We're gonna have a conversation about your future in this house.

1075
01:38:26,440 --> 01:38:28,190
再也受不了了
I just... I can't do it anymore.

1076
01:38:30,110 --> 01:38:31,360
随你
Fine.

1077
01:38:34,780 --> 01:38:35,780
艾斯特
Esther.

1078
01:38:52,590 --> 01:38:56,510
- 喂 - 你是凯瑟琳·科尔曼吗
- Hello? - Is this Katherine Coleman?

1079
01:38:57,760 --> 01:38:59,850
- 喂 - 我是
- Hello? - Yeah. This is she.

1080
01:39:00,010 --> 01:39:03,480
我是Saarne机构的瓦拉瓦医生
My name is Dr. V?rava. I'm calling from the Saarne Institute.

1081
01:39:05,440 --> 01:39:07,520
我刚看了你传给我的照片
I've just seen the picture you e-mailed.

1082
01:39:07,520 --> 01:39:08,810
你认出她了吗
And do you recognize her?

1083
01:39:08,980 --> 01:39:12,690
她现在在哪儿 能听见你说话吗
Where is she right now? Is she someplace where she can hear you?

1084
01:39:12,860 --> 01:39:15,610
她不在我身边 正和我丈夫在家
No, she's not with me. She's with my husband at home.

1085
01:39:15,780 --> 01:39:17,510
马上打电话给你丈夫
Call your husband right now,

1086
01:39:17,510 --> 01:39:20,530
让他转移家人
and tell him to get your family out of the house.

1087
01:39:20,700 --> 01:39:24,790
- 然后报警 - 他不肯听我的 为什么报警
- And then call the police. - He won't listen to me. But why?

1088
01:39:24,960 --> 01:39:26,220
那就告诉他
Then tell him the little

1089
01:39:26,220 --> 01:39:28,750
照片里的不是真正的小女孩
girl in the picture is not really a little girl.

1090
01:39:28,920 --> 01:39:31,840
- 而是个成年女子 - 什么
- She's a grown woman. - What?

1091
01:39:32,000 --> 01:39:34,510
你说什么 我传给你的照片
What are you talking about? The picture I sent you...

1092
01:39:34,670 --> 01:39:38,470
是我们收养的女儿 她才9岁
...is of our adopted daughter, and she's 9 years old.

1093
01:39:38,640 --> 01:39:40,600
不是的
No, she's not.

1094
01:39:41,050 --> 01:39:45,730
她患有罕见的荷尔蒙失调症 又叫垂体机能减退
She has a rare hormone disorder. It's called hypopituitarism.

1095
01:39:45,890 --> 01:39:48,850
导致身材矮小 只是看上去像个孩子
It causes proportional dwarfism. She only looks like a child.

1096
01:39:49,400 --> 01:39:54,650
根据记录 丽娜 克莱姆生于1976年
According to our records, Leena Klammer was born in 1976.

1097
01:39:54,820 --> 01:39:56,780
今年33岁
She's 33 years old.

1098
01:39:56,950 --> 01:39:59,360
不可能 肯定弄错了
This can't be. This is a mistake.

1099
01:39:59,530 --> 01:40:02,740
为了你们的安全 我也希望如此 她有疤痕吗
I hope so, for your sake. Does she have the scars?

1100
01:40:02,910 --> 01:40:05,580
什么 我不知道 什么疤痕
What? I don't know. What scars?

1101
01:40:05,750 --> 01:40:08,170
丽娜是我们院最具暴力的病人之一
Leena was one of our most violent patients.

1102
01:40:08,330 --> 01:40:10,830
她在这儿时 我们给她穿拘束衣
When she was here, she was kept in a straitjacket...

1103
01:40:11,000 --> 01:40:12,840
防止她伤害到工作人员
...to stop her from hurting our staff.

1104
01:40:13,000 --> 01:40:15,010
但她总是不停挣扎想逃脱
She was constantly fighting to get out.

1105
01:40:15,170 --> 01:40:16,880
衣服勒入她的皮肤
It cut into her skin and

1106
01:40:16,880 --> 01:40:20,220
在腕部和颈部留下疤痕
left her with scars around her wrists and neck.

1107
01:40:20,390 --> 01:40:22,680
你们不可能看不到啊
There is no way you could not have seen them.

1108
01:40:22,850 --> 01:40:24,310
她为什么会在你们医院
Why was she at your hospital?

1109
01:40:24,470 --> 01:40:26,420
她非常危险暴力
She's dangerously ill, violent.

1110
01:40:26,420 --> 01:40:28,940
就我们所知已杀害七人
She killed seven people that we know of.

1111
01:40:29,100 --> 01:40:31,900
上帝啊 她怎么会骗得倒我们
Oh, my God. How could she fool us?

1112
01:40:32,060 --> 01:40:33,530
她很多时候
She has been passing herself

1113
01:40:33,530 --> 01:40:35,730
都是装成小女孩到处行骗
off as a little girl for most of her life.

1114
01:40:36,400 --> 01:40:39,450
爱沙尼亚的一户人家因为受骗收养她
She tricked a family here in Estonia into adopting her.

1115
01:40:39,610 --> 01:40:42,120
她勾引养父未遂
When she couldn't seduce the father,

1116
01:40:42,120 --> 01:40:44,620
就杀了他和他一家子
she killed him and his whole family.

1117
01:40:44,790 --> 01:40:48,330
- 然后还纵火烧了房子 - 是的 你怎么知道
- Then she burned the house down. - Yes. How did you know?

1118
01:40:48,500 --> 01:40:51,580
她一年前消失 杳无音讯
She disappeared a year ago and we lost track of her.

1119
01:40:51,750 --> 01:40:54,800
如果她真是丽娜 你得赶紧行动了
If it's really Leena, you don't have much time.

1120
01:41:35,920 --> 01:41:37,670
艾斯特
Esther?

1121
01:42:51,500 --> 01:42:54,580
拜托 约翰 快接电话啊
Come on, Johnny. Come on. Pick up the fucking phone.

1122
01:43:05,090 --> 01:43:06,890
他妈的
Shit.

1123
01:43:28,780 --> 01:43:30,490
快接啊
Come on.

1124
01:43:31,950 --> 01:43:33,160
天哪
Oh, God!

1125
01:44:05,610 --> 01:44:07,030
拜托
Come on.

1126
01:44:10,570 --> 01:44:11,620
快接
Come on.

1127
01:44:11,780 --> 01:44:13,490
911 什么事
911. What is your emergency?

1128
01:44:13,660 --> 01:44:16,620
我要报警 家中有人入侵
I need the police. We have an intruder in our home.

1129
01:44:50,070 --> 01:44:51,160
快接啊
Come on.

1130
01:44:51,440 --> 01:44:52,090
凯特来电

1131
01:44:52,300 --> 01:44:53,090
两个未接来电

1132
01:44:55,620 --> 01:44:57,000
- 我是约翰 - 约翰
- This is John. - John?

1133
01:44:57,160 --> 01:44:59,040
这是我的电话 目前无法接听
You've reached my cell, but I can't pick up.

1134
01:44:59,210 --> 01:45:00,540
该死的
Oh, fuck it.

1135
01:46:17,120 --> 01:46:18,830
约翰
John?

1136
01:46:24,000 --> 01:46:27,090
约翰 约翰
John? John?

1137
01:46:29,170 --> 01:46:31,800
不要啊 上帝
No, God!

1138
01:46:43,940 --> 01:46:45,770
不要啊 上帝
No, God!

1139
01:46:48,820 --> 01:46:50,150
麦克斯
Max.

1140
01:48:30,080 --> 01:48:31,920
搞什么
What the fuck?

1141
01:50:17,040 --> 01:50:18,700
就在那儿 别动

1142
01:50:28,640 --> 01:50:30,000
别动 就躲在那儿

1143
01:51:02,780 --> 01:51:05,530
艾斯特 不许伤害她
Esther! Don't you hurt her!

1144
01:51:11,120 --> 01:51:14,080
别伤害她 我在这儿
Leave her alone! I'm here!

1145
01:51:15,080 --> 01:51:16,670
艾斯特
Esther!

1146
01:52:47,220 --> 01:52:48,510
我知道
I know.

1147
01:54:43,960 --> 01:54:46,960
回去 太危险了 回去
Go back. It's too dangerous. Go back.

1148
01:55:00,600 --> 01:55:02,520
求你了
Please.

1149
01:55:02,680 --> 01:55:04,810
别让我死 妈妈
Don't let me die, Mommy.

1150
01:55:08,310 --> 01:55:11,860
我才不是你那该死的妈妈
I'm not your fucking Mommy!

1151
01:55:27,880 --> 01:55:30,130
宝贝 没事了
Baby, it's okay.

