7
00:00:00,500 --> 00:00:05,000
原创翻译  双语字幕

8
00:00:01,000 --> 00:00:05,000
最新连载海外影视剧下载
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com

9
00:00:06,000 --> 00:00:36,510
m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

10
00:00:05,500 --> 00:00:36,510
m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

11
00:00:06,510 --> 00:00:11,510
翻译     海云生  tong大梨  glida

12
00:00:11,510 --> 00:00:16,510
翻译     吃冰棒  木浅  布塔

13
00:00:16,510 --> 00:00:21,510
校对     布塔

14
00:00:21,510 --> 00:00:26,510
时间轴   西·查  啾  没有影子  紫夏

15
00:00:26,510 --> 00:00:31,510
后期     渔夫

16
00:00:31,510 --> 00:00:36,510
总监     布塔

17
00:00:51,410 --> 00:00:52,970
故事可以治愈
Stories heal.

18
00:00:53,280 --> 00:00:54,680
故事可以伤人
Stories hurt.

19
00:00:55,120 --> 00:00:57,350
只要讲的次数够多
If we repeat them often enough,

20
00:00:57,580 --> 00:00:58,690
它们就会成真
they become real.

21
00:00:59,080 --> 00:01:00,690
它们塑造我们
They make us who we are.

22
00:01:01,080 --> 00:01:03,150
它们有这种力量
They have such power.

23
00:01:03,710 --> 00:01:05,080
这是我在
This I learned

24
00:01:05,090 --> 00:01:07,900
童年最后的秋天里学到的
on the very last autumn of our childhood.

25
00:01:14,390 --> 00:01:17,640
欢迎来到
宾夕法尼亚州  造纸谷

26
00:01:16,180 --> 00:01:17,930
是时候把自己从坟墓里
Now it's time to dig yourselves

27
00:01:17,930 --> 00:01:19,930
挖出来了  造纸谷
out of your graves, Mill Valley.

28
00:01:19,930 --> 00:01:21,750
万圣节到了
It's Halloween.

29
00:01:21,890 --> 00:01:25,380
但是小心  太阳下山后
But be careful, 'cause when the sun goes down,

30
00:01:24,430 --> 00:01:26,140
WNXC音像店

31
00:01:25,610 --> 00:01:28,220
就是女巫的季节
it's The Season of the Witch.

32
00:01:27,280 --> 00:01:28,580
造纸烤肉出品

33
00:01:29,300 --> 00:01:30,450
投票给尼克松
尼克松总统  阿格纽副总统
[涂鸦是骂尼克松是纳粹]

34
00:01:30,500 --> 00:01:32,320
投票不如呕吐

35
00:01:32,350 --> 00:01:33,810
高音部唱片

36
00:01:33,810 --> 00:01:35,990
参军

37
00:01:37,200 --> 00:01:40,480
我做到了  我要去越南了
I did it. I'm going to 'Nam. Yeah.

38
00:01:40,540 --> 00:01:41,900
让共产党好看
Those commies are gonna pay.

39
00:01:41,450 --> 00:01:42,910
美国陆军征兵站

40
00:01:43,870 --> 00:01:46,480
伙计们  今晚去吓唬小屁孩吧
Let's go scare some kiddies tonight, guys.

41
00:02:03,770 --> 00:02:05,960
让全世界人民
But let men everywhere

42
00:02:06,310 --> 00:02:09,550
-认识到美国强大  -谢谢
- know that a strong and a confident... - Thanks.

43
00:02:10,190 --> 00:02:11,480
自信而勇敢
...and a vigilant America...

44
00:02:11,490 --> 00:02:12,890
今晚要和朋友们出去吗
Going out with your friends tonight?

45
00:02:14,110 --> 00:02:15,720
我宁愿待在家里
I'd rather just stay in.

46
00:02:17,240 --> 00:02:19,140
随时准备着
...and stand ready tonight

47
00:02:19,830 --> 00:02:22,270
为伟大事业抗争
to defend an honored cause.

48
00:02:26,870 --> 00:02:27,480
吸血鬼蝙蝠
[1933年电影]

49
00:02:27,500 --> 00:02:28,540
弗兰肯斯坦之女
[1958年电影]

50
00:02:29,790 --> 00:02:30,350
看不见的幽灵
[1941年电影]

51
00:02:30,400 --> 00:02:30,970
不死之人
[1956年电影]

52
00:02:33,330 --> 00:02:36,090
呼啸房间
作者  斯黛拉·尼科尔斯

53
00:02:37,260 --> 00:02:38,200
斯黛拉  回话
Stella, pick up.

54
00:02:41,680 --> 00:02:42,830
斯黛拉
Stella...

55
00:02:42,970 --> 00:02:44,790
我不想去玩"不给糖就捣蛋"
I don't want to go trick-or-treating.

56
00:02:45,520 --> 00:02:46,440
斯泰拉  斯泰拉
Stella. Stella,

57
00:02:46,440 --> 00:02:48,810
我们不是为了要糖  是为了报复
this isn't about candy. It's about payback.

58
00:02:48,810 --> 00:02:51,340
搜集你能找到的所有鸡蛋和卫生纸
Get all the eggs and TP you can

59
00:02:51,480 --> 00:02:53,050
七点和我们碰头
and meet us at 7:00.

60
00:02:53,320 --> 00:02:54,570
斯泰拉  拜托
Stella, please.

61
00:02:54,570 --> 00:02:56,510
这可能是我们一起过的最后一个万圣节了
This could be our last Halloween together.

62
00:02:57,410 --> 00:02:58,610
这点事你都觉得困难
If you think you have it hard,

63
00:02:58,620 --> 00:03:00,560
我可是得从马桶里捞大便
I have to fish a turd out of the toilet.

64
00:03:01,080 --> 00:03:02,390
你真恶心  查克
You are disgusting, Chuck.

65
00:03:02,740 --> 00:03:07,200
美国加油站

66
00:03:12,090 --> 00:03:13,610
小子  你知道自己要去哪吗
You know where you're going, kid?

67
00:03:15,470 --> 00:03:16,660
哪有农活干就去哪
Following the harvest.

68
00:03:21,680 --> 00:03:22,830
仅限今晚
Tonight only.

69
00:03:23,220 --> 00:03:25,600
万圣节
活死人之夜

70
00:03:31,190 --> 00:03:32,670
妈  已经好了
Mom. It's fine.

71
00:03:32,860 --> 00:03:34,180
没好
No, it's not.

72
00:03:35,030 --> 00:03:36,680
裆部还是有点松
Still a little loose in the crotch.

73
00:03:37,610 --> 00:03:38,600
再缝一下
One more.

74
00:03:41,050 --> 00:03:42,270
接我一招
Take that!

75
00:03:43,450 --> 00:03:44,560
正中红心
Bullseye.

76
00:03:49,210 --> 00:03:50,730
走吧  姑娘们
Let's go, girls.

77
00:03:54,380 --> 00:03:55,410
给我
Hey, gimme.

78
00:03:58,840 --> 00:04:00,240
吃屎吧  哈罗德
Eat shit, Harold.

79
00:04:07,430 --> 00:04:09,040
汤米  慢点开
Tommy, slow down.

80
00:04:18,820 --> 00:04:19,820
你到底在干什么
What the hell are you doing?

81
00:04:19,820 --> 00:04:21,640
能不能有点隐私了
A little privacy, please!

82
00:04:27,910 --> 00:04:29,410
我是说蜘蛛侠
I said Spider-Man.

83
00:04:29,410 --> 00:04:31,690
不是蜘蛛...
Not a spider...

84
00:04:31,920 --> 00:04:32,750
人
man.

85
00:04:32,750 --> 00:04:34,650
人要知足
Be happy the Lord provided.

86
00:04:47,100 --> 00:04:49,020
妈  行了
Mom, okay, jeez.

87
00:04:49,020 --> 00:04:50,710
妈  能让我喘口气吗
Mom, can I please breathe?

88
00:04:51,600 --> 00:04:52,560
-乖一点  -好
- Be nice. - Okay!

89
00:04:52,560 --> 00:04:54,550
但你能不能别那样抱我了
Can you please stop hugging me like that?

90
00:04:55,230 --> 00:04:57,470
你玩"不给糖就捣蛋"是不是老了一点
Aren't you a little old to be trick-or-treating?

91
00:05:02,200 --> 00:05:04,890
你出门约会是不是丑了一点
Aren't you too ugly to go on a date?

92
00:05:05,990 --> 00:05:06,950
你这小混蛋
You little turd.

93
00:05:06,950 --> 00:05:08,390
奥吉来了  我走了
Auggie's here, gotta run.

94
00:05:09,370 --> 00:05:10,120
你闭嘴
I don't wanna hear it.

95
00:05:10,120 --> 00:05:11,690
我以为你会打扮成蜘蛛侠
Thought you were gonna be Spider-Man.

96
00:05:11,790 --> 00:05:13,790
是啊  看多了就习惯了
Yeah, well, get used to it, okay.

97
00:05:13,790 --> 00:05:16,240
东西准备好了  好戏可以开始了
I got the goods, so let's banana split.

98
00:05:21,720 --> 00:05:23,680
别盯着我姐姐看  你这变态
Stop staring at my sister, you perv.

99
00:05:47,490 --> 00:05:48,490
你就不能消停一下
Hey, can you not?

100
00:05:48,490 --> 00:05:50,240
这些触须一点也不逼真
I mean, these antennae aren't even realistic.

101
00:05:50,250 --> 00:05:52,580
再说了  蜘蛛人
And, if anything, a spider man

102
00:05:52,580 --> 00:05:54,120
应该有八条腿  而不是四条
should have eight arms, not four.

103
00:05:54,120 --> 00:05:57,110
行吧  最起码我没打扮成小丑
Okay. At least I'm not a clown.

104
00:05:58,250 --> 00:06:00,700
最后说一次  我是男丑角
For the last time, I'm a Pierrot.

105
00:06:01,800 --> 00:06:04,830
这是十七世纪即兴喜剧里面的一种角色
It's a 17th-century character from la commedia dell'arte.

106
00:06:05,550 --> 00:06:06,580
小丑
Clown.

107
00:06:09,390 --> 00:06:10,600
你知道那都含有什么成分吗
Do you even know what's in those?

108
00:06:10,600 --> 00:06:13,100
就是那些化学毒物让我们部队得霍奇金淋巴瘤
It's the same toxic chemicals that's giving our troops Hodgkin's lymphoma

109
00:06:13,100 --> 00:06:15,560
让南越南妇女乳汁结块
and curdling the breast milk of the South Vietnamese.

110
00:06:15,560 --> 00:06:16,670
你还都吃掉了
And you ate them all.

111
00:06:17,650 --> 00:06:20,150
所以才这么好吃的吗
Is that why they taste so good?

112
00:06:20,150 --> 00:06:21,360
让开  小丑
Out of the way, clown.

113
00:06:21,360 --> 00:06:22,840
书呆子
Nerd!

114
00:06:23,320 --> 00:06:24,220
让开
Move!

115
00:06:24,990 --> 00:06:27,140
-他不会来了  -什么  不  他会来的
- He's not gonna show. - What? No, he'll show.

116
00:06:27,490 --> 00:06:29,230
米尔纳每年都这么做
Okay, Milner does it every year

117
00:06:29,370 --> 00:06:31,060
今年是他最后一次了
and this year will be his last.

118
00:06:31,910 --> 00:06:33,270
你在哪呢  汤米
Where are you, Tommy?

119
00:06:34,040 --> 00:06:36,250
我听说校报
I heard the school newspaper

120
00:06:36,250 --> 00:06:37,820
又开始征稿了
is open to submissions again.

121
00:06:38,250 --> 00:06:39,540
你应该投几篇你写的故事
You should submit some of your stories.

122
00:06:39,540 --> 00:06:42,490
-来偷我们的糖果啊  汤米  -不可能
- Come and steal our candy, Tommy. - No way.

123
00:06:43,130 --> 00:06:44,280
我了解我们学校
I know our school.

124
00:06:45,180 --> 00:06:47,080
他们会把我生吞活剥的
They would disembowel me.

125
00:06:48,390 --> 00:06:50,910
庞蒂亚克卡塔里纳  是他  是他  好
Pontiac Catalina. It's him, it's him! Okay.

126
00:06:52,470 --> 00:06:54,250
好  自然点
Okay, just act natural.

127
00:06:58,440 --> 00:07:00,050
你说我们要去吃晚餐
You said we'd go out for dinner.

128
00:07:01,270 --> 00:07:02,340
就我们两人
You and me.

129
00:07:02,860 --> 00:07:04,680
吃点甜点如何
How about some dessert?

130
00:07:04,860 --> 00:07:06,180
准备好  兄弟
Get ready, man.

131
00:07:09,030 --> 00:07:10,220
笨蛋
Suckers!

132
00:07:11,740 --> 00:07:12,940
这是什么味道
What's that smell?

133
00:07:12,990 --> 00:07:14,770
是老头的内裤
It's old-man undies!

134
00:07:16,540 --> 00:07:17,270
他中招了
We got him.

135
00:07:18,670 --> 00:07:20,210
好  开始了  我们上  我们上
All right, here we go. Let's do this. Let's do this!

136
00:07:20,210 --> 00:07:21,860
欺负这个吧  混蛋
Bully this, asshole!

137
00:07:24,920 --> 00:07:25,870
混蛋们
Douchebags!

138
00:07:26,720 --> 00:07:29,160
该死的  这些小混球
God damn it! Those little shits.

139
00:07:33,010 --> 00:07:35,500
现在是政便时刻
And now for the poo d'etat.

140
00:07:37,100 --> 00:07:38,790
吃屎吧  鸟人
Eat turd, shitbird!

141
00:07:39,980 --> 00:07:41,020
该死
Holy shit.

142
00:07:41,020 --> 00:07:42,800
-停车  -扑灭它
- Stop the car! - Put it out!

143
00:07:49,240 --> 00:07:49,780
露丝怎么在车上
What is Ruth doing here?

144
00:07:49,780 --> 00:07:51,410
小查  你这小混蛋
Chucky, you little brat!

145
00:07:51,410 --> 00:07:53,490
我不知道  我以为她是出门和别的人约会
I don't know. I knew she was going on a date but not with him.

146
00:07:53,490 --> 00:07:54,390
该死的
Damn it!

147
00:07:55,580 --> 00:07:57,310
我要杀了他们
I'm gonna murder them!

148
00:07:58,040 --> 00:07:58,940
回来
Come back!

149
00:08:03,460 --> 00:08:04,200
快跑
Go!

150
00:08:05,800 --> 00:08:07,240
你们给我等着
I'm going to get you!

151
00:08:08,800 --> 00:08:09,830
抓住他们
Let's get 'em!

152
00:08:10,760 --> 00:08:12,080
快  伙计们  快跑
Come on, guys, go!

153
00:08:18,100 --> 00:08:19,060
在那边  抓住他
Over there! Get him!

154
00:08:19,060 --> 00:08:20,840
九点方向有混蛋
Douchebags, nine o'clock!

155
00:08:21,930 --> 00:08:24,020
中场时间  来点小吃

156
00:08:29,490 --> 00:08:30,360
在树林后面
...behind those tree

157
00:08:30,360 --> 00:08:31,640
要是你想检查一下的话
if you want to go check it out.

158
00:08:49,550 --> 00:08:51,120
往前走  往前走
Go ahead. Go ahead.

159
00:08:51,630 --> 00:08:52,660
这里有人坐吗
Is this seat taken?

160
00:08:53,090 --> 00:08:54,870
我不...看来没人
I don't... guess not.

161
00:08:57,390 --> 00:08:58,470
滚出我的车
Hey, get out of my car.

162
00:08:58,470 --> 00:08:59,930
拜托  拜托
Please, please.

163
00:08:59,930 --> 00:09:00,770
我们马上就走
Be out of here in a minute.

164
00:09:00,770 --> 00:09:01,750
谢谢了
Thanks, okay.

165
00:09:05,940 --> 00:09:06,770
你们干什么呢
What are you guys doing?

166
00:09:06,770 --> 00:09:08,380
我们在避难
We're saving our bacon.

167
00:09:10,030 --> 00:09:10,720
抱歉
Sorry.

168
00:09:12,280 --> 00:09:14,140
好了  好了  没事了
Okay, okay. We're good.

169
00:09:14,370 --> 00:09:15,640
-没事了  -他走了
- We're good? - He's gone.

170
00:09:18,580 --> 00:09:20,350
谢了  欠你个人情
Thanks. We owe you one.

171
00:09:24,210 --> 00:09:25,400
我扮的是男丑角
I am a Pierrot.

172
00:09:32,550 --> 00:09:33,580
你住在车里
You live in here?

173
00:09:35,430 --> 00:09:36,540
别碰我的东西
Stay out of my stuff.

174
00:09:37,680 --> 00:09:38,710
知道了
Got it.

175
00:09:40,930 --> 00:09:43,500
你怎么一个人在汽车电影院
So, what are you doing alone at a drive-in?

176
00:09:44,060 --> 00:09:45,460
你们怎么还在我的车里
What are you still doing in my car?

177
00:09:45,560 --> 00:09:46,710
我能看出
I understand you're...

178
00:09:46,980 --> 00:09:49,300
你不是本地人  对吗
You're not from here, are you?

179
00:09:49,320 --> 00:09:50,840
你是哪里人
Where are you from?

180
00:09:51,490 --> 00:09:52,690
请原谅我的朋友
Forgive my friend.

181
00:09:52,700 --> 00:09:54,820
他出生前大脑就缺氧
He did not get enough oxygen in the womb.

182
00:09:54,820 --> 00:09:55,820
总比你强  小丑
More than you, clown.

183
00:09:55,820 --> 00:09:57,430
你们能不能消停一下
Can you guys stop?

184
00:09:57,450 --> 00:09:58,480
是他的错  不是我
It's him, not me.

185
00:09:59,200 --> 00:10:00,390
我们消停了
Yeah, we're stopping.

186
00:10:01,620 --> 00:10:03,440
你的朋友有点聒噪
Your friend is a little nosy.

187
00:10:10,170 --> 00:10:11,280
《活死人之夜》
Night of the Living Dead.

188
00:10:12,170 --> 00:10:13,070
是部好片子
It's a good flick.

189
00:10:13,630 --> 00:10:14,490
你看过吗
You've seen it?

190
00:10:15,430 --> 00:10:18,050
"好  文斯  照头打"
"All right, Vince, hit him in the head,

191
00:10:18,050 --> 00:10:19,750
"瞄准两眼中间"
"right between the eyes."

192
00:10:20,350 --> 00:10:21,890
这是最棒的片子
That's the best flick all year.

193
00:10:21,890 --> 00:10:24,460
对  对  的确  的确
Yeah, yeah, it's... it is.

194
00:10:26,770 --> 00:10:27,550
我是雷蒙
Ramon.

195
00:10:28,520 --> 00:10:29,380
我是斯黛拉
Stella.

196
00:10:33,280 --> 00:10:34,300
我是查克
Chuck.

197
00:10:34,360 --> 00:10:35,220
我是奥吉
Auggie.

198
00:10:38,240 --> 00:10:39,270
下车
Get out of the car.

199
00:10:39,330 --> 00:10:40,480
下车
Get out of the car.

200
00:10:42,660 --> 00:10:43,810
下车
Get out of the car.

201
00:10:52,550 --> 00:10:54,410
你们似乎没听见
I don't think that you heard me.

202
00:10:55,170 --> 00:10:57,660
所有人都下车
Everyone needs to get out.

203
00:10:58,180 --> 00:10:59,080
马上
Now.

204
00:10:59,930 --> 00:11:01,160
你也是
You too,

205
00:11:02,390 --> 00:11:03,710
湿背客
wetback.

206
00:11:02,850 --> 00:11:04,670
指偷渡的墨西哥人

207
00:11:09,770 --> 00:11:11,060
你不会像你妈妈一样
You're not going to try and run away

208
00:11:11,070 --> 00:11:13,340
想要跑掉吧  斯黛拉
like Mommy too, now are you, Stella?

209
00:11:22,700 --> 00:11:24,060
你一股大便味
You smell like shit.

210
00:11:27,370 --> 00:11:28,980
别碰我的车
Get the hell off my car.

211
00:11:33,630 --> 00:11:36,200
前面那个  你们挡住屏幕了
Hey, down in front. You're blocking the view!

212
00:11:36,630 --> 00:11:37,780
让开
Come on!

213
00:11:38,380 --> 00:11:39,910
我看不到电影了
I can't see the movie!

214
00:11:40,470 --> 00:11:42,960
要么回你车上  要么滚蛋
Get back in your car or get the hell out of here!

215
00:11:46,180 --> 00:11:47,330
这事没完
This ain't over.

216
00:11:48,230 --> 00:11:49,060
快点
Let's go.

217
00:11:49,060 --> 00:11:50,550
快滚  你这白痴
Move it, you idiot.

218
00:11:50,900 --> 00:11:51,840
快点
Let's go.

219
00:11:54,610 --> 00:11:56,280
回你车上去  快点
Get back in your car. Let's go. Come on.

220
00:11:56,280 --> 00:11:57,510
好  走吧
Okay, let's go.

221
00:11:59,240 --> 00:12:00,100
我们去哪边
Where we goin'?

222
00:12:00,200 --> 00:12:01,020
那边
That way.

223
00:12:01,030 --> 00:12:02,730
好  我们一起去
Okay, we'll go together.

224
00:12:04,370 --> 00:12:05,310
你还好吗
You okay?

225
00:12:06,830 --> 00:12:08,940
失陪片刻
Just excuse me for a second.

226
00:12:11,250 --> 00:12:12,570
是我说错话了吗
Did I say something?

227
00:12:13,500 --> 00:12:15,860
不  是那个混蛋汤米说的话
No, that asshole, Tommy did.

228
00:12:17,550 --> 00:12:21,240
她妈妈在她小时候就丢下她离开了
Her mom left when she was a kid, just like that.

229
00:12:21,640 --> 00:12:24,050
人们还是不停地谈论这件事
Yeah, people wouldn't stop talking about it, though.

230
00:12:24,060 --> 00:12:25,430
你也知道  我们住的这个镇子很小
You know, we live in a small town.

231
00:12:25,430 --> 00:12:27,330
这些闲话说得很刻薄
Yeah, the gossip got really mean.

232
00:12:27,730 --> 00:12:28,580
天呐
Jeez.

233
00:12:29,890 --> 00:12:31,440
但是这件事还是会让她难受
Yeah, but it still bothers her,

234
00:12:31,440 --> 00:12:33,610
我猜这种事大概永远都无法忘怀吧
so I guess that stuff sort of sticks with you.

235
00:12:33,610 --> 00:12:36,130
现在我们差不多是她仅有的朋友了
Yeah, and we're like her only friends now.

236
00:12:42,700 --> 00:12:44,950
要我说她绝对不和你的胃口
So, I would say she's definitely not your type.

237
00:12:44,950 --> 00:12:47,020
她可是斯黛拉  肯定谁的胃口都对不上
It's Stella. She's not anyone's type.

238
00:12:47,250 --> 00:12:49,360
这点我可不同意
Don't think I'd agree with that.

239
00:12:49,500 --> 00:12:51,730
所有的妹子你都喜欢  这可不算
You like every girl. It doesn't count.

240
00:12:51,830 --> 00:12:52,900
也不是所有都喜欢
It's not every girl.

241
00:12:53,580 --> 00:12:55,610
你至少有把弹簧刀之类的吧
Tell me you at least you got a switchblade.

242
00:12:56,550 --> 00:12:58,030
我能看看你的弹簧刀吗
Can I see your switchblade?

243
00:12:58,420 --> 00:13:00,120
我说过我有弹簧刀吗
Did I say I had a switchblade?

244
00:13:00,550 --> 00:13:03,950
不  你没说你有
No, I guess you didn't say you had...

245
00:13:04,970 --> 00:13:06,620
-他有弹簧刀  -我知道
- He has a switchblade. - I know.

246
00:13:13,810 --> 00:13:16,550
今天是万圣节  所以
Well, it is Halloween, so...

247
00:13:17,480 --> 00:13:18,800
你想去鬼屋瞧瞧吗
Do you want to see a haunted house?

248
00:13:37,130 --> 00:13:38,070
你没还真没开玩笑
You weren't kidding.

249
00:13:38,800 --> 00:13:40,320
跟你说了不会失望的
Told you it wouldn't disappoint.

250
00:13:41,370 --> 00:13:44,690
禁止闯入
私人住宅
违者将被起诉

251
00:13:43,970 --> 00:13:46,330
我还以为在万圣节  这个地方会很受欢迎
I don't know, you'd think on Halloween, this place would be hoppin'.

252
00:13:46,510 --> 00:13:48,500
以前火过一段
It was, for a while,

253
00:13:48,560 --> 00:13:51,170
然后有孩子失踪了  他们就把这围起来了
then some kid went missing, so they boarded it up.

254
00:13:51,270 --> 00:13:54,040
我觉得这里会拆掉建商场什么的
I think it's being torn down for a mall or something.

255
00:13:55,230 --> 00:13:56,090
各位
Hey, guys.

256
00:14:02,820 --> 00:14:03,930
小丑优先
Clowns first.

257
00:14:04,570 --> 00:14:05,260
不是吧
Really?

258
00:14:20,420 --> 00:14:21,860
行了  我们看见了
Okay, there, we saw it.

259
00:14:22,630 --> 00:14:23,490
可以走了吗
Can we go now?

260
00:14:24,050 --> 00:14:25,580
谁叫了胆小鬼过来
Who ordered the chicken?

261
00:14:25,590 --> 00:14:27,640
不喜欢晚上待在杀害那些孩子的凶手家
Because I don't like to spend my nights in a house

262
00:14:27,640 --> 00:14:29,160
我就成了胆小鬼吗
where a child murderer lived?

263
00:14:29,970 --> 00:14:31,370
有人在这栋房子里被杀了吗
Someone was killed in that house?

264
00:14:31,930 --> 00:14:33,080
太黑暗了
That's pretty dark.

265
00:14:33,770 --> 00:14:34,710
以前谁住在这
Who lived here?

266
00:14:34,770 --> 00:14:35,980
贝洛斯一家
The Bellows.

267
00:14:35,980 --> 00:14:38,230
最先在这里定居的几大家族之一
One of the first families to settle here

268
00:14:38,230 --> 00:14:40,090
在十九世纪末期
in the late 19th century.

269
00:14:40,320 --> 00:14:42,070
建了一家造纸厂
Built the paper mill that pretty much

270
00:14:42,070 --> 00:14:43,590
真是让这个镇子出了名
put this town on the map.

271
00:14:46,320 --> 00:14:47,970
就不能去找找台阶吗
We could at least look for some stairs.

272
00:14:52,160 --> 00:14:53,100
和我想的一样
Just as I thought.

273
00:14:53,620 --> 00:14:55,770
他们把这里锁得严严实实
They got this place locked up pretty tight.

274
00:14:55,960 --> 00:14:57,230
有人带笔了吗
Anyone got a pen?

275
00:14:58,880 --> 00:15:01,960
来认识一下洛拉  她疯狂地爱着我
Meet Lola. She is madly in love with me.

276
00:15:01,960 --> 00:15:03,360
可能是爱你的手吧
Yeah, your hand maybe.

277
00:15:04,130 --> 00:15:05,160
不错
Nice.

278
00:15:05,420 --> 00:15:07,280
洛拉  干什么
Lola! Hey, what?

279
00:15:18,900 --> 00:15:21,550
他比你有魅力多了
He's so much dreamier than you.

280
00:15:34,910 --> 00:15:36,500
贝洛斯一家有个秘密
The Bellows had a secret:

281
00:15:36,500 --> 00:15:39,650
他们有个女儿  从没允许她踏出过家门一步
a daughter that they never allowed to leave the house.

282
00:15:39,710 --> 00:15:42,460
传说中她有一些很严重的问题
The myth is that there was something really off about her.

283
00:15:42,460 --> 00:15:43,920
真正恐怖的部分是
A really scary part

284
00:15:43,920 --> 00:15:47,570
她的家人把她从每张照片上都清除掉了
is that her family erased her from every single portrait.

285
00:15:47,840 --> 00:15:52,040
直到今天  也没人找到一张莎拉的照片
To this day, nobody's ever found a picture of Sarah.

286
00:15:57,560 --> 00:15:58,880
他们不认她
They disowned her.

287
00:16:03,820 --> 00:16:04,630
-快跑啊  小丑  -靠
- Better run, clown. - Shit!

288
00:16:04,650 --> 00:16:05,590
快跑
Better run!

289
00:16:08,990 --> 00:16:10,560
我打赌你抓不到我
Bet you can't catch me!

290
00:16:13,120 --> 00:16:14,330
查克  如果你跳出来吓我
Chuck, if you jump out at me,

291
00:16:14,330 --> 00:16:16,020
我就一拳打在你喉咙上
I'm going to punch you in the throat.

292
00:16:17,290 --> 00:16:18,770
那她后来怎么了
So what happened to her?

293
00:16:19,250 --> 00:16:21,290
各个地方的孩子都跑过来
Kids would come from all over

294
00:16:21,290 --> 00:16:23,860
希望能瞟到怪人莎拉一眼
in hopes to get a peek at Strange Sarah.

295
00:16:23,880 --> 00:16:25,860
尽管他们看不到她
And though they never saw her,

296
00:16:26,380 --> 00:16:27,740
他们可以听到她的声音
they could hear her.

297
00:16:28,630 --> 00:16:29,830
透过墙壁
Through the wall.

298
00:16:32,050 --> 00:16:33,870
莎拉给他们讲故事
Sarah told them stories.

299
00:16:35,260 --> 00:16:36,750
恐怖故事
Scary stories.

300
00:16:40,650 --> 00:16:42,630
有些孩子再也没回家
Some kids never returned home.

301
00:16:42,690 --> 00:16:44,690
镇里好多孩子死了
Children around town died...

302
00:16:44,690 --> 00:16:46,090
他们说是中毒
Poisoned, they said.

303
00:16:47,070 --> 00:16:48,680
大家都知道是莎拉干的
Everyone knew it was Sarah.

304
00:16:49,030 --> 00:16:51,780
但是他们还没来得及碰到莎拉一根手指头
But before the mob could even get their hands on her,

305
00:16:51,780 --> 00:16:53,560
她就把自己吊死了
she'd already hung herself

306
00:16:54,120 --> 00:16:55,600
用她自己的头发
with her own hair.

307
00:17:06,750 --> 00:17:08,360
根据传说
And as the legend goes,

308
00:17:08,840 --> 00:17:11,450
如果你在天黑之后来贝洛斯家
if you come to the Bellows House at dark,

309
00:17:11,760 --> 00:17:13,450
让莎拉给你讲个故事
and ask Sarah to tell you a story...

310
00:17:14,470 --> 00:17:16,870
那将是你这辈子听到的最后一个故事
it'll be the last story you ever hear.

311
00:17:27,400 --> 00:17:28,470
这是什么
What's this?

312
00:17:35,910 --> 00:17:36,980
推另一边
Push the other way.

313
00:17:37,450 --> 00:17:38,440
推
Push.

314
00:17:42,120 --> 00:17:43,150
不是吧
No way.

315
00:18:26,330 --> 00:18:28,610
就到这了
Well, that's it.

316
00:18:50,400 --> 00:18:51,550
莎拉的房间
Sarah's room.

317
00:18:55,280 --> 00:18:57,100
你吓不到我
You're not going to scare me.

318
00:19:01,870 --> 00:19:02,810
查克
Chuck?

319
00:19:06,580 --> 00:19:07,690
查克
Chuck?

320
00:19:29,520 --> 00:19:30,710
什么鬼
What the...

321
00:20:06,520 --> 00:20:08,420
什么  那个老太太去哪了
What? Where's the old lady?

322
00:20:09,980 --> 00:20:10,900
还有那条狗
And the dog?

323
00:20:10,900 --> 00:20:11,800
什么老太太
What old lady?

324
00:20:14,860 --> 00:20:16,010
我们得赶紧离开
We gotta get out of here.

325
00:20:16,820 --> 00:20:19,680
斯黛拉  斯黛拉  我们得赶紧出去
Stella! Stella! We got to get out of here!

326
00:20:20,160 --> 00:20:21,470
斯黛拉  咱们走吧
Stella, let's go!

327
00:20:22,240 --> 00:20:24,730
各位  你们得来看看这个  过来
Guys, you've gotta see this! Come here.

328
00:20:31,580 --> 00:20:33,250
是谁叫胆小鬼过来了
Who ordered the chicken?

329
00:20:33,250 --> 00:20:34,360
闭嘴
Shut up.

330
00:20:38,010 --> 00:20:39,620
她的家人就是把她关在这里的
This is where her family kept her.

331
00:20:40,050 --> 00:20:42,290
把她锁起来  与世隔离
Locked her away from the world.

332
00:20:42,550 --> 00:20:45,120
孤身一人  像个怪物
All alone as some sort of freak.

333
00:20:45,220 --> 00:20:48,710
她肯定就是坐在这里
She must have just sat right here

334
00:20:49,480 --> 00:20:52,130
透过这面墙壁给孩子们讲故事
and told her stories to the kids through this wall.

335
00:20:53,270 --> 00:20:55,300
我们之前怎么没来这里看过
How have we never seen this before?

336
00:20:56,690 --> 00:20:59,180
我觉得应该没人想让我们看到
I don't think anyone wanted us to?

337
00:21:18,900 --> 00:21:20,670
莎·贝

338
00:21:21,300 --> 00:21:22,530
我们能走了吗
Can we get out of here now?

339
00:21:43,740 --> 00:21:44,600
那是什么
What's that?

340
00:21:49,570 --> 00:21:53,500
莎拉·贝洛斯的书

341
00:21:50,960 --> 00:21:52,150
真不敢相信
I can't believe it.

342
00:21:53,040 --> 00:21:54,860
这是她的恐怖故事书
It's her book of scary stories.

343
00:21:55,880 --> 00:21:56,790
她还有本书
She had a book?

344
00:21:56,790 --> 00:21:59,170
我听到的那个传说版本里没提到书
There's no book in the version of the myth I heard.

345
00:21:59,170 --> 00:22:01,240
每个版本里都提到了这本书
The book is a part of every version of the myth.

346
00:22:01,970 --> 00:22:02,950
还提到
And...

347
00:22:03,590 --> 00:22:06,090
这本书是用那些孩子的血写成的
that it was written in children's blood.

348
00:22:06,100 --> 00:22:08,300
那些孩子听了这些故事之后就死了  好吗
Well, kids died hearing these stories, okay?

349
00:22:08,310 --> 00:22:10,520
把它放回原位
Look, let's put it back where you found it

350
00:22:10,520 --> 00:22:12,000
咱们赶紧出去
and let's just get out of here now.

351
00:22:12,480 --> 00:22:13,090
我去
Oh, shit!

352
00:22:13,100 --> 00:22:14,050
好了好了好了
I got it, I got it, I got it.

353
00:22:14,050 --> 00:22:15,270
各位  没事  快别喊了
Everybody, okay, everybody just shut up.

354
00:22:15,270 --> 00:22:17,130
不  是老太太还有那条狗
Oh, no. It's the old lady and the dog!

355
00:22:18,230 --> 00:22:19,400
汤米  别闹了  行吗
Tommy, stop it, okay?

356
00:22:19,400 --> 00:22:20,880
让他们出来
Just let them out.

357
00:22:21,530 --> 00:22:22,680
露丝  是你吗
Ruth, is that you?

358
00:22:23,900 --> 00:22:25,720
-你能把门打开吗  -别闹了
- Will you open the door? - Joke's over.

359
00:22:25,820 --> 00:22:27,180
如果你不打开
If you don't open it...

360
00:22:28,120 --> 00:22:29,730
-我就告诉警长  -你不能这样
- I'll tell the Chief. - You can't do this! Come on!

361
00:22:33,080 --> 00:22:34,900
你为什么要那样做
Why would you do that?

362
00:22:36,080 --> 00:22:38,530
这一点都不好玩  汤米  快点
This isn't funny! Tommy, come on.

363
00:22:39,040 --> 00:22:40,400
他是我弟弟
It's my little brother.

364
00:22:43,050 --> 00:22:43,950
拜托
Please.

365
00:22:45,130 --> 00:22:46,790
快他妈把门打开
Open the damn door!

366
00:22:47,890 --> 00:22:49,180
-开门  -露丝
- Open it. - Ruth!

367
00:22:49,180 --> 00:22:51,620
在下面  放我们出去
Down here. Let us out!

368
00:22:56,060 --> 00:22:57,590
反正你也是废物
You're trash anyway.

369
00:22:59,860 --> 00:23:02,470
汤米  对不起我们拿燃烧大便丢你
Tommy, I'm sorry about the burning shit, man.

370
00:23:03,240 --> 00:23:05,300
希望你们能找到出路
I hope you find a way out.

371
00:23:05,950 --> 00:23:06,760
没事吧
Good?

372
00:23:07,320 --> 00:23:08,060
嗯
Yeah.

373
00:23:09,620 --> 00:23:10,660
-快拿开  -没事了
- Get it off me! - Oh, you're fine!

374
00:23:10,660 --> 00:23:13,020
不  快拿开  快拿开  快拿开
No! Get it off, get it off me! Get it off me!

375
00:23:13,830 --> 00:23:16,040
-快拿开  快拿开  -没事了
- Get it off me! Get it off me! - You're fine.

376
00:23:16,040 --> 00:23:17,710
-有我呢  有我呢  没事的  -有东西咬我
- I got it, I got it. It's fine. - Something's bit me!

377
00:23:17,710 --> 00:23:18,980
你能来帮我一下吗
Hey, can you help me with this?

378
00:23:19,130 --> 00:23:20,490
-蜘蛛跑掉了  -谢谢
- The spiders are gone. - Thank you.

379
00:23:20,630 --> 00:23:22,500
天呐  奥吉  你跟条发情的公狗一样
Jesus, Auggie. Okay, you're such a horndog.

380
00:23:22,500 --> 00:23:23,840
你能不能先别忙着勃起
Can you lose your stiffy for a second

381
00:23:23,840 --> 00:23:24,960
帮我们离开这里
and help us get out of here?

382
00:23:24,970 --> 00:23:27,200
不好笑  女士还在场呢
Not funny! There's a lady present.

383
00:23:27,680 --> 00:23:30,120
女士们  在场
Ladies... present.

384
00:23:32,180 --> 00:23:34,040
加油  加油  你得用力推  加油
Come on, come on! You gotta push harder. Come on.

385
00:23:40,400 --> 00:23:42,970
莎拉·贝洛斯  给我讲一个故事
Sarah Bellows, tell me a story.

386
00:23:45,240 --> 00:23:46,600
给我讲一个故事
Tell me a story.

387
00:23:47,450 --> 00:23:49,810
莎拉·贝洛斯  给我讲一个故事
Sarah Bellows, tell me a story.

388
00:24:06,970 --> 00:24:08,170
等等  等等  我听到动静了
Wait, wait, wait. I hear something.

389
00:24:08,180 --> 00:24:09,160
有人在这
Someone's here.

390
00:24:09,300 --> 00:24:10,290
他回来了
He came back.

391
00:24:10,390 --> 00:24:11,410
-汤米  -你得...
- Tommy! - You got...

392
00:24:11,640 --> 00:24:13,460
-对不起  非常对不起  -谢谢你
- We're sorry, we're real sorry. - Thank you!

393
00:24:13,470 --> 00:24:15,680
我收回我说过的每一句坏话
I... I take back everything I ever said, man.

394
00:24:15,680 --> 00:24:16,750
对不起
Sorry, man!

395
00:24:17,560 --> 00:24:19,040
汤米  求你了
Tommy, please!

396
00:24:32,570 --> 00:24:34,660
露丝  你为什么跟这种神经病约会
Ruth, why would you date a psychopath like that?

397
00:24:34,660 --> 00:24:36,350
总比你这个捞大便的人强
Better than fishing for turds.

398
00:24:38,410 --> 00:24:39,900
是谁开的门
So, who unlocked it?

399
00:24:40,290 --> 00:24:42,320
管他呢  咱们赶紧出去吧
Who cares? Let's just get out of here.

400
00:24:42,580 --> 00:24:45,110
-男丑角的扮装不错  -谢谢
- Nice Pierrot costume. - Thank you.

401
00:24:46,000 --> 00:24:46,860
我就说吧
See?

402
00:24:49,340 --> 00:24:50,490
这经历真"好玩"
Well, that was fun.

403
00:24:53,700 --> 00:24:58,100
湿背客

404
00:24:57,270 --> 00:24:58,250
该死
Shit!

405
00:25:04,480 --> 00:25:06,280
抱歉出了这些事
I'm really sorry about all of this.

406
00:25:06,660 --> 00:25:08,170
-他为什么这么做  -太低级了
- Why did he do this? - This is low,

407
00:25:08,810 --> 00:25:09,720
就算对汤米来说
even for Tommy,

408
00:25:09,720 --> 00:25:11,630
就像是在我的牛奶盒里放个屁
like "farting in my milk carton

409
00:25:11,630 --> 00:25:13,100
然后让我喝掉那么低级
"and making me drink it" kind-of-low.

410
00:25:14,160 --> 00:25:15,120
五年级的事儿
It was the fifth grade.

411
00:25:16,080 --> 00:25:16,850
是九年级
It was ninth.

412
00:25:17,910 --> 00:25:20,090
我可以试试找点东西来帮忙
I can try and scrounge up something to help.

413
00:25:20,100 --> 00:25:21,640
我能行  没事  还是谢谢你
I got it. It's fine, thank you, though.

414
00:25:23,140 --> 00:25:24,810
我就待在这等到天亮
I'll just stay here until the morning.

415
00:25:25,280 --> 00:25:26,500
把车开去修车店
Get it into a shop.

416
00:25:28,140 --> 00:25:30,030
我家地下室里有一张沙发
We have a sofa in the basement.

417
00:25:30,770 --> 00:25:31,970
欢迎你来过夜
You're welcome to use it.

418
00:25:35,640 --> 00:25:38,030
我真的不想惹麻烦
Look, I really don't want any trouble.

419
00:25:39,930 --> 00:25:41,740
我们只需要在爸爸起床之前溜出去
We'll just have to be gone before Dad gets up.

420
00:25:51,150 --> 00:25:53,910
自动调幅调频立体声台式收音机
An AM/FM stereo table radio with auto...

421
00:26:16,680 --> 00:26:18,400
山姆的宠物居然是只褐鼠
Sam's pet turns out to be a sewer rat?

422
00:26:19,120 --> 00:26:19,990
你还真坏
You've got some demons.

423
00:26:20,380 --> 00:26:21,290
还没写完呢
It's not finished yet.

424
00:26:32,710 --> 00:26:34,290
知名怪物

425
00:26:32,710 --> 00:26:35,290
我小时候很喜欢看这个  你收集的吗
I used to love these as a kid. You collect them?

426
00:26:35,320 --> 00:26:37,190
每一期我都看过
I've read every single issue.

427
00:26:38,500 --> 00:26:39,320
从头读到尾
Cover to cover.

428
00:26:42,650 --> 00:26:44,300
如果你真的想成为一个作家
You know, if you're serious about being a writer,

429
00:26:44,300 --> 00:26:45,420
你不能在这写
you can't do it here.

430
00:26:47,280 --> 00:26:48,160
你要搬到城市里去
You gotta move to the city.

431
00:26:52,220 --> 00:26:53,340
我不能丢下我爸
I couldn't leave my dad.

432
00:27:05,240 --> 00:27:05,950
那个
the,

433
00:27:07,150 --> 00:27:08,670
地下室就在楼下
basement is downstairs.

434
00:27:09,940 --> 00:27:12,370
地下室通常都在楼下
Yeah, that's usually where they are.

435
00:27:48,110 --> 00:27:50,460
莎拉·贝洛斯的书

436
00:28:02,070 --> 00:28:03,250
阁楼

437
00:28:03,370 --> 00:28:04,450
猫爪

438
00:28:04,490 --> 00:28:05,420
"我能提你的篮子吗"

439
00:28:05,420 --> 00:28:06,920
食人怪

440
00:28:18,740 --> 00:28:21,310
哈罗德

441
00:28:20,130 --> 00:28:21,660
哈罗德
Harold.

442
00:28:55,820 --> 00:28:56,880
汤米·米尔纳
Tommy Milner.

443
00:28:58,000 --> 00:29:00,920
很晚了  你又喝醉了吗
It's late! Are you drunk again?

444
00:29:00,920 --> 00:29:01,830
今天是万圣节
It's Halloween.

445
00:29:01,890 --> 00:29:04,570
你本该把鸡蛋送去沃尔弗顿家
You were supposed to deliver eggs to the Wolvertons.

446
00:29:06,640 --> 00:29:07,450
现在去吗
Now?

447
00:29:08,080 --> 00:29:08,910
现在去
Now!

448
00:29:18,380 --> 00:29:19,220
怎么
What?

449
00:29:21,050 --> 00:29:22,920
真该死
This is bullshit.

450
00:29:35,880 --> 00:29:37,470
哈罗德

451
00:29:37,690 --> 00:29:40,220
汤米一直都讨厌那个稻草人
"Tommy hated that scarecrow all his life.

452
00:29:40,860 --> 00:29:43,660
他拿上鸡蛋  这辈子最后一次离开
"He took the eggs and left for the last time."

453
00:29:45,440 --> 00:29:46,240
汤米
Tommy...

454
00:29:46,470 --> 00:29:48,440
汤米

455
00:30:23,600 --> 00:30:24,990
吃屎吧  哈罗德
Eat shit, Harold.

456
00:32:31,680 --> 00:32:32,350
妈
Mom!

457
00:33:21,490 --> 00:33:22,300
救救我
Help me!

458
00:33:24,050 --> 00:33:24,860
妈
Mom!

459
00:34:01,420 --> 00:34:04,300
警察

460
00:34:04,850 --> 00:34:09,030
请熄火  不要吸烟

461
00:34:08,190 --> 00:34:09,540
天啊
Oh, my God.

462
00:34:10,240 --> 00:34:11,330
瞧瞧这个
Will you look at this?

463
00:34:13,280 --> 00:34:16,250
你不是说要去找农活干吗  陌生人
I thought you were going to be on your way, stranger?

464
00:34:17,230 --> 00:34:18,040
我是想去的
I'm trying.

465
00:34:20,880 --> 00:34:23,080
有个叫汤米·米尔纳的高中生
You know, no one's seen this high school kid

466
00:34:23,080 --> 00:34:25,560
昨晚失踪了
named Tommy Milner since last night.

467
00:34:26,340 --> 00:34:28,970
目击者说他在汽车影院和人吵起来了
Witnesses say he got into a fight at the drive-in.

468
00:34:29,580 --> 00:34:32,680
你这车不会是米尔纳干的吧
Milner didn't do this to your car, did he?

469
00:34:36,360 --> 00:34:37,700
我还不知道你的名字
I never got your name.

470
00:34:40,300 --> 00:34:40,970
雷蒙
Ramon.

471
00:34:43,570 --> 00:34:44,430
罗德里格斯
Rodriguez.

472
00:34:46,350 --> 00:34:47,990
听着  我觉得你最好
Look, I think it'd be a good idea

473
00:34:48,790 --> 00:34:51,250
再多待几天
if you stuck around for a few days.

474
00:34:51,710 --> 00:34:52,560
明白吗[西语]
Comprende?

475
00:34:54,900 --> 00:34:55,990
罗德里格斯
Rodriguez.

476
00:35:02,540 --> 00:35:04,010
之前没有这篇故事
It wasn't there before.

477
00:35:04,480 --> 00:35:05,500
红墨水还没干
The red ink was wet.

478
00:35:05,870 --> 00:35:09,140
而且感觉确实像血  比墨水浓
And it did feel like blood. It was thicker than ink.

479
00:35:09,510 --> 00:35:10,590
你怎么能吃那个
How could you eat that?

480
00:35:11,770 --> 00:35:14,140
你知道里面有多少身体部位吗  七个
Do you know how many body parts are in there? Seven!

481
00:35:15,210 --> 00:35:16,160
我在杂志上看到的
I read it in a magazine.

482
00:35:17,380 --> 00:35:19,490
酷  他变成了稻草人吗
Cool. He turns into a scarecrow?

483
00:35:20,030 --> 00:35:20,860
新奇的转折
Fresh twist.

484
00:35:21,430 --> 00:35:22,610
那不是转折
That's not a twist.

485
00:35:23,380 --> 00:35:25,650
我说了  这个故事...
I told you, the story, it...

486
00:35:26,530 --> 00:35:27,840
就这么凭空出现了
It just appeared.

487
00:35:28,760 --> 00:35:30,680
汤米甚至没去上学
Tommy didn't even show up to school.

488
00:35:32,240 --> 00:35:34,230
就好像他凭空消失了
It's like he just disappeared.

489
00:35:34,580 --> 00:35:36,970
大家都知道他迫不及待要去打共产党
Everyone knew he was eager to go shoot some commies.

490
00:35:38,900 --> 00:35:42,660
也许他只是...提前启程了
Maybe he just, I don't know, left early?

491
00:35:43,640 --> 00:35:44,530
确实有一个房间...
There was that room...

492
00:35:44,600 --> 00:35:45,540
别提了
Just drop it.

493
00:35:46,200 --> 00:35:47,080
不  告诉我
Nah, tell me.

494
00:35:48,590 --> 00:35:51,070
在那栋房子里  我躲藏时
In the house, when I was hiding,

495
00:35:51,970 --> 00:35:54,170
那个房间很旧  我是说很新  很完好
the room was old. I mean new. Perfect,

496
00:35:54,170 --> 00:35:55,850
就像他们还住在那里时  我看到一个
like when they lived there, and I saw this...

497
00:35:55,910 --> 00:35:57,450
一个老太太和一条狗
this old lady and this dog

498
00:35:57,450 --> 00:35:58,610
他们就那么盯着我
and they were just staring at me

499
00:35:58,610 --> 00:36:00,570
-那种表情...  -听听你们说的话
- with this look... - Listen to yourselves.

500
00:36:00,700 --> 00:36:02,730
那栋房子里什么都没发生
Nothing happened to us in that house

501
00:36:02,740 --> 00:36:04,200
除了汤米对我们做的事
except for what Tommy did to us.

502
00:36:04,880 --> 00:36:05,740
如果他不见了
If he's gone,

503
00:36:06,200 --> 00:36:07,070
那不是正好吗
good riddance.

504
00:36:08,370 --> 00:36:09,380
我们就不该去那里
We should never have gone there,

505
00:36:09,850 --> 00:36:10,990
我们就不该拿那本书
we should never have taken the book.

506
00:36:11,630 --> 00:36:13,940
你们被鬼故事吓出神经质了
You let a ghost story get into your heads.

507
00:36:14,610 --> 00:36:15,850
没别的
That's all it is.

508
00:36:17,910 --> 00:36:18,760
我很担心
I'm worried.

509
00:36:19,200 --> 00:36:20,390
汤米没去学校
Tommy wasn't at school.

510
00:36:20,730 --> 00:36:21,830
他的名字出现在书里
His name was in the book.

511
00:36:24,660 --> 00:36:26,730
这不可能真的有关联  对吧
I mean, there's no way it's actually connected, right?

512
00:36:27,620 --> 00:36:28,390
是啊  当然没有
Yeah, of course it's not.

513
00:36:32,960 --> 00:36:35,370
斯黛拉  我不能碰上警察
Stella, I can't get mixed up with the police.

514
00:36:36,880 --> 00:36:37,970
我必须去看看
I have to see it.

515
00:37:03,490 --> 00:37:04,880
汤米昨晚穿的就是这件衣服
It's what Tommy was wearing last night.

516
00:37:07,110 --> 00:37:08,370
如果这就是汤米呢
Okay, what if this is Tommy,

517
00:37:09,420 --> 00:37:11,180
而书里发生的事
and what happens in the book

518
00:37:11,180 --> 00:37:12,350
就是真实情况呢
is exactly what's happened for real?

519
00:37:12,460 --> 00:37:13,690
别再吓我了
Stop trying to scare me.

520
00:37:14,570 --> 00:37:15,730
这就是个稻草人
It's just a scarecrow.

521
00:37:22,580 --> 00:37:24,600
-你听说汤米的事了吗  -他失踪了
- Did you hear about Tommy? - He's missing.

522
00:37:59,440 --> 00:38:00,740
你的书还给你
Here's your book back.

523
00:38:27,640 --> 00:38:28,490
你回来晚了
You're home late.

524
00:38:30,250 --> 00:38:31,180
又要去轮班了吗
Picked up another shift?

525
00:38:32,270 --> 00:38:33,110
你必须去吗
You have to?

526
00:38:34,630 --> 00:38:35,520
不能拒绝
Can't say no.

527
00:38:38,700 --> 00:38:39,770
冰箱里有吃的
There's food in the fridge.

528
00:38:43,810 --> 00:38:45,250
你一直都这么热爱工作吗
Did you always work this much?

529
00:38:47,220 --> 00:38:48,030
妈妈没离开前也是这样吗
Even when Mom was here?

530
00:38:52,260 --> 00:38:53,830
听说米尔纳家的儿子没回家
Heard the Milner boy didn't come home.

531
00:39:00,480 --> 00:39:02,470
大家都在谈这事
Everybody's been talking about it.

532
00:39:02,860 --> 00:39:06,250
接下来几天放学直接回家  知道吗
Please just come straight home next few days, okay?

533
00:39:07,360 --> 00:39:08,090
好
Yep.

534
00:39:21,610 --> 00:39:23,180
你给那痘痘扑够粉了吗
You got enough zit paint on there?

535
00:39:23,650 --> 00:39:25,930
这是蜘蛛咬的  你个屁股痘
It's a spider bite, you butt-pimple.

536
00:39:25,930 --> 00:39:26,800
蜘蛛...
A spider...

537
00:39:27,570 --> 00:39:28,810
该死  我的香蕉
Damn it, my banana!

538
00:39:40,190 --> 00:39:40,900
你不是要走了吗
I thought you were leaving?

539
00:39:43,580 --> 00:39:44,520
希望你饿了
Hope you're hungry.

540
00:39:45,000 --> 00:39:46,350
我饿死了  谢谢
I'm starving. Thanks.

541
00:39:47,000 --> 00:39:49,270
我一直在想汤米消失的事
You know, I can't stop thinking about Tommy's disappearance.

542
00:39:49,270 --> 00:39:50,290
肯定有什么...
There has to be some...

543
00:39:55,110 --> 00:39:56,120
你从哪拿的
Where did you get that?

544
00:39:58,010 --> 00:39:59,970
就在你的书架上
It was just here on your bookshelf.

545
00:40:00,690 --> 00:40:03,300
不  我刚刚就在屋里  没有书
No, I... I was just here. It wasn't.

546
00:40:03,300 --> 00:40:04,800
我把它放回那栋房子里了
I took this back to the house.

547
00:40:04,800 --> 00:40:05,630
什么
What?

548
00:40:09,320 --> 00:40:11,870
它是怎么...怎么又回来的
How is it getting... How is it back here again?

549
00:40:15,880 --> 00:40:16,970
大脚趾

550
00:40:19,390 --> 00:40:20,880
-怎么回事  -什么鬼
- What's happening? - What the hell!

551
00:40:21,720 --> 00:40:22,650
怎么会这样
How does that work?

552
00:40:23,890 --> 00:40:25,110
我们必须让它停下
But we've got to make it stop!

553
00:40:25,710 --> 00:40:28,420
大脚趾

554
00:40:32,750 --> 00:40:34,440
一位母亲在花园边上挖掘
"A mother was digging at the edge of the garden

555
00:40:34,440 --> 00:40:35,560
这时她看到一个大脚趾
"when she saw a big toe.

556
00:40:35,560 --> 00:40:36,340
"这个看着不错  胖乎乎的"
'It looks nice and plump, '

557
00:40:36,340 --> 00:40:37,940
她说  "我要放进炖菜里"
"she said, 'I'll put it in the stew...'"

558
00:40:38,880 --> 00:40:39,990
这算什么故事
What kind of story is that?

559
00:40:40,470 --> 00:40:41,260
什么
What...

560
00:40:40,860 --> 00:40:42,670
奥古斯特

561
00:40:43,610 --> 00:40:44,440
奥吉
Auggie.

562
00:40:47,280 --> 00:40:48,110
奥吉
Auggie!

563
00:40:49,550 --> 00:40:50,410
回话
Pick up!

564
00:40:51,250 --> 00:40:51,930
奥吉
Auggie!

565
00:40:51,940 --> 00:40:53,830
不  家里什么都没有
No, there's nothing here.

566
00:40:54,770 --> 00:40:57,690
我说没有  你和杰夫周末去旅游前
I told you, I mean, the least you could have done was go to the store

567
00:40:57,690 --> 00:40:59,540
至少应该去商店买点东西
before you and Jeff took off for the weekend.

568
00:41:00,500 --> 00:41:02,280
不  我才不叫他"爸"
No, I'm not gonna call him "Dad."

569
00:41:07,130 --> 00:41:08,990
行了  我要把炖菜吃了
Okay, I'm eating the stew.

570
00:41:10,570 --> 00:41:11,760
冰箱里的炖菜
The stew in the fridge?

571
00:41:13,170 --> 00:41:14,370
反正是有人做的
Yeah, well someone made it.

572
00:41:15,400 --> 00:41:17,190
好  等你回来见  爱你
Okay, I'll see you when you get back. Love you.

573
00:41:20,540 --> 00:41:21,770
奥吉  回话
Auggie, pick up!

574
00:41:27,080 --> 00:41:27,910
我在吃饭
I'm eating.

575
00:41:28,170 --> 00:41:28,990
奥吉
Auggie!

576
00:41:29,640 --> 00:41:30,310
斯黛拉
Stella!

577
00:41:30,800 --> 00:41:32,700
奥吉  别吃任何东西
Auggie, do not eat anything.

578
00:41:33,220 --> 00:41:34,300
听着  你在下一个故事中
Listen, you're in the next story!

579
00:41:34,300 --> 00:41:37,470
不管你做什么  千万别吃任何东西
Whatever you do, do not eat anything!

580
00:41:42,130 --> 00:41:43,010
真好玩
Very funny.

581
00:41:44,370 --> 00:41:45,380
是查克让你这么做的吗
Did Chuck put you up to this?

582
00:41:45,560 --> 00:41:47,260
奥吉  这不是玩笑
Auggie, this isn't a joke.

583
00:41:47,260 --> 00:41:49,110
故事正在自己出现
Okay, the story is writing itself right now.

584
00:41:49,110 --> 00:41:51,560
我不知道方式或原因  但我正看这个故事
I don't know how or why, but I'm reading it right here.

585
00:41:51,890 --> 00:41:53,640
一个声音吓到了他  是说话声
"A sound scared him. It was a voice.

586
00:41:53,640 --> 00:41:55,430
那个声音大喊  "谁拿了我的脚趾"
"And it called out, 'Who took my toe?'"

587
00:42:00,260 --> 00:42:03,180
是个尸体在找她不见的脚趾
It's a corpse looking for her missing toe.

588
00:42:03,800 --> 00:42:05,500
我知道这个故事
Yeah, I know this story.

589
00:42:05,900 --> 00:42:07,600
我爸过去常给我讲
My dad used to tell me this story.

590
00:42:08,110 --> 00:42:09,410
我小时候特别害怕  但是...
It scared me so much as a kid, but...

591
00:42:09,970 --> 00:42:11,350
有人要说那句话吗
Am I not supposed to wait for someone to say that

592
00:42:11,350 --> 00:42:13,420
我什么也没听到啊
'cause I don't hear anything.

593
00:42:13,500 --> 00:42:14,760
听着  我们正在看这个故事
Listen, we're reading it right here.

594
00:42:15,670 --> 00:42:17,380
然后声音变大了
"And then the voice grew louder:

595
00:42:17,880 --> 00:42:20,340
"谁拿了我的脚趾"
"'Who took my toe?'"

596
00:42:22,130 --> 00:42:23,080
这里就我一个人
I'm all alone.

597
00:42:27,560 --> 00:42:28,620
没有说话声
There's no voice.

598
00:42:28,890 --> 00:42:31,040
可是肯定有说话声
Yeah, well, there has to be a voice.

599
00:42:31,050 --> 00:42:32,850
只有你在说那句话
You're the only one saying it.

600
00:42:36,950 --> 00:42:37,800
奥吉
Auggie!

601
00:42:40,040 --> 00:42:40,900
奥吉
Auggie!

602
00:42:42,560 --> 00:42:44,170
不  奥吉  回话
No, Auggie, pick up.

603
00:42:46,200 --> 00:42:47,330
奥吉  别吃任何东西
Auggie, don't eat anything.

604
00:42:59,490 --> 00:43:00,360
奥吉
Auggie!

605
00:43:00,550 --> 00:43:01,260
天啊
Oh, God!

606
00:43:01,790 --> 00:43:03,570
奥吉  奥吉
Auggie. Auggie?

607
00:43:09,910 --> 00:43:12,550
奥吉  快啊  奥吉  回话
Auggie? Come on, Auggie, pick up!

608
00:43:15,630 --> 00:43:16,680
你们听到了吗
Did you hear that?

609
00:43:16,810 --> 00:43:18,630
听到什么  我什么也没听到
Hear what? I don't hear anything.

610
00:43:20,610 --> 00:43:22,580
炖菜里有个脚趾  见鬼的脚趾
There was a toe in the stew. A freaking toe.

611
00:43:27,080 --> 00:43:28,680
书上说接下来会发生什么
What does the book say happens next?

612
00:43:29,580 --> 00:43:31,240
奥古斯特非常害怕
"August got very scared.

613
00:43:32,620 --> 00:43:34,340
但他想  "它不知道我在哪"
"But he thought, 'It doesn't know where I am.

614
00:43:34,660 --> 00:43:35,650
"它找不到我"
"'It'll never find me...'"

615
00:43:37,390 --> 00:43:39,380
书怎么会知道这个
How does the book know that?

616
00:43:39,850 --> 00:43:42,050
然后他又一次听到那个声音
And then he heard the voice again...

617
00:43:41,680 --> 00:43:43,730
"谁拿了我的脚趾"

618
00:43:45,680 --> 00:43:46,570
谁
Who...

619
00:43:48,150 --> 00:43:49,030
拿了
took...

620
00:43:50,450 --> 00:43:51,300
我的
my...

621
00:43:51,800 --> 00:43:52,670
脚趾
Toe.

622
00:43:58,660 --> 00:44:00,140
奥吉  快出去
Auggie, just get out of the house!

623
00:44:09,590 --> 00:44:10,920
他离这里只有几条街
He's only a couple of blocks away!

624
00:44:44,430 --> 00:44:46,150
谁
Who...

625
00:44:47,730 --> 00:44:48,790
拿了
took...

626
00:44:50,110 --> 00:44:53,140
丑角派对

627
00:44:50,690 --> 00:44:52,110
我的
my...

628
00:44:54,100 --> 00:44:55,350
脚趾
toe?

629
00:45:00,330 --> 00:45:02,170
快啊  快啊
Come on, come on.

630
00:46:44,830 --> 00:46:45,680
奥吉
Auggie?

631
00:46:46,750 --> 00:46:47,590
奥吉
Auggie!

632
00:46:50,390 --> 00:46:51,250
奥吉
Auggie!

633
00:47:06,550 --> 00:47:08,400
-汤米  -汤米·米尔纳
- Tommy! - Tommy Milner!

634
00:47:08,400 --> 00:47:11,980
让今年更加愁云惨淡的是
And as if this year hasn't been grim enough already,

635
00:47:12,000 --> 00:47:14,310
发生了一起失踪案
we have a disappearance on our hands, friends.

636
00:47:14,760 --> 00:47:16,260
我们的汤米·米尔纳
Our own Tommy Milner,

637
00:47:16,670 --> 00:47:19,130
就在我们小造纸谷失踪了
right here, in little Mill Valley.

638
00:47:27,730 --> 00:47:29,510
是我发现了这本书
I was the one that found the book.

639
00:47:30,060 --> 00:47:31,010
是我带回了家
I took it home.

640
00:47:31,890 --> 00:47:32,790
这不是你的错
This is not your fault.

641
00:47:35,480 --> 00:47:36,190
知道吗
You know,

642
00:47:37,810 --> 00:47:42,260
我生命中的每一件坏事都是我自己造成的
I caused every single bad thing that happened in my life.

643
00:47:44,580 --> 00:47:45,540
我妈的离开
My mom leaving.

644
00:47:47,900 --> 00:47:48,770
现在又是奥吉
And now Auggie.

645
00:47:50,770 --> 00:47:51,710
不是这样的
None of that is true.

646
00:47:58,540 --> 00:48:01,480
抱歉我们迟到了  露丝的痘痘粉不够用了
Sorry we're late. Ruth ran out of zit paint.

647
00:48:01,510 --> 00:48:03,370
我发誓  要不是应付你压力太大
I swear, if you weren't so stressful to deal with

648
00:48:03,370 --> 00:48:05,600
我也不会长痘
in the first place, I wouldn't have zits.

649
00:48:05,600 --> 00:48:07,200
什么事这么紧急
What's so urgent?

650
00:48:08,460 --> 00:48:09,300
奥吉呢
Where's Auggie?

651
00:48:10,190 --> 00:48:11,120
奥吉不见了
Auggie's gone.

652
00:48:11,710 --> 00:48:12,990
又出现一个故事
Another story was written.

653
00:48:14,340 --> 00:48:15,380
就在我们眼皮底下
Right in front of our eyes.

654
00:48:16,900 --> 00:48:17,730
我不明白
I don't get it.

655
00:48:19,150 --> 00:48:19,980
这是什么
What is this?

656
00:48:22,750 --> 00:48:24,100
这是个老掉牙的玩笑
This is a stale joke.

657
00:48:25,070 --> 00:48:26,330
万圣节已经过去了
Halloween's over.

658
00:48:26,950 --> 00:48:28,030
奥吉到底在哪
Where the hell is Auggie?

659
00:48:29,850 --> 00:48:30,590
我们不知道
We don't know.

660
00:48:31,620 --> 00:48:34,110
他父母去旅游了  他就这么消失了
His parents are traveling, and he's just gone.

661
00:48:35,170 --> 00:48:35,890
你说不知道是什么意思
What do you mean you don't know?

662
00:48:35,890 --> 00:48:37,010
好吧  那我们去找他
Okay, well, then let's find him!

663
00:48:37,160 --> 00:48:38,380
我觉得他不会回来了
I don't think he's coming back.

664
00:48:41,040 --> 00:48:42,370
-首先  -我就知道事情不对
- First... - I knew something happened.

665
00:48:42,380 --> 00:48:44,780
-是汤米消失了  -我看到那个老太太...
- Tommy disappeared. - Saw that old lady...

666
00:48:44,780 --> 00:48:45,760
然后现在是奥吉
And then now Auggie.

667
00:48:48,540 --> 00:48:51,390
书里出现了他们的故事
They had their stories in the book,

668
00:48:51,690 --> 00:48:54,570
每晚一个故事
and it happens every night.

669
00:48:55,340 --> 00:48:57,020
天呐  他吃了一根脚趾
Jesus, he ate a toe?

670
00:49:00,140 --> 00:49:01,980
不是你读书
You don't read the book.

671
00:49:02,980 --> 00:49:04,100
而是书读你
The book reads you.

672
00:49:07,850 --> 00:49:10,800
恐怕我们唤醒了什么
I'm afraid that we woke something up.

673
00:49:11,920 --> 00:49:13,950
我们所有人都会有同样的遭遇
That the same thing is going to happen to all of us.

674
00:49:17,240 --> 00:49:18,460
我们都去了那栋房子
We were all in that house.

675
00:49:20,740 --> 00:49:22,450
不  这不是真的  好吗
No, this isn't real, okay?

676
00:49:23,420 --> 00:49:25,050
故事伤不了人
Stories can't hurt you.

677
00:49:25,900 --> 00:49:27,900
莎拉·贝洛斯是个传说
Sarah Bellows is a myth,

678
00:49:28,420 --> 00:49:30,340
即便她是真的  她也死了
and even if she's not, she's dead.

679
00:49:32,330 --> 00:49:33,580
我们得去报警
We need to go to the police.

680
00:49:33,580 --> 00:49:34,490
不行
No, we can't.

681
00:49:34,520 --> 00:49:36,600
他们知道汤米对雷蒙的车做了什么
They know what Tommy did to Ramon's car

682
00:49:36,890 --> 00:49:37,820
他们会认为是他...
and they think that he had...

683
00:49:37,820 --> 00:49:39,440
奥吉  我们得找到奥吉
Auggie! We need to find Auggie.

684
00:49:39,440 --> 00:49:41,260
不能报警
Not going to the police.

685
00:49:42,310 --> 00:49:43,720
我说的话他们一句也不会相信的
They'll never believe a word I say.

686
00:49:45,010 --> 00:49:46,320
那我们可以说服他们
Well, then we'll make them believe.

687
00:49:46,320 --> 00:49:48,670
等到他们明白过来
By the time that they make sense of everything,

688
00:49:49,280 --> 00:49:50,250
我们就都已经死了
we're all going to be dead.

689
00:49:50,590 --> 00:49:52,180
不  不  不
No, no, no.

690
00:49:52,180 --> 00:49:55,660
如果不能报警  那我们该怎么办
If... If we can't go to the police, what do we do?

691
00:49:56,390 --> 00:49:58,460
干等着我们的故事出现吗
Just sit and wait for our story to be written?

692
00:49:59,920 --> 00:50:02,170
一定有阻止女巫的办法
There's gotta be some way to stop a witch.

693
00:50:02,560 --> 00:50:04,380
我不相信这些
Well, I don't believe any of it.

694
00:50:04,380 --> 00:50:06,900
我得走了  我的音乐剧今晚开演
I gotta go. My musical's tonight,

695
00:50:06,900 --> 00:50:08,290
我再也不会被你们的
and I'm not falling for another one

696
00:50:08,300 --> 00:50:09,740
白痴万圣节恶作剧唬住了
of your dumb Halloween pranks.

697
00:50:09,740 --> 00:50:11,250
这不是恶作剧  露丝
It's not a prank, Ruth.

698
00:50:11,250 --> 00:50:12,120
露丝  拜托  别走
Ruth, please, don't go.

699
00:50:12,130 --> 00:50:13,040
我知道你想当个作家  斯黛拉
I know you want to be a writer, Stella,

700
00:50:13,050 --> 00:50:14,170
-但这个恶作剧太过分了  -不
- but this prank is sick. - No!

701
00:50:14,170 --> 00:50:16,720
露丝  露丝  别走
Ruthie! Ruthie, stop.

702
00:50:19,220 --> 00:50:21,130
你真的觉得这样能行吗
Do you really think this is going to work?

703
00:50:21,960 --> 00:50:23,710
塞勒姆的女巫审判就奏效了
It worked in Salem.

704
00:50:46,200 --> 00:50:47,620
为什么  为什么烧不坏你
Why? Why won't you burn?

705
00:50:47,630 --> 00:50:49,630
我恨你  我恨你  我恨你  该死的
I hate you! I hate you. I hate you. God damn it!

706
00:50:49,630 --> 00:50:51,210
这就是为什么我不看书
This is... This is why I don't read books!

707
00:50:51,210 --> 00:50:53,220
我们知道这本书烧不掉也毁不了
We know we can't burn or destroy it,

708
00:50:53,230 --> 00:50:56,530
但我们对莎拉·贝洛斯了解多少
but how much do we actually know about Sarah Bellows?

709
00:51:01,150 --> 00:51:06,320
造纸谷公报

710
00:51:16,490 --> 00:51:18,810
造纸厂关闭

711
00:51:22,180 --> 00:51:23,690
造纸谷镇区
人口记录

712
00:51:23,690 --> 00:51:24,400
出生日期
出生地点

713
00:51:24,400 --> 00:51:25,110
姓名
性别
第几胎

714
00:51:27,210 --> 00:51:28,120
再生一个

715
00:51:28,430 --> 00:51:29,970
艾伦
山姆
约瑟夫

716
00:51:30,880 --> 00:51:31,980
黑魔法是什么

717
00:51:34,540 --> 00:51:36,820
是黑魔法吗

718
00:51:35,490 --> 00:51:36,900
听听这一段
Listen to this one:

719
00:51:36,820 --> 00:51:39,300
在家中唯一的女儿自杀后
贝洛斯一家解雇了长期女佣

720
00:51:37,000 --> 00:51:38,290
在莎拉上吊自杀后
"After Sarah hung herself,

721
00:51:38,290 --> 00:51:42,090
贝洛斯一家开除了赛尔维·巴普蒂斯特
"the Bellows family fired Sylvie Baptiste

722
00:51:39,300 --> 00:51:46,670
是黑魔法吗

723
00:51:42,090 --> 00:51:43,350
因为他们认为
"as she and her daughter, Lou Lou,

724
00:51:43,350 --> 00:51:45,100
她和她女儿  露露
"were thought to be responsible

725
00:51:45,100 --> 00:51:47,150
教了莎拉黑魔法
"for teaching her black magic."

726
00:51:47,290 --> 00:51:50,010
报纸上都登了  应该是真事了吧
If it's in the paper, it has to be true, right?

727
00:51:50,570 --> 00:51:52,420
有莎拉的照片吗
Is there a picture of Sarah?

728
00:51:52,490 --> 00:51:54,130
没有  只有她的名字
No, just her name.

729
00:51:52,820 --> 00:51:55,070
莎拉·贝洛斯

730
00:51:54,360 --> 00:51:57,230
不过我找到一则脑盐的广告
But, uh, I did find an ad for brain salt,

731
00:51:55,300 --> 00:51:59,330
脑盐

732
00:51:57,230 --> 00:51:59,820
说是能治疗头痛和便秘
cures headaches and constipation.

733
00:51:59,930 --> 00:52:01,790
不知为什么没火起来
Not sure why it didn't take off.

734
00:52:02,810 --> 00:52:04,980
奥吉  奥吉肯定会很喜欢
Auggie, Auggie would have loved that.

735
00:52:08,550 --> 00:52:09,900
我的眼睛要看出血了
My eyes are literally gonna start bleeding,

736
00:52:09,900 --> 00:52:10,780
最后一个贝洛斯也离开了
小镇命运该何去何从

737
00:52:10,780 --> 00:52:12,560
但还是没有查到莎拉的信息
and we still have nothing on Sarah.

738
00:52:13,700 --> 00:52:15,430
她是哪一年上吊的
What year did she hang herself?

739
00:52:19,330 --> 00:52:20,990
1898年
1898.

740
00:52:22,070 --> 00:52:24,750
之后短短一年间  她家所有人都离开了
In just one year, all her family members left.

741
00:52:24,810 --> 00:52:26,060
不然还能怎么样
What do you expect?

742
00:52:26,060 --> 00:52:27,510
谁会想留在一个跟谋杀小孩的罪名
I mean, who wants to stick around with the name

743
00:52:27,510 --> 00:52:29,580
有牵扯的地方
that's synonymous with murdering kids?

744
00:52:29,580 --> 00:52:30,600
不是留下
Not stick around,

745
00:52:30,600 --> 00:52:32,110
我是说消失了
I mean gone.

746
00:52:32,110 --> 00:52:34,010
就像人间蒸发了一样
Like, off the face of the earth.

747
00:52:35,480 --> 00:52:38,610
以她父亲为例  迪欧戴特
Take the father, Deodat.

748
00:52:38,610 --> 00:52:40,270
她家有一家造纸厂
The cat owned a paper mill

749
00:52:40,270 --> 00:52:42,690
他走时都不把厂卖了吗
and yet he leaves it without ever selling it?

750
00:52:43,120 --> 00:52:44,770
没有任何报道提到他
No stories written about him,

751
00:52:44,770 --> 00:52:46,990
连封信都没有  就那么消失了
not even a letter, just disappears.

752
00:52:47,690 --> 00:52:49,320
迪欧戴特
Deodat...

753
00:52:49,700 --> 00:52:51,190
迪欧戴特
Deodat.

754
00:52:52,040 --> 00:52:53,870
我见过这个名字
I've seen that name.

755
00:53:00,580 --> 00:53:01,780
食人怪

756
00:53:01,780 --> 00:53:03,940
迪欧戴特

757
00:53:02,220 --> 00:53:06,040
富翁迪欧戴特想去打猎
"Deodat was a wealthy man who wanted to go hunting."

758
00:53:07,930 --> 00:53:09,320
再说一个名字
Give me another name.

759
00:53:10,630 --> 00:53:13,280
他们的一个儿子  伊弗列姆
One of their sons, Ephraim.

760
00:53:11,360 --> 00:53:13,060
伊弗列姆

761
00:53:13,370 --> 00:53:14,950
伊弗列姆·贝洛斯
Ephraim Bellows.

762
00:53:15,780 --> 00:53:18,390
伊弗列姆

763
00:53:19,610 --> 00:53:21,650
它们不是离开镇子那么简单
They didn't just leave the town.

764
00:53:23,610 --> 00:53:25,210
他们都有自己的故事
They each have a story.

765
00:53:26,110 --> 00:53:27,410
为什么
Why?

766
00:53:35,070 --> 00:53:36,250
天啊
Oh, my God.

767
00:53:36,250 --> 00:53:37,640
天啊  又开始了
Oh, my God, it's happening again.

768
00:53:37,640 --> 00:53:39,440
她在写另一篇故事
She's writing another story.

769
00:53:41,660 --> 00:53:43,240
《红斑》
"The Red Spot"?

770
00:53:50,200 --> 00:53:52,220
你们看我干什么
Why are you looking at me?

771
00:53:52,920 --> 00:53:54,200
怎么了
What?

772
00:53:56,250 --> 00:53:58,350
靠  靠  是我吗
Oh, shit! Oh, shit, it's me?

773
00:53:58,350 --> 00:53:59,990
我要死了吗
It... I'm gonna die?

774
00:53:59,990 --> 00:54:01,910
我不想死  我还没破处呢
I don't want to die! I even haven't had sex yet.

775
00:54:01,910 --> 00:54:03,330
一天晚上  一只蜘蛛爬上
"One night, a spider crawled across

776
00:54:03,330 --> 00:54:04,670
一个年轻女孩的脸颊并咬了她一口
"a young girl's cheek and bit her."

777
00:54:04,670 --> 00:54:07,030
蜘蛛  我打扮成蜘蛛侠了  我...
Spider? I was the spider man! I'm...

778
00:54:07,170 --> 00:54:08,740
等下  "年轻的女孩"
Wait, "young girl"?

779
00:54:09,960 --> 00:54:12,130
露丝

780
00:54:11,100 --> 00:54:12,690
去了洗手间
"Went to the restroom."

781
00:54:12,740 --> 00:54:14,600
不是你  是你姐姐
It's not you. It's your sister.

782
00:54:14,600 --> 00:54:15,880
露丝
Ruthie?

783
00:54:17,420 --> 00:54:22,900
造纸谷镇区为您献上
欢乐今宵

784
00:54:25,960 --> 00:54:28,460
二十分钟后演员登台
Performers to stage in 20 minutes.

785
00:54:44,430 --> 00:54:47,250
亲爱的  你得处理下那个了
Honey, you need to do something about that.

786
00:54:48,790 --> 00:54:50,080
嗯
Yeah.

787
00:55:51,640 --> 00:55:53,090
不是这个洗手间
It's a different bathroom.

788
00:55:54,880 --> 00:55:56,710
-二楼  -好
- Second floor! - Okay.

789
00:55:57,620 --> 00:55:59,080
露丝
Ruth.

790
00:56:29,990 --> 00:56:31,640
让开  快让开
Move. Out of the way!

791
00:56:57,750 --> 00:56:59,200
露丝
Ruth!

792
00:57:02,270 --> 00:57:03,920
天啊  露丝
Oh, my God, Ruth!

793
00:57:04,940 --> 00:57:07,120
救命  救命
Help me, help me!

794
00:57:07,120 --> 00:57:08,180
露丝  我来了
Ruth, I got you.

795
00:57:08,180 --> 00:57:10,560
没事了  没事了  我来了
It's okay. It's okay. I got you.

796
00:57:10,600 --> 00:57:11,990
救命  把它们弄开
Help me, help me. Get them off!

797
00:57:11,990 --> 00:57:13,540
把它们弄开
Get them off!

798
00:57:13,910 --> 00:57:16,410
露丝  没事了  没事了  我来了
Ruth, it's okay. It's okay. I got you.

799
00:57:16,410 --> 00:57:19,520
-把它们弄开  -没事的  好吗  没事了
- Get them off! - You're going to be okay, all right? It's okay.

800
00:57:22,720 --> 00:57:24,710
让开  让开  让开
Move, move, move!

801
00:57:28,010 --> 00:57:30,930
没事了  没事了  没事了  露丝
You're okay. You're okay, you're okay, Ruthie.

802
00:57:31,410 --> 00:57:33,450
快来人啊  快去叫人来
Help! Somebody, get help, now!

803
00:57:41,050 --> 00:57:42,120
没事了  露丝  没事了
You're okay, Ruthie, you're okay.

804
00:57:42,120 --> 00:57:44,080
-都结束了  -把它们弄开  把它们弄开
- It's all finished. - Get them off, get them off.

805
00:57:44,080 --> 00:57:46,110
都没了  露丝  都没了
They're all gone, Ruthie. They're all gone.

806
00:57:46,110 --> 00:57:48,790
把它们弄开  把它们弄开
Get them off me. Get them off. Get them off me.

807
00:57:48,790 --> 00:57:50,750
-把它们弄开  -露丝  都没了
- Get them off me! - Ruthie, they're all gone,

808
00:57:50,750 --> 00:57:52,270
都没了  都没了  好吗
they're all gone, they're all gone, okay?

809
00:57:52,270 --> 00:57:54,500
-把它们弄开  -没事了
- Get them off me. - You're okay.

810
00:57:54,500 --> 00:57:56,310
把它们弄开
Get them off me.

811
00:57:59,220 --> 00:58:02,060
造纸谷镇区

812
00:58:04,400 --> 00:58:06,740
真是千钧一发  希望她没事
It's intense. I hope she's okay.

813
00:58:07,800 --> 00:58:10,190
我看见她了  莎拉刚才也在
I saw her. Sarah was there.

814
00:58:10,190 --> 00:58:12,300
这一切都是她控制的
She was controlling the entire thing.

815
00:58:12,880 --> 00:58:14,470
我姐姐被干掉了
My sister's gone.

816
00:58:14,910 --> 00:58:16,360
接下来就是我们了
We're next.

817
00:58:17,460 --> 00:58:18,820
接下来就是我们了
We're next.

818
00:58:25,750 --> 00:58:26,980
你找到了吗
You find it?

819
00:58:29,600 --> 00:58:31,640
露易丝·巴普蒂斯特
Louise Baptiste...

820
00:58:32,360 --> 00:58:33,660
露露吗
Lou Lou?

821
00:58:34,700 --> 00:58:36,460
戈德夏尔路220号
220 Goldshire Road.

822
00:58:36,080 --> 00:58:37,340
露易丝·巴普蒂斯特

823
00:58:39,460 --> 00:58:41,830
我又做了那个可怕的梦
I had this messed-up dream again.

824
00:58:42,280 --> 00:58:44,100
我被困在一个红房间里
I was trapped in the red room.

825
00:58:44,100 --> 00:58:48,940
有个苍白的胖女人一直在小声嘟囔
And there's that fat, pale lady who keeps whispering,

826
00:58:49,360 --> 00:58:51,320
"这是个邪恶的地方"
"This is an evil place.

827
00:58:51,550 --> 00:58:53,640
"趁还有机会快跑"
"Run away while you still can."

828
00:58:56,660 --> 00:58:59,100
我害怕女巫会用这个来对付我
I'm scared the witch is going to use it against me.

829
00:59:04,100 --> 00:59:05,440
你们好
Hello.

830
00:59:05,580 --> 00:59:08,040
露露·巴普蒂斯特还住在这吗
Does Lou Lou Baptiste live here still?

831
00:59:08,850 --> 00:59:10,260
我不想轰炸任何人
"I don't want to bomb anybody

832
00:59:10,270 --> 00:59:13,220
除非是需要救...
"if it's not necessary to save..."

833
00:59:13,220 --> 00:59:16,130
狡猾的迪克  总统不该叫这个名字
Tricky Dicky. That's no name for a president.

834
00:59:13,220 --> 00:59:16,130
尼克松的外号

835
00:59:16,240 --> 00:59:18,800
妈妈  你有客人
Mama, you got company!

836
00:59:32,710 --> 00:59:34,510
露露  能听见我们说话吗
Lou Lou, can you hear us?

837
01:00:03,040 --> 01:00:05,870
露·巴

838
01:00:19,560 --> 01:00:21,900
下一个可能是你
You may be the next.

839
01:00:23,170 --> 01:00:24,710
你为什么这么说
Why do you say that?

840
01:00:26,380 --> 01:00:28,520
歌是这么唱的  姑娘
Why, that's the song, girl.

841
01:00:30,180 --> 01:00:34,660
♪ 灵车经过时不要笑 ♪
♪ Don't ever laugh as a hearse goes by ♪

842
01:00:34,660 --> 01:00:36,970
♪ 因为你可能是 ♪
♪ For you may be ♪

843
01:00:36,970 --> 01:00:39,570
♪ 下一个死去的人 ♪
♪ The next to die ♪

844
01:00:41,720 --> 01:00:43,700
莎拉很喜欢这首歌
Sarah loved that song.

845
01:00:49,560 --> 01:00:51,070
她的书在我们手上
We have her book.

846
01:00:55,120 --> 01:00:57,710
你找到了她的书吗  拿来
You found her book? Give it here.

847
01:01:11,610 --> 01:01:13,280
这是我给她的
I give her this.

848
01:01:14,950 --> 01:01:16,910
我真的很可怜那个姑娘
I feel so sorry for that girl,

849
01:01:16,910 --> 01:01:21,260
独自一人坐在黑暗之中
sitting down there in the darkness all by herself.

850
01:01:24,740 --> 01:01:27,280
你妈妈有教过她什么吗
Did your mom ever teach her anything?

851
01:01:28,330 --> 01:01:29,800
教她
Teach her?

852
01:01:30,590 --> 01:01:32,070
黑魔法
Black magic?

853
01:01:33,860 --> 01:01:35,180
没有
No.

854
01:01:35,350 --> 01:01:37,660
这世上没有魔法  孩子
There is no magic, child.

855
01:01:38,850 --> 01:01:40,910
只有愤怒
There is only rage.

856
01:01:42,160 --> 01:01:45,190
那她现在怎么还能写故事
Then how is she still writing the stories?

857
01:01:47,480 --> 01:01:49,450
故事可以伤人
Stories hurt.

858
01:01:50,230 --> 01:01:52,290
故事可以治愈
Stories heal.

859
01:01:53,110 --> 01:01:55,290
你知道你干了什么吗
Do you know what you have done?

860
01:01:55,430 --> 01:01:56,800
干了什么
Done what?

861
01:01:57,030 --> 01:01:59,470
你不该拿走这本书
You shouldn't have taken the book.

862
01:02:01,810 --> 01:02:03,630
你惹怒她了
You made her angry.

863
01:02:08,720 --> 01:02:12,080
"蛆虫爬进又爬出"
"The worms crawl in, the worms crawl out..."

864
01:02:12,080 --> 01:02:13,480
她有时候会神志不清
She gets this way sometimes.

865
01:02:13,480 --> 01:02:14,830
我必须问清楚
Look, I need to know.

866
01:02:14,830 --> 01:02:16,920
改天吧  我得让她平静下来
Another time. I need to settle her down.

867
01:02:16,930 --> 01:02:19,100
不  我们必须问清楚  我必须问清楚
No, we need to know. I need to know.

868
01:02:19,100 --> 01:02:21,130
莎拉在医院上吊自杀后
She told the doctors everything she knew at the hospital

869
01:02:21,130 --> 01:02:22,780
她把知道的一切都告诉医生了
where that disturbed girl hung herself.

870
01:02:22,780 --> 01:02:23,620
但我以为...
But I... I thought...

871
01:02:23,620 --> 01:02:25,760
大家都说莎拉是在家里上吊的
Everyone always said Sarah hanged herself in the house.

872
01:02:25,760 --> 01:02:27,760
你又不在场  妈妈在场
You weren't there. Mama was.

873
01:02:28,960 --> 01:02:30,320
医院有病历
The hospitals have records.

874
01:02:30,320 --> 01:02:31,820
莎拉的病历
Records of Sarah.

875
01:02:31,870 --> 01:02:34,890
那我们还在这儿干什么  快走吧
Then what are we still doing here? Let's go.

876
01:02:37,290 --> 01:02:39,110
今天是大选日  各位
It's election day, folks,

877
01:02:39,110 --> 01:02:41,420
请投出自己的一票
so let your voice be heard.

878
01:02:41,540 --> 01:02:45,970
拒绝战争  拒绝越战
Say no to the war! Say no to Vietnam.

879
01:02:46,050 --> 01:02:50,080
拒绝让我们的孩子们去送死
Say no to sending our children to die.

880
01:03:23,050 --> 01:03:24,390
打扰一下
Excuse me.

881
01:03:24,870 --> 01:03:28,830
我们需要一位前患者的病历
We need to see the records of a former patient.

882
01:03:29,690 --> 01:03:31,890
我们不能随便给出患者的病历
We don't give out patient records.

883
01:03:34,390 --> 01:03:36,030
这个...
Well, uh,

884
01:03:36,200 --> 01:03:37,460
我是说
I mean,

885
01:03:37,460 --> 01:03:40,440
她一百年前就去世了
she died about 100 years ago.

886
01:03:41,150 --> 01:03:43,380
她自己或者任何人
I'm sure she or anybody else

887
01:03:43,380 --> 01:03:46,200
应该都不会在乎了
probably doesn't care, you know.

888
01:03:46,200 --> 01:03:48,640
你们几个孩子看病历干什么
Why do you kids wanna look at old patient files for?

889
01:03:48,640 --> 01:03:50,540
这是学校作业
For a school assignment

890
01:03:50,540 --> 01:03:52,090
研究...
on, uh...

891
01:03:52,730 --> 01:03:54,680
人类心理学研究

892
01:03:54,260 --> 01:03:56,600
人类心理学研究
psychological human studies.

893
01:03:56,770 --> 01:03:58,570
没错  研究
Yes, the studies.

894
01:04:01,650 --> 01:04:02,690
我想老医院的病历
I think they put the files

895
01:04:02,690 --> 01:04:04,650
应该都在红房间里
from the old hospital in the red room.

896
01:04:05,660 --> 01:04:07,190
红房间
Red room?

897
01:04:08,460 --> 01:04:10,240
申请需要六周时间
Six weeks processing time.

898
01:04:10,240 --> 01:04:11,790
最多六周
At most.

899
01:04:12,320 --> 01:04:13,680
需要笔吗
Need a pen?

900
01:04:19,080 --> 01:04:20,580
白费功夫
So much for that.

901
01:04:25,800 --> 01:04:26,700
走
Come on!

902
01:04:26,700 --> 01:04:27,830
不
No.

903
01:04:44,560 --> 01:04:46,320
我们不能进红房间
We are not going to the red room!

904
01:04:46,320 --> 01:04:47,690
不  我们要进红房间
No, we are going to the red room.

905
01:04:47,690 --> 01:04:48,680
-我不去  -你得去
- No, I'm not. - Yes.

906
01:04:48,680 --> 01:04:50,130
不  我不要
No. I'm not doing it.

907
01:04:52,600 --> 01:04:54,860
考夫曼医生请接电话
Dr. Kaufmann to telephone, please.

908
01:04:54,860 --> 01:04:56,310
考夫曼医生
Dr. Kaufmann.

909
01:04:56,650 --> 01:05:00,390
我跟你说了我的梦  我不想去
I told you about my dream. I don't want to go.

910
01:05:01,670 --> 01:05:04,320
原来不是红色而是缩写  没事的
So, it isn't actually red. You're fine.

911
01:05:04,220 --> 01:05:06,050
红房间
病历和审计科

912
01:05:07,810 --> 01:05:09,270
缩写就是红房间  好吗
It is called the red room, okay?

913
01:05:09,270 --> 01:05:11,770
谁说一定要是红色了
Who said it had to be red?

914
01:05:12,470 --> 01:05:14,360
我坚决不去
Count me out.

915
01:05:14,570 --> 01:05:16,780
好吧  那留在这里
Okay. Just... stay here.

916
01:05:18,490 --> 01:05:20,850
很快的  不会有事的
Be quick. It'll be fine.

917
01:05:23,100 --> 01:05:24,650
别被抓到了
Just don't get caught.

918
01:05:49,070 --> 01:05:51,780
红房间
病历和审计科

919
01:06:08,270 --> 01:06:09,250
乔治·弗曼
George Foreman.

920
01:06:09,250 --> 01:06:11,460
他会成为73年的世界冠军
He's going to be the world champion in '73.

921
01:06:12,790 --> 01:06:14,320
你知道自己要去哪吗
You know where you're going?

922
01:06:18,500 --> 01:06:21,100
天啊  天啊  天啊
Oh, God. Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.

923
01:06:24,170 --> 01:06:25,380
说你呢
You there.

924
01:06:25,380 --> 01:06:27,180
你不该来这里
You're not supposed to be here.

925
01:06:27,490 --> 01:06:28,790
站住
Stop!

926
01:06:38,860 --> 01:06:40,230
红房间
The R.E.D. Room.

927
01:06:40,530 --> 01:06:42,790
红房间
病历和审计科

928
01:06:57,420 --> 01:07:02,110
莎拉·贝洛斯

929
01:07:05,820 --> 01:07:08,600
入院记录  心理测试
Admittance records, psychological exams,

930
01:07:08,600 --> 01:07:09,960
进食情况
what she ate...

931
01:07:10,220 --> 01:07:12,620
这里  什么都记录了
This is... everything.

932
01:07:13,280 --> 01:07:15,670
她是被自己的家人送来的
She was admitted by her own family.

933
01:07:14,910 --> 01:07:17,170
彭赫斯特医院
精神病院

934
01:07:16,910 --> 01:07:19,390
这上面说她患有
Says here that she was suffering

935
01:07:17,170 --> 01:07:20,000
检查收治精神病患者莎拉·贝洛斯

936
01:07:19,390 --> 01:07:22,440
色素缺乏-白化病
from achromasia-albinism.

937
01:07:22,960 --> 01:07:25,450
因为她与常人有异  他们就把她关在地下室
They put her in her basement because she was different.

938
01:07:30,290 --> 01:07:32,360
看这个  她的主治医师
Here, her supervising doctor was...

939
01:07:33,960 --> 01:07:35,750
是伊弗列姆·贝洛斯
Dr. Ephraim Bellows.

940
01:07:36,490 --> 01:07:37,910
她亲哥哥吗
Her own brother?

941
01:07:38,150 --> 01:07:39,350
是的
Yeah.

942
01:07:43,070 --> 01:07:46,300
天呐  他们各种折磨她
Jesus! They tortured her.

943
01:07:46,310 --> 01:07:47,880
看  电击
Look, electroshock,

944
01:07:47,880 --> 01:07:49,910
隔绝疗法
isolation therapy,

945
01:07:50,280 --> 01:07:52,940
侧脑电热疗法
lateral cerebral diathermia treatment.

946
01:07:55,210 --> 01:07:56,610
这个呢
What about this thing?

947
01:08:02,500 --> 01:08:04,060
这是什么
What is this?

948
01:08:06,900 --> 01:08:08,890
我见过这种东西
I've seen one of these before.

949
01:08:09,640 --> 01:08:11,590
这是留声机圆筒
It's a wax cylinder.

950
01:08:15,710 --> 01:08:17,290
器材柜

951
01:08:15,960 --> 01:08:18,970
唱片出现之前就是用这个录音的
They used them to make recordings before LPs.

952
01:08:22,420 --> 01:08:25,260
你是说我们能听到莎拉说话了
So, does that mean we're going to get to hear Sarah?

953
01:08:32,960 --> 01:08:34,560
他往这边跑了
He went this way.

954
01:08:34,920 --> 01:08:36,550
拉警报
Sound the alarm!

955
01:08:41,610 --> 01:08:44,090
这回你要说实话
You're going to tell the truth now.

956
01:08:44,640 --> 01:08:46,360
明白吗  莎拉
Aren't you, Sarah?

957
01:08:52,090 --> 01:08:55,850
我没有伤害那些孩子
I didn't hurt the children.

958
01:08:57,740 --> 01:08:59,720
我没有
I didn't.

959
01:09:01,810 --> 01:09:02,820
伊弗列姆
Ephraim...

960
01:09:02,820 --> 01:09:06,430
这不是实话  对不对
That isn't the truth, is it?

961
01:09:06,980 --> 01:09:09,230
不是我干的
I didn't do it.

962
01:09:09,610 --> 01:09:11,700
我没有伤害...
I didn't hurt...

963
01:09:15,100 --> 01:09:16,960
说实话  莎拉
Tell the truth, Sarah.

964
01:09:17,200 --> 01:09:18,830
我是你妹妹啊
I'm your sister...

965
01:09:18,830 --> 01:09:20,180
你毒死了那些孩子
You poisoned those children.

966
01:09:20,180 --> 01:09:22,740
不  不是的
No. No.

967
01:09:23,520 --> 01:09:25,100
我想...
I tried...

968
01:09:25,540 --> 01:09:28,130
我想救他们的
I tried to save them.

969
01:09:29,850 --> 01:09:32,450
但谁也不信我
But nobody listened.

970
01:09:32,870 --> 01:09:37,840
我不想伤害他们  但你们不放我出去
I didn't want them hurt, but you wouldn't let me out.

971
01:09:37,840 --> 01:09:39,310
莎拉
Sarah...

972
01:09:44,050 --> 01:09:46,280
说实话
Tell the truth.

973
01:09:46,540 --> 01:09:48,250
她不知道自己干了什么
She doesn't know what she did.

974
01:09:48,860 --> 01:09:50,410
是水
It was the water.

975
01:09:50,410 --> 01:09:52,240
我们谈过这个了  莎拉
We went over this, Sarah.

976
01:09:52,240 --> 01:09:53,710
是水
The water.

977
01:09:53,750 --> 01:09:57,050
水没有问题
There's nothing wrong with the water.

978
01:09:57,440 --> 01:09:59,140
所以你才被送来这里
That's why you're here.

979
01:09:59,140 --> 01:10:00,570
造纸厂
The mill.

980
01:10:00,570 --> 01:10:03,270
是造纸厂排放的水银
It was the mercury from the mill.

981
01:10:03,270 --> 01:10:05,790
你们污染了水...
You poisoned the wa...

982
01:10:08,430 --> 01:10:09,950
不是她干的
She didn't do it.

983
01:10:10,110 --> 01:10:11,690
是她的家人
It was her family.

984
01:10:14,670 --> 01:10:16,100
莎拉
Sarah,

985
01:10:16,640 --> 01:10:18,510
你还有意识吗
are you still here?

986
01:10:21,980 --> 01:10:23,670
我说
I'll tell you.

987
01:10:25,020 --> 01:10:27,470
你想听什么我都说
I'll tell you what you want to hear.

988
01:10:28,190 --> 01:10:29,850
说来听听
And what's that?

989
01:10:38,270 --> 01:10:41,800
查理梦到了一个红房间
Charlie had a dream of a red room...

990
01:10:44,170 --> 01:10:45,260
查理
Charlie?

991
01:10:45,260 --> 01:10:46,360
红房间
The R.E.D. Room.

992
01:10:46,360 --> 01:10:48,050
哪个查理
Charlie who?

993
01:10:48,700 --> 01:10:50,120
查克
Chuck.

994
01:10:50,340 --> 01:10:52,450
在他的梦里
In his dream,

995
01:10:52,810 --> 01:10:55,910
一个女人脸色苍白
a woman with a pale face,

996
01:10:56,320 --> 01:10:58,310
双眼乌黑
black eyes,

997
01:10:58,790 --> 01:11:01,450
头发又黑又长
and long black hair

998
01:11:00,700 --> 01:11:03,200
梦

999
01:11:01,630 --> 01:11:04,490
悄悄溜进了他的房间
slipped silently into his room.

1000
01:11:05,400 --> 01:11:08,750
她俯下身低语
She leaned over and whispered,

1001
01:11:08,750 --> 01:11:13,350
"这是个邪恶的地方"
"This is an evil place.

1002
01:11:13,420 --> 01:11:17,070
"趁还有机会快跑"
"Run away while you still can."

1003
01:11:32,130 --> 01:11:33,360
不妙
That's not good.

1004
01:11:33,360 --> 01:11:34,630
查克
Chuck!

1005
01:11:44,310 --> 01:11:45,720
救命
Help!

1006
01:11:48,550 --> 01:11:50,520
救命  谁来救救我
Help! Somebody, help!

1007
01:12:37,470 --> 01:12:39,830
救命  谁来救救我
Help! Please, somebody, help.

1008
01:13:17,670 --> 01:13:19,140
救命  救命
Help. Help!

1009
01:13:19,140 --> 01:13:20,700
谁来救救我
Somebody, help!

1010
01:13:21,340 --> 01:13:22,580
快啊
Come on!

1011
01:14:15,990 --> 01:14:18,420
查克  查克  你在哪
Chuck! Chuck, where are you?

1012
01:14:18,430 --> 01:14:19,780
查克
Chuck!

1013
01:14:21,230 --> 01:14:22,250
他在哪
Where is he?

1014
01:14:22,250 --> 01:14:23,550
他应该就在这里的
He should be right here.

1015
01:14:23,550 --> 01:14:25,790
查克  查克
Chuck? Chuck?

1016
01:14:28,000 --> 01:14:29,380
查克
Chuck.

1017
01:14:41,550 --> 01:14:42,820
那么
So,

1018
01:14:43,220 --> 01:14:44,840
你们的朋友呢
where's your little friend?

1019
01:14:47,110 --> 01:14:50,660
继续报道68年大选之夜新闻
News coverage of election night '68 continues.

1020
01:14:52,360 --> 01:14:53,260
斯黛拉
Stella?

1021
01:14:53,260 --> 01:14:54,520
爸
Dad.

1022
01:14:54,960 --> 01:14:56,620
你没事吧  你在哪
Are you okay? Where are you?

1023
01:14:57,260 --> 01:14:58,600
斯黛拉
Stella?

1024
01:14:58,680 --> 01:15:00,610
爸  恐怕我要死了
I'm afraid I'm gonna die, Dad.

1025
01:15:01,050 --> 01:15:02,800
亲爱的  别这么说
Sweetie, don't say that.

1026
01:15:02,810 --> 01:15:04,880
告诉我怎么回事  告诉我怎么帮你
Tell me what's wrong. Tell me what I can do.

1027
01:15:04,960 --> 01:15:06,810
你什么也做不了
Can't do anything about it.

1028
01:15:07,290 --> 01:15:09,030
我也什么都做不了
I can't do anything about it.

1029
01:15:09,320 --> 01:15:12,580
不不  你得帮帮我  亲爱的
No, no. You gotta help me out here, sweetie.

1030
01:15:12,680 --> 01:15:15,190
告诉我你在哪  我马上过去
Tell me where you are. I will get there right away.

1031
01:15:15,190 --> 01:15:17,060
不管你遇到了什么事  你要告诉我
I don't care what you're going through, just tell me, please.

1032
01:15:17,060 --> 01:15:18,360
如果我消失了
If I go missing...

1033
01:15:18,550 --> 01:15:19,700
消失
Missing?

1034
01:15:20,600 --> 01:15:22,120
如果你找不到我了
If you can't find me...

1035
01:15:22,870 --> 01:15:24,280
去哪找你
Find you where?

1036
01:15:26,030 --> 01:15:26,910
斯黛拉
Stella?

1037
01:15:27,230 --> 01:15:29,390
你要知道我没有丢下你
I didn't leave you.

1038
01:15:29,420 --> 01:15:31,520
我绝不会那样对你
I would never do that to you.

1039
01:15:31,650 --> 01:15:32,410
我不懂
I don't understand

1040
01:15:32,410 --> 01:15:34,000
你到底在说什么  斯黛拉  丢下我
what you're talking about, Stella, leave me?

1041
01:15:34,000 --> 01:15:35,240
你为什么要丢下我
Why would you leave me?

1042
01:15:35,240 --> 01:15:36,610
你旁边是不是有别人  你...
Is someone there with you? Do...

1043
01:15:42,450 --> 01:15:44,660
听我说  亲爱的
Please just listen to me, sweetie.

1044
01:15:46,040 --> 01:15:47,870
那不是你的错  斯黛拉
It's not your fault, Stella.

1045
01:15:48,810 --> 01:15:51,020
她离开不是你的错
It's not your fault she left.

1046
01:15:52,230 --> 01:15:54,960
所有人都说是因为我
Everyone said it was because of me.

1047
01:15:54,960 --> 01:15:57,390
不  拜托  求你听我说
Oh, no, please, please, please listen to me.

1048
01:15:57,860 --> 01:16:00,080
她离开不是你的错
It's not your fault she left.

1049
01:16:00,730 --> 01:16:05,160
从来都不是因为你  是她自己
It was never, ever about you. It was about her.

1050
01:16:07,690 --> 01:16:10,680
我不知道  内心深处  她...
I don't know, somewhere deep down inside, she just...

1051
01:16:11,710 --> 01:16:14,080
感觉被困住了  我也不知道  我...
felt trapped or something, I don't know, I...

1052
01:16:15,360 --> 01:16:16,200
事情很复杂
It's complicated.

1053
01:16:16,200 --> 01:16:17,970
我也希望能给你答案  亲爱的
I wish I had answers for you, sweetie,

1054
01:16:17,970 --> 01:16:20,590
但我没办法  我很抱歉
but I just don't and I'm so sorry.

1055
01:16:23,590 --> 01:16:26,290
爸  我爱你  我得挂了
I love you, Dad. I gotta go.

1056
01:16:26,290 --> 01:16:28,990
-那不是你的错  斯黛拉  求你别挂  -对不起
- It's not your fault, Stella. Please don't hang up, sweetie. - I'm sorry,

1057
01:16:28,990 --> 01:16:29,560
对不起  我得挂了
I'm sorry, I gotta go.

1058
01:16:29,560 --> 01:16:31,120
我告诉你  那不是你的错...
I'm telling you, it wasn't your...

1059
01:16:33,040 --> 01:16:36,110
如何  你爸来接你吗
So? Is your dad going to come pick you up?

1060
01:16:38,680 --> 01:16:41,880
斯黛拉  怎么回事
Stella, what's going on?

1061
01:16:42,700 --> 01:16:45,180
我需要你立刻回答我的问题
I need answers from you right now.

1062
01:16:45,440 --> 01:16:46,710
明白吗
Understand?

1063
01:16:47,140 --> 01:16:50,510
理查德·尼克松得票率仍有43%  汉弗莱35%
Richard Nixon is still holding at 43 and Humphrey 35,

1064
01:16:50,520 --> 01:16:52,940
不过华莱士有1%的涨幅
but, uh, Wallace has come up one point.

1065
01:16:52,940 --> 01:16:54,240
该我打电话了吧
What about my call?

1066
01:16:54,560 --> 01:16:57,820
逃避兵役的家伙没有权利
Rules don't apply to draft dodgers.

1067
01:16:58,670 --> 01:17:00,440
你以为我不会发现吗
You think I wouldn't find out?

1068
01:17:01,030 --> 01:17:03,440
雷蒙·莫拉莱斯
Ramon Morales.

1069
01:17:04,090 --> 01:17:05,820
无论如何你都要为你的国家
You're gonna do your duty to this country

1070
01:17:05,820 --> 01:17:07,490
尽你的责任
one way or the other.

1071
01:17:07,540 --> 01:17:10,860
把你们失踪的朋友的事告诉我  我才能帮你们
I can help you if you tell us about your missing friends.

1072
01:17:10,860 --> 01:17:12,400
我们知道的都告诉你了
Told you everything we know.

1073
01:17:12,490 --> 01:17:13,930
是啊
Oh, yeah, right.

1074
01:17:14,640 --> 01:17:16,760
莎拉·贝洛斯的书
Sarah Bellows' book.

1075
01:17:17,230 --> 01:17:22,220
故事自己出现  然后都成真了
The stories write themselves and it all comes alive.

1076
01:17:22,690 --> 01:17:25,090
我们找不到任何尸体
We can't find any bodies.

1077
01:17:25,090 --> 01:17:26,200
我知道
Yeah, I know.

1078
01:17:27,690 --> 01:17:29,090
很难以置信
It's hard to believe.

1079
01:17:30,150 --> 01:17:32,140
我们在学校救了露丝
We saved Ruth at school.

1080
01:17:32,140 --> 01:17:34,290
我们阻止了她被杀害
I mean, we stopped her from getting killed.

1081
01:17:36,230 --> 01:17:37,640
露丝·施泰因贝格
Ruth Steinberg?

1082
01:17:38,190 --> 01:17:39,730
你说的是她吗
That's who you're talking about?

1083
01:17:40,760 --> 01:17:41,990
你们才没救人
You didn't save anyone.

1084
01:17:41,990 --> 01:17:45,530
她要在精神病院度过余生了
She's stuck in the nuthouse for the rest of her life.

1085
01:17:46,200 --> 01:17:49,140
走吧  斯黛拉  你可以走了
Get out of here, Stella. You're free to go.

1086
01:17:49,190 --> 01:17:52,130
你比这个逃避兵役的家伙强多了
You're so much better than this draft dodger.

1087
01:17:53,040 --> 01:17:55,160
拜托  你爸爸会怎么说
Come on, what would your father say?

1088
01:17:56,890 --> 01:17:58,000
我不走
I'm not leaving.

1089
01:18:01,010 --> 01:18:02,170
既然你不打算去越南
Since you're not going to 'Nam,

1090
01:18:02,170 --> 01:18:06,000
也许拘留一晚会让你松口
maybe a night behind bars will loosen those lips of yours.

1091
01:18:07,480 --> 01:18:08,710
走吧  霍布斯
Come on, Hobbs.

1092
01:18:10,150 --> 01:18:12,020
回家把钱准备好
Go home, dig out that 10 bucks

1093
01:18:12,020 --> 01:18:14,300
等尼克松赢了大选你就欠我十块钱了
you're gonna owe me when Nixon wins,

1094
01:18:14,440 --> 01:18:16,310
今晚我来关门
and, uh, I'll close up here.

1095
01:18:16,310 --> 01:18:17,050
好  晚安
All right, have a good night.

1096
01:18:17,050 --> 01:18:18,710
晚安  小情侣
Nighty-night, lovebirds.

1097
01:18:19,860 --> 01:18:21,390
我应该告诉你的
I should've told you.

1098
01:18:23,050 --> 01:18:24,440
你肯定觉得我是个懦夫  但是
You must think I'm a coward, but...

1099
01:18:24,450 --> 01:18:25,960
我绝对不会那么想
I would never think that.

1100
01:18:34,560 --> 01:18:38,030
两个月前他们把我哥从越南运回来了
Two months ago they shipped my brother back from Vietnam

1101
01:18:38,930 --> 01:18:40,170
他的尸体残骸
in pieces.

1102
01:18:41,290 --> 01:18:42,850
我很遗憾
I'm so sorry.

1103
01:18:46,150 --> 01:18:48,860
上周我收到征兵通知的时候
Last week when I got my draft notice,

1104
01:18:51,090 --> 01:18:52,240
我没办法
I couldn't.

1105
01:18:52,980 --> 01:18:54,770
他们只是让你去送死
They just send you there to die.

1106
01:18:55,970 --> 01:18:57,810
如果这本书读了我
If the book reads me,

1107
01:18:59,230 --> 01:19:00,980
我担心它会讲述什么
I'm afraid what it's going to say.

1108
01:19:28,320 --> 01:19:29,760
吃吧  孩子
There you go, boy.

1109
01:19:30,010 --> 01:19:31,930
好吃吧
Yeah, that's good, huh?

1110
01:19:40,080 --> 01:19:43,040
《叮里个咚咚叮》
"Me Tie Dough-ty Walker"?

1111
01:19:41,040 --> 01:19:43,420
叮里个咚咚叮

1112
01:19:53,480 --> 01:19:56,000
这些变态故事是谁想出来的
Who came up with all this sick stuff?

1113
01:19:57,590 --> 01:19:59,060
是你吗  斯黛拉
Is this you, Stella?

1114
01:20:00,210 --> 01:20:02,370
这些故事不是我们写的
We didn't write the stories.

1115
01:20:39,660 --> 01:20:40,700
扳机
Trigger?

1116
01:20:43,700 --> 01:20:45,330
等等  有新故事了吗
Wait, is there another story?

1117
01:20:46,530 --> 01:20:47,620
求你了  你得放我们出去
Please, you have to let us out!

1118
01:20:47,620 --> 01:20:48,750
如果有新故事了
Okay, if there's another story,

1119
01:20:48,750 --> 01:20:50,910
我们都会有危险
we are all gonna be in danger.

1120
01:20:53,460 --> 01:20:55,040
告诉我们发生了什么
Tell us what's happening!

1121
01:20:55,060 --> 01:20:56,540
是什么故事
What's the story?

1122
01:21:01,680 --> 01:21:02,850
求你了  听我说好吗
Please just listen to me, okay?

1123
01:21:02,850 --> 01:21:04,310
我们都会死
We're all going to die.

1124
01:21:20,010 --> 01:21:21,270
轮到我了
It's my turn.

1125
01:21:21,480 --> 01:21:23,820
故事里发生了什么
Okay, what happens in the story?

1126
01:21:24,850 --> 01:21:27,060
告诉我书里写了哪个名字就行
Just tell me which name is in the book.

1127
01:21:28,000 --> 01:21:29,120
雷蒙
Ramon.

1128
01:21:40,080 --> 01:21:41,620
是个篝火晚会上讲的故事
It's a campfire story.

1129
01:21:42,170 --> 01:21:43,760
曾经把我吓得要死
It used to scare me to death.

1130
01:21:48,920 --> 01:21:50,480
叮咚人要来了
The Jangly Man is coming.

1131
01:21:50,650 --> 01:21:52,640
-他要带我去...  -发生什么了
- He's going to take me... - What's going on?

1132
01:21:52,640 --> 01:21:54,290
他会说那句话的  小心听
He's going to say it. Listen.

1133
01:22:02,090 --> 01:22:06,100
叮里个咚咚叮
Me tie dough-ty walker!

1134
01:22:06,100 --> 01:22:07,900
你在耍我吗
Are you shitting me?

1135
01:22:28,590 --> 01:22:30,650
求你了  放我们出去
Please, just let us out, please!

1136
01:23:03,740 --> 01:23:08,040
叮里个咚咚叮
Me tie dough-ty walker!

1137
01:23:25,770 --> 01:23:27,140
雷蒙
Ramon!

1138
01:23:29,280 --> 01:23:30,730
雷蒙
Ramon.

1139
01:23:31,070 --> 01:23:32,600
天啊  雷蒙
Oh, my God, Ramon.

1140
01:23:32,920 --> 01:23:34,740
天啊  这是什么
Oh, my God, what is that?

1141
01:23:37,670 --> 01:23:41,100
救命  救命啊  有人能听到吗
Help. Help, please. Can someone hear me?

1142
01:23:46,770 --> 01:23:47,850
钥匙
Keys.

1143
01:23:48,150 --> 01:23:49,000
快
Hurry!

1144
01:24:05,760 --> 01:24:07,510
懦夫
Coward!

1145
01:24:10,000 --> 01:24:11,360
我拿到钥匙了
I got the keys.

1146
01:24:13,280 --> 01:24:14,720
快  快  快
Come on, come on, come on, come on.

1147
01:24:18,580 --> 01:24:19,810
懦夫
Coward!

1148
01:24:21,970 --> 01:24:24,180
快跑  快  快
Run! Go, go, go!

1149
01:24:38,720 --> 01:24:40,300
你还在等什么
What are you waiting for?

1150
01:24:41,030 --> 01:24:42,110
回她家去
Go to the house.

1151
01:24:42,690 --> 01:24:43,810
告诉她真相
Tell her the truth.

1152
01:24:43,810 --> 01:24:45,370
那东西会跟着我
That thing will follow me.

1153
01:24:45,370 --> 01:24:47,450
但这些故事每次都成真了
But the stories come true every time.

1154
01:24:47,450 --> 01:24:49,000
那你最好跑快点
Then you better run fast.

1155
01:24:49,610 --> 01:24:51,970
阻止她你就能阻止这一切
Stop her and you'll stop this.

1156
01:26:36,110 --> 01:26:37,360
莎拉
Sarah!

1157
01:26:37,610 --> 01:26:39,230
你能听到吗
Can you hear me?

1158
01:26:39,770 --> 01:26:42,860
该死的  你不能再讲这些故事了
God damn you! You have to stop telling these stories!

1159
01:26:42,860 --> 01:26:44,870
我们又没伤害你
We didn't do anything to you!

1160
01:26:44,870 --> 01:26:47,650
我们只想帮你  我们知道你是无辜的
We just want to help you! We know you're innocent!

1161
01:26:47,700 --> 01:26:49,650
我们知道你没有给那些孩子下毒
We know you didn't poison the kids!

1162
01:26:49,650 --> 01:26:53,130
但是求你了  不要再讲这些故事了
But, please, you just have to stop telling the stories!

1163
01:27:47,940 --> 01:27:49,020
斯黛拉
Stella!

1164
01:27:49,420 --> 01:27:50,780
你在哪
Where are you?

1165
01:27:55,650 --> 01:27:58,160
鬼屋

1166
01:27:57,290 --> 01:27:58,660
不不不
No, no, no, no.

1167
01:27:58,160 --> 01:28:00,420
斯黛拉

1168
01:27:59,650 --> 01:28:00,680
斯黛拉
Stella.

1169
01:28:07,830 --> 01:28:08,900
斯黛拉
Stella!

1170
01:28:21,220 --> 01:28:22,310
斯黛拉
Hey, Stella!

1171
01:28:27,330 --> 01:28:28,760
她又不在自己房间里
She's out of her room again.

1172
01:28:28,770 --> 01:28:31,050
孩子们  莎拉出来了
Boys? Sarah's out!

1173
01:28:31,720 --> 01:28:33,260
马上把她找出来
Find her now!

1174
01:28:34,270 --> 01:28:35,440
莎拉
Sarah!

1175
01:28:43,860 --> 01:28:45,020
莎拉
Sarah!

1176
01:28:47,820 --> 01:28:49,800
交给我吧  哈罗德
You leave that to me, Harold.

1177
01:28:53,530 --> 01:28:54,900
莎拉
Sarah!

1178
01:28:56,640 --> 01:28:58,930
莎拉  你在哪
Sarah, where are you?

1179
01:29:06,120 --> 01:29:07,060
莎拉
Sarah!

1180
01:29:20,650 --> 01:29:22,140
我听到了
I hear her.

1181
01:29:30,820 --> 01:29:32,330
她在这儿
She's here!

1182
01:29:33,920 --> 01:29:36,070
她在这里
She's in here!

1183
01:29:54,650 --> 01:29:55,590
莎拉
Sarah!

1184
01:29:58,450 --> 01:29:59,580
你在哪
Where are you?

1185
01:30:06,210 --> 01:30:07,440
露露
Lou Lou.

1186
01:30:24,880 --> 01:30:25,680
你看到莎拉了吗
Did you see Sarah?

1187
01:30:25,680 --> 01:30:26,720
没有  女士
No, ma'am.

1188
01:30:26,720 --> 01:30:27,910
她在撒谎
She's lying.

1189
01:30:28,100 --> 01:30:31,360
你不会撒谎吧  露露
You wouldn't lie, Lou Lou?

1190
01:30:31,380 --> 01:30:32,370
不会  女士
No, ma'am.

1191
01:30:32,420 --> 01:30:33,790
我没看到莎拉
No, I didn't see Sarah.

1192
01:30:33,790 --> 01:30:35,530
不要  贝洛斯先生  求你了
No, Mr. Bellows, please, no!

1193
01:30:35,540 --> 01:30:36,910
求你了  不要
Please, no!

1194
01:31:08,060 --> 01:31:09,690
你躲不过我们的
You can't hide from us.

1195
01:31:10,090 --> 01:31:10,600
抓到你了
Got you!

1196
01:31:10,600 --> 01:31:11,980
不  不
No! No!

1197
01:31:11,980 --> 01:31:14,560
救救我  救救我
Help me! Help me!

1198
01:31:14,730 --> 01:31:17,370
-救救我  -斯黛拉
- Help me! - Stella!

1199
01:31:17,390 --> 01:31:20,560
救救我
Please! Help me!

1200
01:31:20,560 --> 01:31:22,440
-救救我  -她一直在跟大家说水的事
- Please, help me! - She's been telling everyone about the water.

1201
01:31:22,440 --> 01:31:23,000
我们该拿她怎么办
What should we do with her?

1202
01:31:23,000 --> 01:31:25,150
-谁来救救我  -闭上你的臭嘴
- Somebody, help me, please. - You're going to shut your ugly mouth

1203
01:31:25,150 --> 01:31:26,250
不然我们就帮你把嘴封上
or we're going to shut it for you.

1204
01:31:26,250 --> 01:31:28,250
救救我
Please, help me!

1205
01:31:28,910 --> 01:31:30,850
救救我
Help me, please!

1206
01:31:36,000 --> 01:31:36,740
回你该待的地方去
Going back where you belong.

1207
01:31:36,740 --> 01:31:39,530
救救我
Help me, please.

1208
01:31:39,530 --> 01:31:41,680
把嘴闭上  不然你知道会有什么下场
Be quiet or you know what you'll get.

1209
01:31:41,680 --> 01:31:45,700
求求你们  我不是莎拉
Please. I'm not Sarah. Please!

1210
01:31:45,820 --> 01:31:48,690
求你们放我走
Please let me go. Please...

1211
01:31:48,730 --> 01:31:50,430
放我走
Let me go.

1212
01:31:51,450 --> 01:31:52,730
求你们别把我关在这里
Please, don't put me in here.

1213
01:31:52,730 --> 01:31:53,690
再敢跑出去  我们就送你去精神病院
Try this again and we'll send you to the asylum.

1214
01:31:53,690 --> 01:31:56,260
求求你们  等等
Please. Wait! Please?

1215
01:31:57,880 --> 01:31:59,800
你应该待在自己的房间里的
You should have stayed in your room.

1216
01:31:59,930 --> 01:32:02,160
求求你们
Please. Please. Please.

1217
01:32:02,160 --> 01:32:03,480
不是我干的
I didn't do it.

1218
01:32:03,490 --> 01:32:05,170
你不配有灯光
You don't deserve the light.

1219
01:32:05,290 --> 01:32:06,410
不
No!

1220
01:32:08,090 --> 01:32:10,770
我告诉你了  我告诉你了
I'm telling you, I'm telling you,

1221
01:32:10,770 --> 01:32:12,560
我不是莎拉
I'm not Sarah.

1222
01:32:14,100 --> 01:32:15,790
求你了
Please.

1223
01:33:24,150 --> 01:33:26,270
斯黛拉
Stella...

1224
01:33:40,680 --> 01:33:42,950
我还有一个故事
I have another story

1225
01:33:43,100 --> 01:33:45,170
专为你准备
just for you.

1226
01:33:51,370 --> 01:33:52,430
斯黛拉
Stella,

1227
01:33:54,580 --> 01:33:57,830
如果你能听到  不管你在哪里
if you can hear me, wherever you are,

1228
01:33:58,550 --> 01:34:01,000
告诉她真相
tell her the truth.

1229
01:34:06,590 --> 01:34:07,870
不
No.

1230
01:34:09,990 --> 01:34:12,950
该讲故事给你听了  莎拉
It's time that you hear a story, Sarah.

1231
01:34:16,960 --> 01:34:18,410
你曾经是受害者
You were a victim.

1232
01:34:19,970 --> 01:34:22,540
现在你变成了怪物
Now you've turned into a monster.

1233
01:34:23,890 --> 01:34:26,250
变成了他们口中的怪物
The one that they said you were.

1234
01:34:35,410 --> 01:34:36,390
斯黛拉
Stella.

1235
01:34:37,910 --> 01:34:39,930
你夺走了我的朋友
You took my friends.

1236
01:34:41,300 --> 01:34:43,930
我最爱的两个人
Two of the people that I love most.

1237
01:34:52,380 --> 01:34:54,190
雷蒙
Ramon!

1238
01:34:55,670 --> 01:34:56,930
斯黛拉
Stella!

1239
01:34:58,400 --> 01:35:00,360
你也要夺走他吗
Are you going to take him, too?

1240
01:35:01,420 --> 01:35:03,540
你的家人对你做了什么
What your family did to you,

1241
01:35:04,260 --> 01:35:06,120
他们说了什么  那是他们的错
what they said, that's on them.

1242
01:35:07,890 --> 01:35:09,340
但是你的所作所为
But what you do,

1243
01:35:11,850 --> 01:35:13,670
这是你的错  莎拉
this is on you, Sarah.

1244
01:35:17,110 --> 01:35:18,570
都是你的错
It's all on you.

1245
01:35:26,590 --> 01:35:28,480
我会讲述你的故事
I'll tell your story.

1246
01:35:30,930 --> 01:35:33,560
真实的故事  我会说出真相
The real story, I'll tell the truth.

1247
01:35:36,930 --> 01:35:38,260
但是这种愤怒
But the rage,

1248
01:35:39,070 --> 01:35:42,020
愤怒必须停止  莎拉
the rage has to stop, Sarah.

1249
01:36:02,860 --> 01:36:04,390
用你的血
Use your blood.

1250
01:36:27,200 --> 01:36:30,320
莎拉·贝洛斯是无辜的
Sarah Bellows was innocent.

1251
01:36:30,320 --> 01:36:32,910
她知道真相
She knew the truth,

1252
01:36:33,700 --> 01:36:35,600
并试图阻止他们
and tried to stop them.

1253
01:36:35,600 --> 01:36:36,930
她很勇敢
She was brave.

1254
01:36:37,440 --> 01:36:40,770
她被自己的家人
She was harmed and destroyed

1255
01:36:40,770 --> 01:36:42,690
伤害并毁灭
by her own family.

1256
01:36:42,930 --> 01:36:45,070
被他们的贪婪
By their greed,

1257
01:36:45,500 --> 01:36:47,230
他们的谎言
and their lies

1258
01:36:47,750 --> 01:36:49,430
和他们的罪恶
and their sins.

1259
01:36:51,510 --> 01:36:53,310
我会讲述你的故事
I'll tell your story.

1260
01:36:58,450 --> 01:36:59,980
你可以放手了
You can let it go.

1261
01:37:02,150 --> 01:37:03,750
你可以放手了  莎拉
You can let it go, Sarah.

1262
01:37:48,960 --> 01:37:50,710
故事可以伤人
Stories hurt.

1263
01:37:51,090 --> 01:37:52,560
故事可以治愈
Stories heal.

1264
01:37:56,440 --> 01:37:58,880
只要讲的次数够多
If we repeat them often enough,

1265
01:37:58,880 --> 01:38:00,230
它们就会成真
they become real.

1266
01:38:00,860 --> 01:38:02,510
它们有这种力量
They have that power.

1267
01:38:06,240 --> 01:38:07,730
它们塑造我们
They make us who we are.

1268
01:38:07,730 --> 01:38:08,590
斯黛拉
Stella.

1269
01:38:08,890 --> 01:38:10,880
你没事我就放心了
I'm just so happy you're okay.

1270
01:38:23,390 --> 01:38:26,500
如果说我从莎拉身上学到了什么
And if there's anything I learned from Sarah,

1271
01:38:28,130 --> 01:38:29,840
那就是永不放弃
it's to never give up.

1272
01:38:32,460 --> 01:38:36,280
我信守承诺  讲述了莎拉的故事
I told Sarah's story exactly as I promised.

1273
01:38:37,540 --> 01:38:40,510
我描述那个在黑暗中写故事的
I wrote about the pale, lonely girl

1274
01:38:40,510 --> 01:38:42,670
苍白孤独的女孩
who wrote stories in the dark.

1275
01:38:42,530 --> 01:38:48,180
恐怖故事背后的真相

1276
01:38:43,590 --> 01:38:47,430
以及她是如何被她的家人变成一个怪物的
And how she was turned into a monster by her family.

1277
01:38:48,190 --> 01:38:50,070
优胜故事
作者  斯黛拉·尼科尔斯

1278
01:38:50,260 --> 01:38:53,590
有些人相信我  但大多数人不相信
Some people believed me. Most didn't.

1279
01:38:53,690 --> 01:38:55,300
因为就像莎拉一样
Because, like Sarah,

1280
01:38:55,680 --> 01:38:57,510
我曾经也是一个
I was a lonely girl

1281
01:38:57,510 --> 01:39:00,260
擅长讲述恐怖故事的孤独的女孩
who knew how to tell a good creepy story.

1282
01:38:58,050 --> 01:38:59,280
专车

1283
01:39:06,990 --> 01:39:07,930
写信给我
Write me?

1284
01:39:20,500 --> 01:39:21,540
每天都写
Every day.

1285
01:39:23,260 --> 01:39:24,290
回头见
See you around.

1286
01:39:29,110 --> 01:39:30,170
孩子  你叫什么
What's your name, kid?

1287
01:39:30,180 --> 01:39:31,740
雷蒙·莫拉莱斯
Ramon Morales.

1288
01:39:31,680 --> 01:39:33,200
除美国陆军车辆外禁止停车

1289
01:39:35,810 --> 01:39:38,230
故事可以教导我们关怀
Stories can teach us to care.

1290
01:39:41,620 --> 01:39:43,020
它们使我们鼓起勇气
They make us brave enough

1291
01:39:43,020 --> 01:39:45,070
承认我们需要彼此
to admit that we need each other.

1292
01:39:46,130 --> 01:39:49,190
给我们一个可以回去的家
Give us a home to go back to.

1293
01:39:46,600 --> 01:39:49,430
请尽快回家

1294
01:39:49,770 --> 01:39:51,440
爱你的斯黛拉

1295
01:40:00,970 --> 01:40:04,720
查克和奥吉还没回来
Chuck and Auggie are still gone,

1296
01:40:05,320 --> 01:40:08,640
但我知道有办法带他们回来
but I know there is a way to bring them back

1297
01:40:08,640 --> 01:40:10,700
而秘密就在书中
and that the secret is in the book.

1298
01:40:12,020 --> 01:40:14,540
不找到他们
And we won't stop...

1299
01:40:16,140 --> 01:40:17,680
我们决不放弃
until we find them.

1300
01:40:43,280 --> 01:40:53,150
在黑暗中讲述的恐怖故事

