1
00:00:54,730 --> 00:00:58,740
当时所有的报纸都在报道
Ilt was in all the papers at the time.

2
00:00:58,740 --> 00:01:03,710
人们在北极发现了一种黄色的金属
Men searching in the arctic had found a yellow metal.

3
00:01:05,040 --> 00:01:06,510
金子
Gold.

4
00:01:07,610 --> 00:01:12,680
世界各地掀起了一场狂潮
A mad fever spread as far as word can travel

5
00:01:12,690 --> 00:01:17,890
驱使着成千上万的人北上 希望能被幸运之神眷顾
And thousands more rushed to the north to try their luck.

6
00:01:19,390 --> 00:01:21,860
这些人需要狗
These men needed dogs.

7
00:01:21,860 --> 00:01:26,430
足够强壮的狗 来拉他们的雪橇
Big dogs with strong muscles to pull their sleds.

8
00:01:29,330 --> 00:01:31,630
早上好 巴克
Good morning there, buck!

9
00:01:31,640 --> 00:01:34,210
巴克既不是家养犬
Buck was neither house dog

10
00:01:34,210 --> 00:01:35,340
也不是犬舍犬
Nor kennel dog.

11
00:01:35,340 --> 00:01:36,710
给你啦 孩子
Here you go, boy.

12
00:01:36,710 --> 00:01:39,240
他的主人是圣克拉拉郡的法官
His master was santa clara county judge.

13
00:01:39,240 --> 00:01:40,540
嘿
Hey!

14
00:01:41,780 --> 00:01:43,410
喂 看着点路
Whoa! watch it, you!

15
00:01:43,420 --> 00:01:46,950
在这个地盘 巴克就是国王
In this realm, buck was king.

16
00:01:48,020 --> 00:01:49,220
该死的 小畜生
Damn it, creature!

17
00:01:49,220 --> 00:01:51,420
长点心 那是米勒法官的狗
Careful! that's judge miller's dog.

18
00:01:51,420 --> 00:01:53,390
替我祝法官大人生日快乐
You wish the judge a happy birthday from me.

19
00:01:53,390 --> 00:01:55,160
谢谢 会转达的 巴克 我们走吧
Thanks, will do. come on, buck! let's go.

20
00:01:55,160 --> 00:01:56,460
克朗代克
klondike!

21
00:01:56,460 --> 00:01:59,160
上千淘金者涌入道森市 (加拿大北部)
Thousands of gold rushers converge in dawson city!

22
00:01:59,170 --> 00:02:00,970
克朗代克速报
News of the klondike! oh.

23
00:02:00,970 --> 00:02:02,670
给你吧 小家伙
Here you go, lad.

24
00:02:04,640 --> 00:02:05,970
巴克 停下
Buck, stop!

25
00:02:05,970 --> 00:02:07,040
巴克
Buck!

26
00:02:07,040 --> 00:02:08,110
让开 快让开
Get out of the way! get out of the way!

27
00:02:08,110 --> 00:02:09,340
巴克
Buck!

28
00:02:09,340 --> 00:02:11,340
快抓住它 别动
come get it, stop!

29
00:02:11,340 --> 00:02:12,940
女士 快叫住你的狗
Lady, call your dog!

30
00:02:12,950 --> 00:02:14,480
小心
Look out!

31
00:02:15,210 --> 00:02:16,450
让开
Out of the way!

32
00:02:16,450 --> 00:02:18,750
- 这就对了 - 巴克 回来
- that's right! - buck! stop!

33
00:02:22,660 --> 00:02:23,690
巴克
Buck.

34
00:02:25,360 --> 00:02:27,460
不要 我非常抱歉
No! i'm so, so sorry!

35
00:02:27,460 --> 00:02:29,730
- 对不起 - 这狗太危险了
- I'm sorry. - that dog's a menace.

36
00:02:29,730 --> 00:02:31,700
他只是被宠坏了
Oh, he's just spoiled.

37
00:02:31,700 --> 00:02:33,630
巴克没有恶意
Buck means well.

38
00:02:33,630 --> 00:02:34,530
大部分时候
Usually.

39
00:02:34,530 --> 00:02:36,670
阿比盖尔 厨师找你
Abigail, cook needs you.

40
00:02:36,670 --> 00:02:37,970
巴克
Buck.

41
00:02:37,970 --> 00:02:39,340
去把孩子们叫醒
Go wake the girls.

42
00:03:06,930 --> 00:03:09,370
快把烤好的收起来
Grab the roast!

43
00:03:11,270 --> 00:03:13,110
我得小心点
Uh... i'll look out!

44
00:03:23,220 --> 00:03:25,420
出去
Out!

45
00:03:51,040 --> 00:03:51,910
不行
No.

46
00:03:51,910 --> 00:03:53,880
巴克 记着我们说好的
Remember we talked about this, buck.

47
00:03:53,880 --> 00:03:56,250
今天 你必须表现出最好的一面
Today you need to be on your best behavior.

48
00:03:58,120 --> 00:03:59,750
巴克
Buck?

49
00:04:17,740 --> 00:04:18,670
阁下
Your honor.

50
00:04:18,670 --> 00:04:21,870
闻起来真香
Smells very, very good.

51
00:04:23,680 --> 00:04:25,240
大家先到这儿来
Everyone over here first.

52
00:04:38,290 --> 00:04:40,860
好了 莫莉 你真漂亮
All right, molly. you look beautiful.

53
00:04:40,860 --> 00:04:42,590
好了 准备
All right. settle.

54
00:04:53,110 --> 00:04:55,070
巴克
Buck.

55
00:05:25,370 --> 00:05:27,670
你给我呆在外面
Why don't you sit out here

56
00:05:28,570 --> 00:05:31,710
好好想想你干了些什么
And you think on what you've done.

57
00:05:35,180 --> 00:05:37,120
不 巴克 现在不行
No. not now, buck.

58
00:06:00,970 --> 00:06:05,060
这不是巴克在走廊上度过的第一个晚上
This wasn't the first night Buck spent on the porch.

59
00:06:13,250 --> 00:06:14,850
过来 巴克 过来
Come on, buck. come on.

60
00:06:18,690 --> 00:06:22,340
他对主人的命令不是很上心
He was less attentive to his master's commands...

61
00:06:22,860 --> 00:06:24,960
嘿 巴克 我这儿有吃的
Hey, buck. i got a treat for ya.

62
00:06:24,960 --> 00:06:27,530
他更遵循自己的本能
...than he was to his own instincts.

63
00:06:27,530 --> 00:06:28,770
来吧
Come on.

64
00:06:29,530 --> 00:06:31,170
吃吧 过来
Get the treat. come on!

65
00:06:32,040 --> 00:06:33,100
好孩子
Good boy.

66
00:06:33,110 --> 00:06:34,570
乖
Good boy.

67
00:06:34,570 --> 00:06:36,680
去吧 快去吃
Get the treat. get the treat.

68
00:06:40,610 --> 00:06:42,610
好孩子 真乖
Good boy. good boy!

69
00:06:50,060 --> 00:06:52,490
叫它巴克它会答应的
He answers to the name of Buck.

70
00:06:52,490 --> 00:06:54,760
他在那边能卖个好价钱
He'll fetch a fine price where he's going.

71
00:07:15,180 --> 00:07:16,210
坚持住
Hold up!

72
00:07:16,220 --> 00:07:19,220
最后这次中转还需要点人手
I'll need extra hands for this last transfer.

73
00:07:25,460 --> 00:07:28,060
这里面装的什么鬼
What in the world is in this thing?

74
00:07:28,060 --> 00:07:29,190
狗
Dog.

75
00:07:29,200 --> 00:07:30,490
几只
How many?

76
00:07:30,500 --> 00:07:31,660
就一只
Just one.

77
00:08:11,940 --> 00:08:13,700
关在那个箱子里
Locked in that box...

78
00:08:15,980 --> 00:08:19,380
无法进食 喝水 也无法睡觉
...he couldn't eat, drink, or sleep.

79
00:08:20,880 --> 00:08:23,780
巴克不知道他在哪
Buck had no idea where he was,

80
00:08:25,250 --> 00:08:26,990
经过了哪些地方
Where he had been,

81
00:08:27,720 --> 00:08:29,860
之后要去哪
Where he was going.

82
00:08:50,680 --> 00:08:51,940
放轻松 小伙子
Easy, boy.

83
00:08:54,280 --> 00:08:56,980
你只需要
All you have to do

84
00:08:56,980 --> 00:08:58,780
坐下
Is sit.

85
00:09:13,000 --> 00:09:15,300
这已经不是南方了
This ain't the southland anymore.

86
00:09:17,100 --> 00:09:18,300
来
Go on.

87
00:09:19,640 --> 00:09:21,000
自己看
See it.

88
00:09:21,010 --> 00:09:22,810
小伙子 你看
See it, boy.

89
00:09:23,910 --> 00:09:26,780
在这片土地 这就是律法
It's the law of the land now.

90
00:09:27,250 --> 00:09:29,780
建立在棍棒
The law of club

91
00:09:30,420 --> 00:09:32,080
和爪牙之上的律法
And fang.

92
00:09:33,790 --> 00:09:35,850
无人能凌驾在这之上
No one above it.

93
00:09:37,820 --> 00:09:39,960
所以你现在打算怎样 狗狗
Now what's it gonna be, doggy?

94
00:09:48,530 --> 00:09:50,040
很好
Good.

95
00:09:50,470 --> 00:09:51,840
很好
Good.

96
00:09:52,500 --> 00:09:54,270
你学得很快
You a fast learner.

97
00:10:09,690 --> 00:10:11,120
巴克在拿着棍棒的男人面前
Buck stood no chance

98
00:10:11,120 --> 00:10:13,760
毫无还击之力
Against a man with a club.

99
00:10:15,730 --> 00:10:17,760
他很清楚
He knew that.

100
00:10:18,560 --> 00:10:20,000
他被打败了
He was beaten.

101
00:10:24,640 --> 00:10:26,900
但这并没摧毁他的意志
But he was not broken.

102
00:10:45,460 --> 00:10:46,460
喂
Hey!

103
00:10:48,490 --> 00:10:50,860
快回来
Come on!

104
00:11:15,050 --> 00:11:17,120
斯卡圭 阿拉斯加
Skagway, alaska.

105
00:11:17,720 --> 00:11:19,860
育空河口
Gateway to the yukon.

106
00:11:20,490 --> 00:11:22,790
荒野的边界
The edge of nowhere.

107
00:11:22,800 --> 00:11:27,160
淘金人几乎都会经过这里
Most anyone looking for gold went through here first.

108
00:11:27,170 --> 00:11:29,600
好了 我们走吧
All right, let's go, let's go.

109
00:11:29,600 --> 00:11:31,030
真听话
There you go.

110
00:11:33,070 --> 00:11:34,540
来点驯鹿汤吗
Get your caribou stew! right there.

111
00:11:34,540 --> 00:11:37,110
巴克离家千里
Buck was a long way from home.

112
00:11:38,510 --> 00:11:42,110
你会因为对金子的贪婪背叛上帝吗
Will you betray our god for your lust of gold?

113
00:11:42,110 --> 00:11:43,550
别理他们 走吧
Don't mind them. come on.

114
00:11:43,550 --> 00:11:45,020
不 这边
No. this way. this way.

115
00:11:47,950 --> 00:11:49,320
快点 动起来
Come on! move.

116
00:11:49,320 --> 00:11:52,090
嘿 快过来
Hey. come on. come on.

117
00:11:59,300 --> 00:12:01,230
过来吧 伙计
Come on now, buddy.

118
00:12:01,230 --> 00:12:03,240
巴克 这只是雪 来吧
It's just snow, buck. come on.

119
00:12:25,620 --> 00:12:27,560
喂 巴克 过来
Hey! buck, come on!

120
00:12:28,730 --> 00:12:29,930
快给我过来
Get over here!

121
00:12:31,930 --> 00:12:33,130
巴克
Buck!

122
00:12:40,510 --> 00:12:41,870
好了
All right.

123
00:12:41,880 --> 00:12:43,310
就这样
That's it.

124
00:12:43,980 --> 00:12:45,610
房子是她的了?
The house is hers?

125
00:12:45,610 --> 00:12:48,510
是的 先生 包括房子里面的所有
Yes, sir. the house and everything in it.

126
00:12:49,310 --> 00:12:50,750
挺好
That's good.

127
00:12:50,750 --> 00:12:52,420
是她应得的
She deserves it.

128
00:12:52,420 --> 00:12:54,380
上船
All aboard!

129
00:12:54,390 --> 00:12:56,750
去年好像运势不太好
Not much luck up there this last year.

130
00:12:56,760 --> 00:12:58,090
比起满载而归的
Seems more folks coming back

131
00:12:58,090 --> 00:13:00,090
更多人两手空空地回来了
Pockets empty than full of gold.

132
00:13:01,130 --> 00:13:03,100
我不是来淘金的
I'm not looking for gold.

133
00:13:21,110 --> 00:13:23,480
喂 拜托
Hey! jeez...

134
00:13:31,490 --> 00:13:32,690
注意点
Watch yourself.

135
00:13:42,130 --> 00:13:46,240
去道森的最后一班船要发了
Last boat to dawson leaving now!

136
00:13:46,240 --> 00:13:48,510
不上的话 开春之前只能坐雪橇过去了
Miss it, it's only sleds till spring.

137
00:13:57,920 --> 00:13:59,450
这是我的
That's mine.

138
00:13:59,450 --> 00:14:01,750
嘿 谢谢
Hey! thanks.

139
00:14:01,750 --> 00:14:02,950
巴克
Buck!

140
00:14:02,960 --> 00:14:04,520
抓到你了
Got ya.

141
00:14:04,520 --> 00:14:05,990
他叫巴克吗
Buck's his name?

142
00:14:06,630 --> 00:14:07,690
我们走吧
Come on, let's go.

143
00:14:07,690 --> 00:14:08,760
谢谢你 巴克
Thanks, buck.

144
00:14:08,760 --> 00:14:10,560
你跑的真快
You're a fast one.

145
00:14:10,560 --> 00:14:12,160
好了 过来
All right. this way.

146
00:14:19,540 --> 00:14:20,500
早上好
Good morning.

147
00:14:20,510 --> 00:14:22,610
佩罗 好久不见
Perrault! been a long time.

148
00:14:22,610 --> 00:14:23,670
很高兴见到你
Good to see you.

149
00:14:23,680 --> 00:14:24,840
你过得怎样
How've you been?

150
00:14:24,840 --> 00:14:26,210
挺不错的
Good, good.

151
00:14:26,210 --> 00:14:29,040
电报还没抢光邮政的生意吗
So, telegraph hasn't put the mail service out of business yet?

152
00:14:29,480 --> 00:14:30,380
还没
Not yet.

153
00:14:30,380 --> 00:14:32,350
我的队伍缺两只狗
I need two dogs for my team.

154
00:15:02,310 --> 00:15:03,950
你想先上去吗
You wanna go?

155
00:15:03,950 --> 00:15:05,420
不用等我
Don't wait for me!

156
00:15:23,770 --> 00:15:25,300
你好 弗朗索瓦丝 Francoise
Bonjour, francoise!

157
00:15:29,270 --> 00:15:31,780
你这回又干了什么
What have you done now?

158
00:15:34,850 --> 00:15:36,780
这是巴克
This is buck.

159
00:15:37,880 --> 00:15:40,490
两只  我说过我们要两只
Two. we needed two.

160
00:15:41,720 --> 00:15:43,620
那又怎样 他这么大
What? he's big.

161
00:15:43,620 --> 00:15:44,590
太大了
Too big.

162
00:15:44,590 --> 00:15:46,260
- 他不行 - 他可以的
- he'll never make it. - he'll make it.

163
00:15:46,260 --> 00:15:48,490
你懂什么
What do you know? aah.

164
00:15:48,490 --> 00:15:50,630
先带你认识一下队员们吧
Okay, let's you meet the team.

165
00:15:50,630 --> 00:15:53,000
巴克 这是斯皮茨
Buck, meet spitz.

166
00:15:53,000 --> 00:15:55,170
你的新老大
Your new boss.

167
00:15:55,170 --> 00:15:56,830
别惹他
Stay out of his way.

168
00:15:58,910 --> 00:16:00,270
这是多莉
That's dolly.

169
00:16:00,740 --> 00:16:02,110
派克
Pike.

170
00:16:02,110 --> 00:16:03,540
乔
Jo.

171
00:16:03,540 --> 00:16:04,540
比利
Billie.

172
00:16:04,980 --> 00:16:06,180
杜布
Dub.

173
00:16:06,780 --> 00:16:07,880
戴夫
Dave.

174
00:16:08,650 --> 00:16:10,180
和索莱尔
And sol-leks.

175
00:16:10,180 --> 00:16:11,880
你的位置在这
You are here.

176
00:16:15,960 --> 00:16:17,590
欢迎加入
Welcome to the team.

177
00:16:19,190 --> 00:16:22,190
大家注意 我们有一条新路线
We have a new route, so everyone pay attention.

178
00:16:23,330 --> 00:16:26,200
说的就是你 戴夫 我们在这
You, too, dave. we are here.

179
00:16:26,200 --> 00:16:31,200
我们要把邮件送到800公里外的地方
We deliver mail 500 miles all the way to here.

180
00:16:31,540 --> 00:16:32,740
道森
Dawson.

181
00:16:32,740 --> 00:16:34,300
他们可听不懂你说的话
They don't understand you.

182
00:16:34,310 --> 00:16:38,080
巴克 斯皮茨做啥你就做啥 懂了吗
Buck, just do what spitz does. okay?

183
00:16:38,080 --> 00:16:39,880
他领队 你跟着他
He leads, you follow.

184
00:16:53,890 --> 00:16:55,160
大家 准备好了吗
Team,  ready?

185
00:16:56,060 --> 00:16:58,800
谨记 我们肩负着的不仅仅是邮件
Remember, we don't just carry the mail,

186
00:16:58,800 --> 00:17:00,530
还有生命
We carry lives!

187
00:17:00,530 --> 00:17:02,900
出发
And, mush!

188
00:17:06,540 --> 00:17:08,300
快点 走啊
Come on, mush!

189
00:17:14,010 --> 00:17:15,350
前进
Allez!

190
00:17:18,550 --> 00:17:19,680
前进
Allez!

191
00:17:33,770 --> 00:17:35,730
斯皮茨 驾
Spitz! gee!

192
00:17:58,000 --> 00:18:01,060
这下你满意了?现在我们是一条绳上的蚂蚱了
You see that? Now all our fates are one.

193
00:18:00,790 --> 00:18:03,330
它们是狗 听不懂的
They're dogs! They don't understand.

194
00:18:03,330 --> 00:18:04,900
不 它能的
Oh, yes, he does.

195
00:18:04,900 --> 00:18:05,800
听得懂
Oh, yes.

196
00:18:05,800 --> 00:18:09,470
巴克 我们现在可是拴在一起了
Buck, we're all tied up together now.

197
00:18:09,470 --> 00:18:11,470
一损俱损
We fall all together,

198
00:18:11,470 --> 00:18:13,670
但一荣俱荣
But so do we get up as one.

199
00:18:15,740 --> 00:18:17,780
来吧 我们再试一次
Come. We try again.

200
00:18:18,880 --> 00:18:19,980
放松
Easy.

201
00:18:21,010 --> 00:18:22,380
就是这样斯皮茨
That's it, Spitz.

202
00:18:29,420 --> 00:18:31,090
我觉得你的狗受伤了
I think your dog is broken.

203
00:18:31,090 --> 00:18:32,320
它才没受伤
He's not broken.

204
00:18:32,320 --> 00:18:33,930
它只是不适应而已
He's just got Californian feet.

205
00:18:53,310 --> 00:18:57,280
在这里 开阔的天空之下
Out here, under an open sky...

206
00:18:58,420 --> 00:19:02,320
巴克感觉到了从未有过的寒冷
Buck felt a cold he'd never known.

207
00:19:19,240 --> 00:19:20,610
出去
Out!

208
00:19:21,840 --> 00:19:24,370
狗在外边睡
Dogs sleep outside!

209
00:19:32,550 --> 00:19:35,520
在人类世界长大
Growing up in the world of man...

210
00:19:35,520 --> 00:19:39,090
巴克学会了听人们讲话
Buck had learned to listen to their voices.

211
00:19:44,360 --> 00:19:45,730
今晚
Tonight,

212
00:19:46,800 --> 00:19:49,770
它将开始倾听自己的声音
He would begin to hear his own.

213
00:20:35,080 --> 00:20:36,050
快来巴克
Come on, Buck!

214
00:20:36,050 --> 00:20:38,080
我们要出发了
We have to get on the day.

215
00:20:38,080 --> 00:20:39,520
前进
Allez!

216
00:20:56,870 --> 00:20:57,870
有人吗
On by!

217
00:20:58,740 --> 00:20:59,740
邮件
Mail!

218
00:21:02,040 --> 00:21:03,110
谢了 佩罗
Thanks, Perrault.

219
00:21:05,810 --> 00:21:08,450
- 邮件 - 谢谢
- Mail! - Thank you!

220
00:21:55,290 --> 00:21:56,630
好多了
That's better!

221
00:21:59,970 --> 00:22:02,070
你真沉啊
You are a heavy one.

222
00:22:37,100 --> 00:22:38,870
斯皮茨 转弯
Spitz! Gee!

223
00:22:39,600 --> 00:22:42,170
耶 转的漂亮
Yeah! That's a turn!

224
00:22:42,880 --> 00:22:44,840
你看到了吗 他学的真快
You see? He learns quick.

225
00:22:52,990 --> 00:22:55,590
做雪橇犬的工作
Doing the work of a sled dog

226
00:22:55,590 --> 00:22:59,660
让巴克感到自信并且快乐
Brought Buck confidence and joy.

227
00:22:59,660 --> 00:23:03,830
现在 它属于这个团队
Now, he belonged to a pack.

228
00:23:05,660 --> 00:23:06,870
转弯
Gee!

229
00:23:07,970 --> 00:23:09,600
漂亮 就是这样
Yeah, that's it!

230
00:23:09,600 --> 00:23:11,100
棒极了
Fantastique!

231
00:23:11,900 --> 00:23:14,770
你是只真正的雪橇犬 Buck
You're a real sled dog now, Buck!

232
00:23:36,960 --> 00:23:37,960
等下
Hold up.

233
00:23:39,030 --> 00:23:40,630
巴克别动
Buck, stay.

234
00:23:49,710 --> 00:23:51,640
不不不 弗朗索瓦丝
No, no, no! Francoise!

235
00:23:55,650 --> 00:23:56,880
弗朗索瓦丝
Francoise!

236
00:24:11,430 --> 00:24:12,770
弗朗索瓦丝
Francoise!

237
00:24:41,990 --> 00:24:43,490
弗朗索瓦丝
Francoise!

238
00:24:49,570 --> 00:24:50,770
你还好吗
You okay?

239
00:24:51,440 --> 00:24:52,840
巴克
Buck!

240
00:24:55,510 --> 00:24:56,570
巴克
Buck!

241
00:24:56,580 --> 00:24:58,480
救它
Save him!

242
00:24:58,480 --> 00:24:59,680
巴克
Buck!

243
00:25:06,320 --> 00:25:07,850
巴克
Buck!

244
00:25:08,790 --> 00:25:10,220
巴克
Buck!

245
00:25:11,020 --> 00:25:12,020
巴克
Buck!

246
00:25:17,230 --> 00:25:19,100
巴克
Buck!

247
00:25:22,370 --> 00:25:24,100
巴克
Buck!

248
00:25:24,440 --> 00:25:25,500
巴克
Buck!

249
00:25:27,470 --> 00:25:28,870
巴克
Buck.

250
00:25:33,710 --> 00:25:35,780
巴克
Buck.

251
00:25:48,930 --> 00:25:49,930
巴克
Buck.

252
00:25:58,770 --> 00:25:59,970
噢巴克
Oh, Buck.

253
00:26:01,370 --> 00:26:02,840
巴克
Oh, Buck.

254
00:26:06,910 --> 00:26:09,320
为一只狗流泪
Crying for a dog.

255
00:26:10,920 --> 00:26:12,750
没有
No.

256
00:26:12,750 --> 00:26:15,850
不不 我没哭
No, no. I wasn't crying.

257
00:26:18,290 --> 00:26:19,290
你哭了
You were crying.

258
00:26:22,360 --> 00:26:23,360
没有
No.

259
00:26:24,630 --> 00:26:26,360
我没有
I wasn't.

260
00:26:31,170 --> 00:26:34,170
佩罗送邮件这么多年
In all his years hauling the mail...

261
00:26:34,170 --> 00:26:37,110
他从来没有准时过
Perrault has never been on time.

262
00:26:37,110 --> 00:26:38,740
一次都没有
Not once.

263
00:26:40,010 --> 00:26:43,450
但他每天仍旧相信自己可以按时送到
But he drives every day like it might happen.

264
00:26:44,350 --> 00:26:46,750
他相信自己可以
He believes.

265
00:26:46,750 --> 00:26:49,220
但我从未见过他像相信你一样
But I never saw him believe in anything

266
00:26:49,220 --> 00:26:51,990
相信别的东西
As much as he believes in you.

267
00:27:04,200 --> 00:27:06,110
现在我也相信你了
Now I do, too.

268
00:28:26,920 --> 00:28:31,890
一个团队只能有一个首领
A pack can have only one leader.

269
00:28:32,890 --> 00:28:36,400
斯皮茨已经忍够了
Spitz had had enough.

270
00:32:20,220 --> 00:32:22,090
斯皮茨
Spitz!

271
00:32:24,260 --> 00:32:26,760
斯皮茨
Spitz!

272
00:32:29,060 --> 00:32:31,530
斯皮茨 斯皮茨
Spitz! Spitz!

273
00:32:33,030 --> 00:32:35,230
这不像它啊
It's not like him.

274
00:32:35,230 --> 00:32:36,970
我找了一个早上了
I looked all morning.

275
00:32:36,970 --> 00:32:38,500
哪儿都找不到它
I can't find him anywhere.

276
00:32:39,500 --> 00:32:41,570
就像消失了一样
It's like he's vanished.

277
00:32:44,340 --> 00:32:45,380
斯皮茨
Spitz!

278
00:32:46,450 --> 00:32:49,180
我们得走了 不能等它了
We have to go. Without him.

279
00:32:49,180 --> 00:32:50,680
不能为它浪费一整天
Can't lose the day.

280
00:32:51,620 --> 00:32:53,550
索莱尔
Sol-leks! oh.

281
00:32:54,120 --> 00:32:56,790
巴克 归位
Buck? Back in place.

282
00:32:57,690 --> 00:32:58,620
去啊
Allez!

283
00:32:58,620 --> 00:33:01,630
索莱尔比你多干五年都不止
Sol-leks has got more than five years on you.

284
00:33:01,630 --> 00:33:02,830
回队里去
Get in line.

285
00:33:07,100 --> 00:33:09,230
巴克
Buck.

286
00:33:09,230 --> 00:33:11,900
你拉的好不代表你能领的好
Just because you pull good don't make you ready to lead.

287
00:33:11,900 --> 00:33:13,570
好吗 回去吧
Okay? Allez.

288
00:33:18,780 --> 00:33:20,980
我觉得它不会动的
I don't think he's gonna move.

289
00:33:20,980 --> 00:33:22,550
它会的
Oh, he'll move.

290
00:33:23,120 --> 00:33:24,420
巴克
Buck...

291
00:33:25,580 --> 00:33:26,690
走开
Move.

292
00:33:34,830 --> 00:33:35,930
索莱尔过来
Sol-leks, come.

293
00:33:35,930 --> 00:33:36,930
过来
Come.

294
00:33:37,560 --> 00:33:39,930
走
Allez!

295
00:33:40,900 --> 00:33:41,970
到这来
Here.

296
00:33:46,340 --> 00:33:49,040
嘿 过来啊
Hey. Come here.

297
00:33:49,040 --> 00:33:51,610
嘿
Hey.

298
00:33:51,610 --> 00:33:53,180
这狗今天早上怎么了
What got into this dog this morning?

299
00:33:53,180 --> 00:33:54,310
别
No.

300
00:33:54,310 --> 00:33:55,810
我觉得它们有什么事是你不知道的
I think they know something you don't know.

301
00:33:55,820 --> 00:33:57,850
没什么是我不知道的
There's nothing I don't know.

302
00:33:57,850 --> 00:33:59,380
嘿 它哪去了 嘿
Hey. Where did he go? Hey!

303
00:33:59,380 --> 00:34:01,320
我们可没法补上浪费的这么多时间
We can't make up this much time.

304
00:34:01,320 --> 00:34:02,820
邮局要关门了
They'll close the office.

305
00:34:02,820 --> 00:34:03,820
不
No!

306
00:34:04,160 --> 00:34:05,220
不
No!

307
00:34:05,220 --> 00:34:06,560
不不不不 别这样
No, no, no, no, no!

308
00:34:06,560 --> 00:34:08,220
我们要准时到那
We were going to be on time.

309
00:34:08,230 --> 00:34:09,760
就一次
Just once!

310
00:34:23,840 --> 00:34:24,840
好吧
Fine.

311
00:34:30,550 --> 00:34:31,550
套上吧
Take it.

312
00:35:10,620 --> 00:35:13,190
没那么糟糕嘛
It's not that bad.

313
00:35:13,190 --> 00:35:15,660
我的领头犬丢了
I lost my lead dog.

314
00:35:16,600 --> 00:35:19,030
幸运的话我们会比预计的晚两天
We'll be two days behind if we're lucky.

315
00:35:19,030 --> 00:35:20,670
但我们从不走运
And we've never been lucky.

316
00:35:36,120 --> 00:35:37,680
你可能得要
You might wanna...

317
00:35:38,520 --> 00:35:40,750
- 系上点 - 好吧好吧
- ...hang on. - Yeah, yeah.

318
00:35:41,350 --> 00:35:42,690
好了巴克
Okay, Buck.

319
00:35:43,860 --> 00:35:45,360
前进
And, mush!

320
00:35:58,670 --> 00:36:00,040
前进 巴克
Go, Buck!

321
00:36:00,040 --> 00:36:01,040
前进
Go!

322
00:36:18,160 --> 00:36:20,060
就是这样巴克
Yes, Buck!

323
00:36:20,060 --> 00:36:21,190
走着
Go!

324
00:36:30,300 --> 00:36:32,710
巴克左转
Buck, haw!

325
00:36:36,040 --> 00:36:37,080
往左转
Turn left!

326
00:36:37,880 --> 00:36:39,440
左
Left!

327
00:36:39,440 --> 00:36:41,340
左转
Turn left!

328
00:36:41,350 --> 00:36:43,650
走啊 左转
Go! Turn left!

329
00:36:55,390 --> 00:36:57,400
不不
No! No!

330
00:36:58,100 --> 00:36:59,970
不不不
No, no, no!

331
00:37:01,200 --> 00:37:02,670
疯了吗你
Are you crazy?

332
00:37:19,150 --> 00:37:22,120
不不不 不
No, no, no! No!

333
00:37:34,330 --> 00:37:36,670
走走走走
Go, go, go, go!

334
00:37:45,180 --> 00:37:48,180
再快点 巴克 别停
Faster, Buck! Don't stop!

335
00:37:54,650 --> 00:37:56,290
佩罗
Perrault?

336
00:38:00,960 --> 00:38:02,560
就这样 就这样
This is it! This is it!

337
00:38:02,560 --> 00:38:04,460
别放松 巴克
Don't let up now, Buck!

338
00:38:04,460 --> 00:38:08,170
好样的
Yeah, that's it!

339
00:38:12,810 --> 00:38:14,240
别挡路
Clear the way!

340
00:38:14,240 --> 00:38:15,340
走开
Move!

341
00:38:15,340 --> 00:38:16,540
快走
Go!

342
00:38:22,110 --> 00:38:23,410
停
Whoa!

343
00:38:23,420 --> 00:38:24,950
停
Whoa!

344
00:38:30,590 --> 00:38:31,960
你看见了吗
Did you see that?

345
00:38:35,490 --> 00:38:37,030
我们做到了
We made it!

346
00:38:38,800 --> 00:38:39,930
做到了
We did it!

347
00:38:42,800 --> 00:38:44,070
这是凯莉的信
Here's one for Kelly.

348
00:38:44,070 --> 00:38:44,940
对
Yeah.

349
00:38:44,940 --> 00:38:46,000
麦卡锡 给你
Mccarthy, right here.

350
00:38:46,010 --> 00:38:47,300
有伊丽莎白·雪诺的吗
Anything for Elizabeth Snow?

351
00:38:47,310 --> 00:38:48,440
有奥马利的吗
Is there something for O'malley?

352
00:38:48,440 --> 00:38:49,610
- 拉维恩在吗 - 肖
- Laverne? - Shaw.

353
00:38:49,610 --> 00:38:50,940
我有三个邮件
I got three!

354
00:38:51,610 --> 00:38:53,110
拉维恩
Laverne!

355
00:38:53,110 --> 00:38:54,540
道尔 肯尼迪
Doyle? Kennedy?

356
00:38:54,550 --> 00:38:56,120
有史密斯的一封信 这里
I've got one for Smith. Here.

357
00:38:58,420 --> 00:38:59,620
林奇
Lynch.

358
00:39:03,060 --> 00:39:04,160
看到了吗巴克
See, Buck?

359
00:39:04,960 --> 00:39:06,620
我们送的不是信
We don't carry mail.

360
00:39:07,560 --> 00:39:09,100
是生命
We carry lives.

361
00:39:10,060 --> 00:39:11,700
是希望
We carry hope.

362
00:39:12,200 --> 00:39:13,770
是爱
We carry love.

363
00:39:15,100 --> 00:39:18,800
我们早上出发 去歇会吧
We leave in the morning. Let's get some rest.

364
00:39:20,470 --> 00:39:23,140
奥尼尔·沃尔什
O'neil? Walsh?

365
00:39:24,840 --> 00:39:27,110
加拉格尔
Gallagher?

366
00:39:33,220 --> 00:39:34,820
你看
Look.

367
00:39:46,370 --> 00:39:48,560
最亲爱的萨拉
Dearest Sarah.

368
00:39:48,570 --> 00:39:52,570
此刻我仿佛灵魂出窍
The soul seems to have gone out of me now.

369
00:39:53,570 --> 00:39:55,770
每一天
Each day

370
00:39:55,780 --> 00:39:58,680
我都在想念最爱的儿子的梦中醒来
Starts with the memory of our dearest son.

371
00:40:00,850 --> 00:40:02,750
蒂姆的生日快到了
Tim's approaching birthday

372
00:40:02,750 --> 00:40:06,220
这让我记起我们失去的时光
Reminds me of all that's been lost.

373
00:40:08,820 --> 00:40:10,860
家里的温暖
The warmth of our home...

374
00:40:12,890 --> 00:40:15,630
我们儿子梦中的冒险
...the adventures our son dreamed of.

375
00:40:18,230 --> 00:40:22,770
我多希望在安静变得无法忍受之前
I wish I'd found the words to express how I felt

376
00:40:23,840 --> 00:40:26,340
找到合适的词
Before the silence became

377
00:40:27,240 --> 00:40:28,970
来描述我的感觉
Unbearable.

378
00:40:30,610 --> 00:40:32,240
然而我走了
And I left.

379
00:40:39,290 --> 00:40:41,850
去找一个
I search for a place...

380
00:40:43,790 --> 00:40:46,090
让我能够感到
I might feel some

381
00:40:46,590 --> 00:40:47,790
些许平静的地方
Peace.

382
00:40:52,870 --> 00:40:55,870
虽然我觉得我可能永远都找不到
Though I fear I will never find it.

383
00:41:02,840 --> 00:41:06,240
因为我心里其实清楚
Because I know that as I am,

384
00:41:06,250 --> 00:41:12,080
这个世界也许再也没有属于我的家了
There may be no home for me in this world.

385
00:41:48,590 --> 00:41:51,050
- 别走 别走 - 驾
- Don't leave. Don't leave! - Mush!

386
00:42:00,430 --> 00:42:02,030
别 别 别
No, no, no!

387
00:42:05,040 --> 00:42:06,770
巴克 咋回事儿
Buck! What?

388
00:42:08,740 --> 00:42:10,940
你还有时间在离开之前多带一封吗
You got time for one more before you leave?

389
00:42:11,380 --> 00:42:12,780
你迟到了
You're late.

390
00:42:12,780 --> 00:42:15,680
事关我儿子的生日
It's just that it's my son's birthday.

391
00:42:15,680 --> 00:42:17,650
我得把这份思恋送给我的妻子
And I need to send this remembrance to my wife.

392
00:42:17,650 --> 00:42:19,390
我们收信的时候你就该送来
You should have come when we were taking.

393
00:42:20,450 --> 00:42:23,190
斟酌字句花了些时间
Took time to find the words.

394
00:42:33,870 --> 00:42:36,240
你要是识字的话 我们就不需要佩罗了
You learn to read, we won't need perrault anymore.

395
00:42:39,100 --> 00:42:40,640
算你运气好
You are lucky.

396
00:42:40,640 --> 00:42:41,710
巴克说了算
Buck is the boss.

397
00:42:41,710 --> 00:42:44,340
还有谁吗
Anyone else?

398
00:42:45,010 --> 00:42:48,980
巴克 我记得你
Hey, buck. I remember you.

399
00:42:51,050 --> 00:42:52,850
谢谢你
Thank you.

400
00:42:52,850 --> 00:42:54,850
- 谢谢你为我停下 - 现在要走了
- Thank you for stopping. - Now we go!

401
00:42:55,190 --> 00:42:56,490
巴克 准备好了吗
Ready, buck?

402
00:42:56,490 --> 00:42:59,060
好 驾
And, mush!

403
00:43:04,200 --> 00:43:05,300
列队
Line up!

404
00:43:06,330 --> 00:43:07,330
好
Yep!

405
00:43:08,300 --> 00:43:09,770
漂亮 巴克
Nice, buck!

406
00:43:10,800 --> 00:43:12,400
对 就是这样
Yeah, that's it!

407
00:43:17,410 --> 00:43:19,280
直行
Straight ahead!

408
00:43:19,980 --> 00:43:22,250
好
Yep!

409
00:43:35,830 --> 00:43:38,130
80天走了3800公里?
2,400 miles in 80 days?

410
00:43:39,900 --> 00:43:42,130
巴克得睡到秋天
Buck is gonna sleep till fall.

411
00:43:44,140 --> 00:43:46,970
佩罗 有封你的信 像是官方的
Perrault! One for you. Looks official.

412
00:43:52,710 --> 00:43:54,750
南边来了什么消息
What's the news from down south?

413
00:43:54,750 --> 00:43:56,050
做得好
Good work.

414
00:44:01,790 --> 00:44:03,320
佩罗
Perrault?

415
00:44:21,680 --> 00:44:23,510
没事 没事
It's okay. It's okay.

416
00:44:23,510 --> 00:44:25,410
没事的
It's okay.

417
00:44:25,410 --> 00:44:27,910
你们什么都没做错
You did nothing wrong.

418
00:44:27,910 --> 00:44:30,480
你们所有人都很棒
You all done good.

419
00:44:31,520 --> 00:44:32,820
好吗
Okay?

420
00:44:33,450 --> 00:44:35,090
对不起 巴克
I'm sorry, buck.

421
00:44:37,260 --> 00:44:40,060
他们再也不需要我和雪橇了
They don't need me and my sled anymore.

422
00:44:41,090 --> 00:44:43,600
入夏之前 电报会通到这里
By summer, the telegraph will reach here.

423
00:44:44,560 --> 00:44:47,030
送信的新方式
A new way to send the mail.

424
00:44:49,000 --> 00:44:50,970
这是你的团队了
It's your team now.

425
00:44:52,240 --> 00:44:55,510
你还有很长的路要走
You still have a mighty journey ahead.

426
00:45:34,250 --> 00:45:38,050
他脚下的土地又一次变了
The ground had shifted under him again.

427
00:45:38,950 --> 00:45:41,520
巴克失去了另一位主人
Buck had lost another master.

428
00:45:43,320 --> 00:45:47,160
现在他要做自己的主人
Now he would have to be the leader himself.

429
00:45:48,230 --> 00:45:52,100
直到新主人到来
Until a new master came along.

430
00:46:19,220 --> 00:46:22,730
我向你保证过的 对吗 现在我们来了
I promised you, didn't I? And here we are.

431
00:46:22,730 --> 00:46:24,260
你保证的是金子
You promised me gold.

432
00:46:24,260 --> 00:46:27,230
在哪呢 狗身上吗
Where is it? In the dogs?

433
00:46:30,670 --> 00:46:32,670
装好雪橇
Get the sled loaded.

434
00:46:32,670 --> 00:46:35,110
是时候下命令了
It's time to stake our claim.

435
00:46:36,510 --> 00:46:37,510
我们走
Let's go.

436
00:46:38,180 --> 00:46:39,450
接着
And...

437
00:46:40,850 --> 00:46:42,050
驾
Mush!

438
00:46:46,320 --> 00:46:47,350
驾
Mush!

439
00:46:49,990 --> 00:46:51,120
他们受伤了吗
Are they broken?

440
00:46:51,120 --> 00:46:53,560
没有 他们就是懒
No. They're just lazy.

441
00:46:53,560 --> 00:46:54,690
巴克
Buck?

442
00:46:54,690 --> 00:46:56,160
驾
Mush!

443
00:46:57,100 --> 00:46:59,630
查尔斯 搞定牲口
Charles, persuade the beast.

444
00:46:59,630 --> 00:47:01,070
别用棍子
Not the club.

445
00:47:02,500 --> 00:47:03,670
查尔斯
Charles!

446
00:47:03,670 --> 00:47:05,040
放下那东西不然我
Put that down or I'll...

447
00:47:05,040 --> 00:47:06,940
我就不走了
I won't go a step!

448
00:47:06,940 --> 00:47:08,640
查尔斯
Charles!

449
00:47:12,880 --> 00:47:14,980
还记得我吗
Remember me?

450
00:47:18,080 --> 00:47:20,050
是的 我知道
Yeah, I know.

451
00:47:25,730 --> 00:47:27,460
你雪橇的滑板冻住了
Your runners are frozen.

452
00:47:27,460 --> 00:47:29,260
如果你能用舵杆把结的冰弄碎
You'll help your dogs a mighty lot

453
00:47:29,260 --> 00:47:31,960
可以帮你的狗很大的忙
If you take the gee pole and break 'em out.

454
00:47:31,970 --> 00:47:33,570
舵杆
Gee pole?

455
00:47:37,340 --> 00:47:39,000
他在做什么
What is he doing?

456
00:47:42,640 --> 00:47:44,370
先生 当心留声机
Sir! Watch the victrola.

457
00:47:46,110 --> 00:47:48,710
你要去哪儿 先生
Where are you heading, mister?

458
00:47:48,720 --> 00:47:50,450
不关你的事
It's none of your concern.

459
00:47:50,450 --> 00:47:53,080
那张地图该不会是在斯开格威买的吧
You didn't buy that map in skagway, did you?

460
00:47:53,090 --> 00:47:55,050
- 不是 - 那个老童话
- No. - That old fairy tale.

461
00:47:55,590 --> 00:47:56,990
迷失小屋
Lost cabin.

462
00:47:58,390 --> 00:48:00,120
黄金之河
River of gold?

463
00:48:00,130 --> 00:48:02,030
春天还有很久才到
NYou're setting off too far into the spring.

464
00:48:02,030 --> 00:48:03,590
现在一半的路都在河上
Half that trail is on the river.

465
00:48:03,600 --> 00:48:05,800
也就是说另一半路可以走
Well, that leaves half the trail fit for travel.

466
00:48:05,800 --> 00:48:08,000
也就是说你们同伴和狗跑到河上
Oh, it means the ice is gonna break up

467
00:48:08,000 --> 00:48:10,630
冰面会碎
With your companions and the dogs on it.

468
00:48:10,640 --> 00:48:12,970
你为什么不等到春天雪化了再去呢
Why don't you lay over till the spring thaw?

469
00:48:12,970 --> 00:48:15,980
免得你的同伴和狗狗们受罪
Save your dogs and your companions the suffering.

470
00:48:16,020 --> 00:48:19,080
- 好让某个老淘金客抢在我们之前找到黄金吗 - 我不是淘金客
- And let some old prospector beat us to the gold? - I'm not a prospector.

471
00:48:19,080 --> 00:48:20,380
不用了 谢谢你
No, thank you.

472
00:48:20,380 --> 00:48:22,650
我为这支犬队花了一大笔钱
I paid a fortune for this team.

473
00:48:22,650 --> 00:48:24,250
他们会为我拉雪橇
They'll pull my sled.

474
00:48:24,250 --> 00:48:27,550
他们是好雪橇犬 先生 他们会为你拉雪橇
They're good dogs, sir. They'll pull your sled.

475
00:48:28,520 --> 00:48:31,120
他们会为你拉雪橇 直到死去
They'll pull your sled till they die.

476
00:48:36,030 --> 00:48:37,230
谢谢你
Thank you.

477
00:48:38,600 --> 00:48:40,070
我们走
Let's go.

478
00:48:44,200 --> 00:48:46,370
好的 我们走
All right, let's go.

479
00:48:48,310 --> 00:48:49,170
驾
Mush!

480
00:49:07,160 --> 00:49:09,030
你这懒惰的杂种狗
You lazy mutts!

481
00:49:09,030 --> 00:49:11,190
我对这些狗不太有把握
I'm not so sure about those dogs.

482
00:49:11,200 --> 00:49:12,960
也许你应该买另外那一队
Maybe you should've bought a different team.

483
00:49:12,970 --> 00:49:14,260
也许我们应该喂他们点吃的
Maybe we should feed them.

484
00:49:14,270 --> 00:49:16,570
我们应该呆在路上的
We should've stayed on the trail.

485
00:49:16,570 --> 00:49:17,640
驾
Mush!

486
00:49:21,770 --> 00:49:22,670
停下来
Make it stop!

487
00:49:33,720 --> 00:49:36,390
也许他们需要一点鼓励
Maybe they need a little encouragement.

488
00:49:39,520 --> 00:49:41,330
驾
Mush!

489
00:49:42,130 --> 00:49:44,260
驾
Mush!

490
00:49:44,260 --> 00:49:46,000
这是第一次
For the first time,

491
00:49:46,000 --> 00:49:48,570
巴克懂的比主人多
Buck knew more than his masters.

492
00:49:49,430 --> 00:49:51,170
驾
Mush!

493
00:49:51,840 --> 00:49:54,040
但鞭子
But the whip

494
00:49:54,040 --> 00:49:56,310
让他没得选
Offered him no choice.

495
00:50:30,710 --> 00:50:32,240
龟儿子
Son of a...

496
00:50:39,020 --> 00:50:40,220
好吧 这下
Well, now,

497
00:50:40,220 --> 00:50:41,890
我们要跨过去
We're going across.

498
00:50:42,660 --> 00:50:43,990
走
Move!

499
00:50:47,160 --> 00:50:50,290
我让你走
I say you go.

500
00:50:50,300 --> 00:50:51,730
哈尔 他过不去
Hal, he can't.

501
00:50:52,530 --> 00:50:53,530
走啊
Move.

502
00:50:57,700 --> 00:50:58,710
你敢
Don't you dare.

503
00:50:59,810 --> 00:51:00,940
嘿
Hey!

504
00:51:04,210 --> 00:51:07,080
冰面会随时裂开
That river ice is gonna break up any minute!

505
00:51:07,080 --> 00:51:08,410
你个蠢货
You fool!

506
00:51:08,410 --> 00:51:10,650
这只狗想保住你的命
That dog is trying to help you keep your life!

507
00:51:10,650 --> 00:51:11,880
哈尔
Hal!

508
00:51:14,050 --> 00:51:16,450
你为什么这么迫切地想阻止我们
Why are you so keen to stop us?

509
00:51:16,460 --> 00:51:18,860
你知道黄金在哪儿 对吗
You know where the gold is, don't you?

510
00:51:24,300 --> 00:51:27,600
把你的脏手从我的狗身上拿开
You keep your filthy hands off of my dogs.

511
00:51:27,930 --> 00:51:29,270
哈尔
Hal.

512
00:51:34,410 --> 00:51:35,970
哈尔 他说过我们不该过河
Hal, he said we shouldn't cross.

513
00:51:35,980 --> 00:51:38,840
哈尔 你确定吗 我们要不就把狗留下来吧
Hal, are you sure? Maybe we just leave the dogs?

514
00:51:38,850 --> 00:51:40,880
我知道自己在做什么
I know what I'm doing.

515
00:51:40,880 --> 00:51:42,280
驾
Mush!

516
00:51:52,520 --> 00:51:53,760
驾
Mush!

517
00:52:01,300 --> 00:52:03,200
别这样
Don't do this.

518
00:52:03,200 --> 00:52:04,400
别这么对他们
Not to them.

519
00:52:13,280 --> 00:52:14,650
驾
Mush!

520
00:53:08,500 --> 00:53:10,870
我该拿你怎么办
What am I gonna do with you?

521
00:54:10,860 --> 00:54:12,560
他们不在这里
They're not here.

522
00:54:15,270 --> 00:54:17,440
他们走了
They're gone.

523
00:54:20,810 --> 00:54:23,510
你在我床上
You've been sleeping for two days

524
00:54:24,010 --> 00:54:25,540
睡了两天了
In my bed.

525
00:54:36,420 --> 00:54:38,120
我过会儿回来
I'll be back.

526
00:54:49,470 --> 00:54:51,600
走或留
Stay. go.

527
00:54:55,310 --> 00:54:57,080
你自己选
Do what you want.

528
00:55:25,940 --> 00:55:27,240
威士忌
Whiskey.

529
00:55:54,370 --> 00:55:56,000
我要整瓶的
I want the bottle.

530
00:56:02,940 --> 00:56:04,680
他们都走了
They're all gone!

531
00:56:05,610 --> 00:56:07,050
我的狗跑了
My dogs ran off.

532
00:56:07,950 --> 00:56:09,750
我的钱都打了水漂
My fortune lost.

533
00:56:09,750 --> 00:56:11,880
你管这叫一个童话故事
You called it a fairy tale.

534
00:56:13,820 --> 00:56:16,150
你不想让我找到金子
You didn't want me finding the gold.

535
00:56:27,230 --> 00:56:28,270
放松 巴克 放松
Easy, buck, easy.

536
00:56:29,870 --> 00:56:31,270
巴克
Buck.

537
00:56:31,270 --> 00:56:33,240
- 放松 - 你们都看到了
- Easy. - Well, you all saw.

538
00:56:33,240 --> 00:56:35,170
我和这个男人有矛盾
This man and I had business

539
00:56:35,170 --> 00:56:36,870
这狗朝着我的喉咙咬
And the dog went for my throat.

540
00:56:36,880 --> 00:56:38,140
可能还有狂犬病
Probably rabid.

541
00:56:40,880 --> 00:56:42,550
别碰那条狗
You leave that dog alone!

542
00:56:42,550 --> 00:56:44,110
巴克 坐下
Buck, settle!

543
00:56:44,120 --> 00:56:46,350
看到没
You see?

544
00:56:46,350 --> 00:56:48,250
要我说现在就该在这杀了它
I say it gets put down here and now.

545
00:56:48,250 --> 00:56:50,390
- 不要 拜托了 先生 - 你别碰它
- No. Come on, mister. - You don't touch him!

546
00:56:50,390 --> 00:56:52,730
弄清真相之前
No one puts any creature down.

547
00:56:54,560 --> 00:56:56,630
谁也不准杀狗
Until we hear all the facts.

548
00:56:56,630 --> 00:56:58,060
这混蛋打了我
The man sucker punched me.

549
00:57:01,530 --> 00:57:03,070
巴克 放松
Buck, easy.

550
00:57:04,840 --> 00:57:07,210
朋友 你腰带里别着东西吧
What might you have on that belt, friend?

551
00:57:20,890 --> 00:57:24,150
本店不许带枪
No guns on the premises!

552
00:57:32,830 --> 00:57:35,170
没事吧 John Thornton
You okay, John Thornton?

553
00:57:36,170 --> 00:57:37,670
还行
Yeah.

554
00:57:38,400 --> 00:57:40,070
没什么事
I'm fine.

555
00:57:58,660 --> 00:57:59,860
怎么了
What?

556
00:58:00,830 --> 00:58:03,060
你在看什么呢
What are you looking at, huh?

557
00:58:17,980 --> 00:58:19,640
你有什么要说的吗
You got something to say?

558
00:58:31,320 --> 00:58:32,320
巴克
Buck!

559
00:58:34,330 --> 00:58:36,360
你这也太不乖了
That's not very nice.

560
00:58:36,360 --> 00:58:37,700
你为什么要这样
What did you do that for?

561
00:58:38,060 --> 00:58:39,600
嘿巴克
Hey, buck!

562
00:58:39,600 --> 00:58:40,970
巴克 你
Buck, what...?

563
00:58:41,600 --> 00:58:42,730
巴克
Buck?

564
00:58:42,740 --> 00:58:44,270
把它给我
Bring that back.

565
00:58:46,870 --> 00:58:49,310
你现在又想干嘛
Now what are you gonna do, huh?

566
00:58:58,550 --> 00:59:00,650
巴克 你在干嘛
Buck? What are you doing?

567
00:59:00,650 --> 00:59:02,250
还给我
Bring that back.

568
00:59:02,250 --> 00:59:04,090
巴克 别这样
Buck, don't do this.

569
00:59:04,090 --> 00:59:05,390
那是我的
That's mine.

570
00:59:05,790 --> 00:59:07,690
我需要它
I need that.

571
00:59:07,690 --> 00:59:09,360
别这样对我
Don't do this to me.

572
00:59:09,360 --> 00:59:11,130
你做了什么 酒在哪里
What'd you do? Where is it?

573
00:59:11,130 --> 00:59:13,230
你 你能
Just, would you...

574
00:59:13,230 --> 00:59:16,840
走开
Get off.

575
00:59:19,140 --> 00:59:20,240
巴克
Buck.

576
00:59:29,520 --> 00:59:31,080
该死的 你块头真大
Darn, you're big.

577
00:59:39,630 --> 00:59:41,960
今天是他的生日
This was his birthday.

578
00:59:51,240 --> 00:59:52,740
我儿子的
My son.

579
00:59:57,010 --> 00:59:59,850
他死后 我和他的妈妈
After he died, his mom and I...

580
01:00:01,550 --> 01:00:04,010
我们就分开了
...we just grew apart.

581
01:00:04,020 --> 01:00:06,790
她不想在我身边
She didn't wanna be around me...

582
01:00:08,690 --> 01:00:11,420
我不想任何人在我身边
I didn't wanna be around anybody.

583
01:00:16,600 --> 01:00:18,860
所以我来到这里
So, I came up here.

584
01:00:23,600 --> 01:00:25,570
遇到了你
Then I met you.

585
01:00:35,380 --> 01:00:36,650
见鬼了
Hell.

586
01:00:36,650 --> 01:00:38,520
就放在这的
It's around here somewhere.

587
01:00:40,620 --> 01:00:42,490
太好了 你醒了
Good, you're awake.

588
01:00:43,760 --> 01:00:45,090
我把它放在
I put it...

589
01:00:46,890 --> 01:00:48,190
在这里
Here it is.

590
01:00:49,500 --> 01:00:51,260
我有东西要给你看
Something I want to show ya.

591
01:00:53,830 --> 01:00:55,030
过来
Come here.

592
01:00:55,930 --> 01:00:58,200
这是育空地区的地图
This is a map of the Yukon.

593
01:00:58,200 --> 01:01:03,510
我儿子以前老爱看冒险故事
My son was always reading adventure stories,

594
01:01:04,580 --> 01:01:07,720
他对育空地区的消息很痴迷
And he was crazy about the news coming out of the Yukon.

595
01:01:07,810 --> 01:01:09,480
但他关心的不是金子
It wasn't the gold. he didn't care about that.

596
01:01:09,480 --> 01:01:10,950
而是那些山脉
It was the mountains.

597
01:01:10,950 --> 01:01:14,520
他一天到晚盯着山脉的地图和照片
He spent all day looking at maps and at pictures of the mountains.

598
01:01:14,640 --> 01:01:17,850
想象着山的那边有什么
Dreaming about what was on the other side.

599
01:01:17,860 --> 01:01:19,990
无人踏足之地
Places no one had been.

600
01:01:21,330 --> 01:01:22,560
原始之地
Wild places.

601
01:01:24,530 --> 01:01:26,660
我就说 出发吧
"let's go," I said.

602
01:01:26,670 --> 01:01:28,600
他说 好啊老爸
He said, "Yeah, pop."

603
01:01:28,600 --> 01:01:30,070
我们从这开始
We'd start there,

604
01:01:30,070 --> 01:01:33,270
然后他拿起一支铅笔
But then he grabbed a pencil

605
01:01:33,270 --> 01:01:36,910
画了条线 画出了地图
And he drew a line off the map

606
01:01:36,910 --> 01:01:39,780
接着说 不如我们去那里吧
And he said, "but let's go there.

607
01:01:39,780 --> 01:01:43,020
地图上没有的 从来没人去过的地方
"off the map. where no one's been."

608
01:01:45,280 --> 01:01:48,890
这是一趟他会喜欢的旅行
It's... it's a trip he would've loved.

609
01:01:48,890 --> 01:01:50,890
一次真正的冒险
A real adventure.

610
01:01:55,390 --> 01:01:57,200
我们可以试试
We could go.

611
01:01:59,530 --> 01:02:00,900
我们两个人
You and me.

612
01:02:02,840 --> 01:02:04,640
看看那里有什么
See what's out there.

613
01:02:05,570 --> 01:02:07,040
你觉得呢
What do you think?

614
01:02:07,040 --> 01:02:10,510
这是艘独木舟 Buck 我们得坐这个
It's a canoe, Buck. we're gonna ride in it.

615
01:02:15,580 --> 01:02:19,520
乖一点 坐 坐下 Buck
Settle. sit. sit. sit, Buck.

616
01:02:19,520 --> 01:02:21,990
好样的 乖孩子
Good. good boy.

617
01:02:46,080 --> 01:02:49,110
你在干什么
Ha. what are you doing?

618
01:02:50,680 --> 01:02:52,020
求我
Begging?

619
01:02:57,760 --> 01:02:59,390
你可不是我的宠物
You're not my pet.

620
01:03:10,100 --> 01:03:11,600
你要进来吗
Are you comin'?

621
01:03:12,810 --> 01:03:14,440
进来
Get in here.

622
01:03:36,030 --> 01:03:39,430
来吧 巴克 唱首歌
Come on, Buck. give us a song.

623
01:03:42,000 --> 01:03:43,600
还是算了
Maybe not.

624
01:04:31,080 --> 01:04:33,380
你喜欢就好
I'm glad you're enjoying this.

625
01:04:49,030 --> 01:04:50,740
你喜欢这个 对吧
Oh, you like that, huh?

626
01:05:03,680 --> 01:05:05,690
我想我们得开始用走的了
I guess we walk from here.

627
01:06:00,040 --> 01:06:02,570
你的先祖曾在此自在漫游
Your ancestors used to roam here.

628
01:06:03,080 --> 01:06:04,510
我的也是
And mine.

629
01:06:05,210 --> 01:06:07,380
在那个原始的时代
Back when we were wild.

630
01:06:15,390 --> 01:06:17,660
我们来去自由 不是吗
We come and go, don't we?

631
01:06:20,030 --> 01:06:21,860
这里永远都在
This is always here.

632
01:06:34,770 --> 01:06:35,870
怎样
What?

633
01:06:35,880 --> 01:06:37,940
我不知道 走哪边 你说呢
I don't know. Which way? You tell me.

634
01:06:37,940 --> 01:06:39,850
走吧 你带路
Go on. You lead.

635
01:06:51,990 --> 01:06:53,530
巴克
Buck?

636
01:07:06,910 --> 01:07:10,380
看你找到了什么
Ah. Look what you found.

637
01:07:24,160 --> 01:07:25,520
天啊
Boy...

638
01:07:28,260 --> 01:07:30,960
看看这个 Buck
Look at this, Buck.

639
01:07:30,960 --> 01:07:33,970
我们可能还没脱离地图
I don't think we're off all maps.

640
01:07:43,880 --> 01:07:45,910
可能以前住了个淘金客
A prospector, I guess.

641
01:07:46,680 --> 01:07:47,910
垃圾
Trash.

642
01:07:48,450 --> 01:07:50,780
垃圾
Trash.

643
01:07:50,780 --> 01:07:52,220
垃圾
Trash.

644
01:08:00,990 --> 01:08:02,830
好东西
Treasure.

645
01:08:11,000 --> 01:08:14,400
这是我的 好吧
This is mine. all right?

646
01:08:14,410 --> 01:08:16,010
别碰它 这是我的
Just leave it alone. It's mine.

647
01:08:39,260 --> 01:08:40,730
今天运气不错
Good day.

648
01:09:00,820 --> 01:09:02,690
是你的祖先们
It's your ancestors.

649
01:09:04,690 --> 01:09:06,030
狼群
Wolves.

650
01:10:07,650 --> 01:10:10,460
不错啊 Buck
That's good, Buck,

651
01:10:11,190 --> 01:10:13,630
但是多找点这样的 好吗
But more like this, huh?

652
01:10:22,000 --> 01:10:23,970
该死的童话 居然是真的
Damn fairy tale's true.

653
01:10:31,980 --> 01:10:33,880
这才像话 Buck
That's more like it, Buck.

654
01:10:35,280 --> 01:10:36,850
好样的
Attaboy!

655
01:10:48,630 --> 01:10:51,500
怎么了 你在看什么
What? What you looking at?

656
01:10:56,370 --> 01:10:57,740
去看看吧
Go take a look.

657
01:10:58,970 --> 01:11:00,040
去吧
Go on.

658
01:11:00,540 --> 01:11:01,940
去吧
Go on.

659
01:11:03,710 --> 01:11:06,580
天黑前要回来啊
Just be back before dark!

660
01:13:19,910 --> 01:13:20,910
巴克
Buck!

661
01:15:15,900 --> 01:15:18,330
在这里 我们背井离乡
Here, so far from home...

662
01:15:19,700 --> 01:15:22,270
我能看到巴克身上的改变
I can see a change in Buck.

663
01:15:26,310 --> 01:15:29,040
有东西吸引着他回归森林
Something's pulling him into the forest.

664
01:15:31,480 --> 01:15:33,180
回归狩猎
Into the hunt.

665
01:15:44,490 --> 01:15:46,360
这个很漂亮 巴克
That's beautiful, Buck.

666
01:15:47,160 --> 01:15:48,730
很漂亮
Beautiful.

667
01:15:49,600 --> 01:15:53,560
他还是跟着我的那条狗狗
He's still the same dog with me,

668
01:15:53,570 --> 01:15:55,940
但是我很难想象他还能
But I find it hard to imagine him

669
01:15:56,840 --> 01:15:59,440
再回到文明社会
Back in civilization.

670
01:16:01,910 --> 01:16:04,510
有足够大的房子容纳他吗
Is there any house big enough to hold him?

671
01:16:19,990 --> 01:16:24,100
这趟旅途似乎正引领着巴克走向他的命运
This journey seems to be leading Buck to his destiny.

672
01:16:33,610 --> 01:16:35,940
而我的命运又在哪儿呢
Where is it leading me?

673
01:17:39,440 --> 01:17:40,840
这次不行
Not this time.

674
01:17:43,210 --> 01:17:44,980
天黑很久了
Long after dark.

675
01:17:46,850 --> 01:17:51,050
你每天在外面呆得越来越晚
You've been staying out later and later every day.

676
01:17:52,690 --> 01:17:56,090
我知道 有很多东西值得探索
Yeah, I know, there's a lot to explore

677
01:17:56,090 --> 01:17:58,560
但这个世界很危险
But world's a dangerous place.

678
01:17:59,490 --> 01:18:02,090
你永远都不知道有什么在等着你
You never know what's coming.

679
01:18:03,560 --> 01:18:06,300
永远都不知道
You never know.

680
01:18:11,840 --> 01:18:15,940
蒂姆高烧了两天就走了
Fever took Timmy in two days.

681
01:18:25,620 --> 01:18:26,990
该死
Hell.

682
01:18:29,760 --> 01:18:31,620
好了 巴克
Okay, Buck.

683
01:18:48,910 --> 01:18:51,380
这是个美好的夏天
It's been a beautiful summer.

684
01:18:58,980 --> 01:19:00,450
你知道吗 巴克
You know what, Buck?

685
01:19:01,950 --> 01:19:03,560
我一直在想
I've been thinking.

686
01:19:04,990 --> 01:19:07,830
我可能会给自己买一条铁路
I might buy myself a railroad.

687
01:19:07,830 --> 01:19:08,990
那是我的帽子吗
Is that my hat?

688
01:19:08,990 --> 01:19:10,630
那是我的帽子 拿来
That's my hat. come on.

689
01:19:10,630 --> 01:19:12,030
把帽子给我
Give me my hat.

690
01:19:12,030 --> 01:19:13,800
把帽子给我
Give me my hat.

691
01:19:13,800 --> 01:19:16,270
把帽子给我 把帽子给我
Give me my hat. Give me my hat.

692
01:19:17,440 --> 01:19:18,440
巴克
Buck!

693
01:19:18,710 --> 01:19:19,870
巴克
Buck!

694
01:19:20,170 --> 01:19:21,100
过来
Come on.

695
01:19:21,110 --> 01:19:23,540
抓住你了
There you go.

696
01:19:30,950 --> 01:19:32,520
森林狼
Timber wolf.

697
01:19:33,690 --> 01:19:35,250
真漂亮
Beautiful.

698
01:19:36,690 --> 01:19:38,690
这是它们的地盘
This is their domain.

699
01:19:39,430 --> 01:19:41,290
这些山丘是它们的
They own these hills.

700
01:19:48,670 --> 01:19:49,670
你想去吗
You wanna go?

701
01:19:50,700 --> 01:19:51,800
去吧
Go.

702
01:19:51,810 --> 01:19:53,170
就是
Just...

703
01:19:55,440 --> 01:19:57,140
小心点
...be careful.

704
01:20:48,700 --> 01:20:51,160
他在人类的手中
He had been both spoiled

705
01:20:52,230 --> 01:20:54,200
既被宠坏
and he'd suffered

706
01:20:54,200 --> 01:20:56,200
又吃尽了苦头
at the hand of man.

707
01:20:57,870 --> 01:21:03,540
现在 巴克找到了他的同类
Now, Buck found himself with his own kind.

708
01:21:04,980 --> 01:21:09,080
他跋山涉水 在这里找到他的家
How far he has traveled to find his home.

709
01:21:11,550 --> 01:21:15,190
而我却背井离乡
How far I have traveled from mine.

710
01:21:34,710 --> 01:21:36,110
这儿 看看 巴克
Here, look, Buck.

711
01:21:36,480 --> 01:21:41,180
生活用品
Groceries for life.

712
01:21:42,080 --> 01:21:44,350
这些就够了
No man needs more than that.

713
01:21:47,190 --> 01:21:49,490
我该走了 巴克
It's time for me to go, Buck.

714
01:21:50,720 --> 01:21:52,190
该回家了
Go home.

715
01:21:52,730 --> 01:21:55,090
不管剩下的日子怎么样
Whatever's left of it.

716
01:21:55,090 --> 01:21:56,360
跌倒了就得爬起来
Pick up the pieces,

717
01:21:58,060 --> 01:21:59,360
至少也得试试
or at least try.

718
01:22:05,810 --> 01:22:11,280
不 我不是要你跟我走 巴克
No. I'm not asking you to come with me, Buck.

719
01:22:15,010 --> 01:22:17,350
你在这还有事
You got something here.

720
01:22:18,180 --> 01:22:20,290
很重要的事
Something important.

721
01:22:21,090 --> 01:22:23,420
抓住它 别放手
Hang onto it.

722
01:22:26,990 --> 01:22:28,660
我明天早上就走
I'm leaving in the morning.

723
01:22:29,860 --> 01:22:31,800
来说再见吧
Come say bye.

724
01:22:38,240 --> 01:22:40,670
你是条乖狗狗 巴克
You're a good dog, Buck.

725
01:22:52,050 --> 01:22:54,520
你是条乖狗狗
You're a good dog.

726
01:24:53,670 --> 01:24:55,540
你大老远来到这里
You came all the way out here.

727
01:24:55,540 --> 01:24:57,570
你一定知道些什么 对吧
You knew something, didn't you?

728
01:24:57,580 --> 01:24:58,440
放松点
Easy.

729
01:24:58,440 --> 01:25:00,450
这都是你自找的
You wanted it all for yourself.

730
01:25:01,250 --> 01:25:03,250
在哪
Where is it?

731
01:25:03,250 --> 01:25:04,980
金子在哪
Where's the gold?

732
01:25:14,890 --> 01:25:16,330
到处都是
It's everywhere.

733
01:25:20,530 --> 01:25:22,230
拿走吧
Take it.

734
01:25:22,240 --> 01:25:24,030
都拿走吧
Take it all.

735
01:25:24,040 --> 01:25:25,870
它什么也改变不了
It won't change anything.

736
01:25:27,040 --> 01:25:29,410
它不能让人起死回生
It won't bring back the dead.

737
01:25:50,160 --> 01:25:51,590
你认识这个 对吧
You know this, do you?

738
01:25:51,600 --> 01:25:53,200
很好
Good.

739
01:25:53,200 --> 01:25:54,430
看见了吗 小子
You see it, boy?

740
01:25:55,100 --> 01:25:56,830
你看见了吗
You see it?

741
01:25:56,840 --> 01:25:58,440
很好
Good.

742
01:26:33,870 --> 01:26:34,940
巴克
Buck.

743
01:26:36,180 --> 01:26:37,380
好了
Yeah.

744
01:26:40,050 --> 01:26:41,580
你回来了
You came back.

745
01:28:00,160 --> 01:28:01,730
哇哦 巴克
Wow, Buck.

746
01:28:06,430 --> 01:28:08,730
多有意思的冒险 对吗
What an adventure, huh?

747
01:28:22,480 --> 01:28:24,650
没事的 孩子
It's okay, boy.

748
01:28:43,170 --> 01:28:44,940
你到家了
You're home.

749
01:30:25,770 --> 01:30:29,140
在这些山里有个地方
There is a place in these mountains

750
01:30:31,180 --> 01:30:35,280
一群新的森林狼在那里出没
Where a new breed of timber wolf roams...

751
01:30:36,420 --> 01:30:40,220
它们比人或狼都要聪明
Wiser than man or wolf...

752
01:30:41,690 --> 01:30:46,330
是领头的那只狗的功劳
...because of the dog that runs at the head of the pack.

753
01:30:48,360 --> 01:30:51,960
现在它们无所畏惧地生活
Now they live without fear,

754
01:30:51,960 --> 01:30:55,900
养育后代 生生不息
raise their young, and flourish.

755
01:31:23,130 --> 01:31:27,170
有人说 这只是个传说
Some say it's just a legend.

756
01:31:28,300 --> 01:31:29,900
并非如此
Not so.

757
01:31:29,900 --> 01:31:33,740
我曾经认识他
You see, I knew him once.

758
01:31:34,910 --> 01:31:38,810
那时他还只是一个男人的身边的狗
When he was just a dog at a man's side.

759
01:31:42,780 --> 01:31:45,780
即便这片土地其实属于他
And even though this land is his.

760
01:31:46,320 --> 01:31:48,090
每个夏天
Every summer.

761
01:31:48,090 --> 01:31:51,390
他来到山谷
When he comes down to the valley,

762
01:31:51,390 --> 01:31:54,760
都会想起善良的人
He remembers kind hands

763
01:31:54,760 --> 01:31:56,730
和他的几位老主人
and old masters.

764
01:32:00,600 --> 01:32:03,340
在他自食其力之前
Before he went to his own,

765
01:32:04,570 --> 01:32:07,340
在他成为自己的主人之前
Became his own master.

766
01:32:09,810 --> 01:32:14,310
在他听见野性的呼唤之前
Before he heard the call.

