(HORSE HUFFING)
(HORSES WHINNYING)
(INDISTINCT WHIRRING)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(HELICOPER BLADES WHIRRING)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(HORSES WHINNYING)
(METAL CLANGING)
(METAL THUDDING)
(INDISTINCT CREAKING)
(HORSES WHINNYING)
(MEN YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
(MAN WHISTLES)
PSYCHOLOGIST:
"On your way home from work
"you stop at the shopping mall
"to pick up some dinner.
"As you walk past
a restaurant
"you catch a glimpse
of your partner
"with another man or woman.
"They are kissing publicly
and very passionately.
"Up until this moment
"you believed
your relationship was stable,
"loving and committed.
"A. I don't feel
angry at all.
"B. | feel slightly annoyed.
"C. | feel moderately angry.
"D. | feel very angry.
E. lfeel furious.
"At a karaoke night,
your friends. .
(MAN EXHALES)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Yeah.
I know.
Let's do it differently.
Um...
Let me be more specific.
You've been in isolation
in Ely State Prison
and you've just been
transferred here,
back into isolation again.
What do you think
about that?
As I said, this is your
pre-classification meeting,
so that we can discover
what options
are available to you
as you enter back
into the general population.
Is there a vocation
you're interested in?
Would you like
to resume your education?
It's just... It's real easy
to get lost in the system.
Especially when
you come into a new facility,
and, you know,
you're not from around here.
I'm just trying to find out
what's important to you.
Is your freedom
important to you?
Is that something
you think about?
Are you listening to me
at all, Mr. Coleman?
(CHUCKLES)
Yeah.
"Yeah" what?
Yeah, you're listening?
Or yeah, your freedom's
important to you?
I'm listening.
Okay, thank you.
Just get me back there.
PSYCHOLOGIST:
Hey, hey, hey, hey! What?
(ALARM BLARING)
It's okay, thank you.
Sit down!
Sit down. Sit down!
| get it. You feel like
you have no control in here.
| get it.
I understand that.
lam giving you
some control.
That's what this is.
And like it or not,
you're gonna be reintegrated
into the general population.
Hmm. I'm not good
with people.
All right.
I can get you into the outdoor
maintenance program then.
And while you're there,
you'll have the opportunity
to reflect on
where you wanna be.
(PAPERS RUSTLING)
Can I go now?
Yep.
GUARD: Open D wing!
(DOOR BUZZES)
(INMATES TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
GUARD: Pop three.
(DOOR BUZZES)
(DOOR SHUTS AND BUZZES)
(HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING
OVER EARPHONES)
Want one?
(ALARM BUZZING)
(HORSES HUFFING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER
OVER COMMS)
(HORSE NEIGHS)
Here you go.
Start with this pile
right here.
Are you kidding me?
No, man.
When you get done with it,
put it in that pile
over there.
What, you're in charge here?
Yeah, I'm the chief
of shit-shoveling.
Get for it, get busy.
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(INDISTINCT THUDDING)
(THUDDING CONTINUES)
(THUDDING CONTINUOUSLY)
(HORSE WHINNYING)
Come on, let's go.
GUARD: Pop three.
(DOOR BUZZES)
You smell like shit.
(WATER RUNNING)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(INDISTINCT THUDDING)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(MAN WHlSTLlNG)
(THUDDING CONTINUES)
(THUDDING INTENSIFIES)
(THUDDING STOPS)
(ROARING)
(GRUNTS)
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(HORSE SNORTS)
What the hell are you
doing in there? Get out now!
You never go in there.
That's a dangerous animal.
Don't ever fuck with him.
(HORSE NEIGHING)
You have a name?
What's your name?
Roman.
Well, Roman,
I don't need my yard
and my lawn fertilized.
So why don't you just
take your wheelbarrow
and your pitchfork
and get rid
of all this shit?
(MAN SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY ON PA)
(THUDDING)
GUARD: Coleman! Visitor.
(BABY CRYING)
(PEOPLE TAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
WOMAN: Who the hell are you?
MARTHA: I'm over here.
INMATE: I love it.
(MAN LAUGHING)
PHOTOGRAPHER: All right.
And one of you two.
(BUZZER SOUNDS)
Why are you here?
PHOTOGRAPHER: All right.
Very good.
ljust need you
to sign this.
Don't come back here.
PHOTOGRAPHER: Very good.
Thank you.
INMATE: Thank you.
PHOTOGRAPHER: Good day.
And... All right.
Okay, guys.
Now, is everybody ready?
MAN: Yes, boss.
(THUDDING)
MYLES: 'Cause this one
is particularly crazed.
MAN: All right.
MYLES: So be very careful.
And open the gate on three.
One...
MAN: Whoo!
(HORSE BLOWING)
MYLES: Two...
Three! Let her rip!
(HORSE WHINNYING)
(MEN CHEERING AND EXCLAIMING)
MYLES: Yeah. Son of a bitch.
Look at him go.
Jesus Christ.
(HORSE WHINNYING)
(MEN TALKING
AND YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
How long you been
standing here?
Huh?
I'm talking to you.
Yeah, right.
How long you been here?
You can make a sound, right?
You can speak?
Yeah, I can.
Okay. What's your name?
I told you, sir.
lt's Coleman Roman.
Coleman Roman is your name?
That's a joke, right?
(MAN SNIGGERING)
Shut up, Henry.
It's not funny.
He's got a name.
It's just backwards.
You ever rode a horse?
No, sir.
5:00 am. tomorrow morning.
No, I'm just here
for maintenance.
No, sir. You're not here
You're here to do
what I decide
you're gonna do.
And here's the drill.
lfyou can stay in there
for more than five seconds,
you're in the program.
Get it?
And you're in charge.
Get him fed, get him water
and get him calmed down.
(MAN WHlSTLlNG)
HENRY: Your boots,
Mr. Coleman.
Yeah, they go
on your feet.
(HENRYLAUGHS)
Fellas, fellas, fellas,
good morning, good morning,
good morning.
INMATE 1: Just in time.
What up?
HENRY: What's up? What's up?
Mikey. How you feeling?
All right?
INMATE 2: Oh, good morning.
HENRY: Good morning,
good morning.
INMATE 3: Whoo!
Hey, did you get that...
(MEN LAUGHING)
MAN: What's up? What's up?
HENRY: Hey, man, what's up?
How you been?
Top of the morning.
ROBERTO: Ah, ah, ah,
got the boots on.
HENRY: Oh, yeah, don't worry,
you'll get used to it.
INMATE: Nice boots.
Pop your cherry
today, homeboy.
Walking a little funny.
(LAUGHS) That's definitely
not their first rodeo.
(MAN WOLF WHISTLES)
ROBERTO: Cute in that orange.
HENRY: He's fucking
with you, man.
He's fucking with you.
The whole purpose
of this program is to learn
how to break these wild horses
and turn them
into some horse of value
that can be auctioned off
in the next 12 weeks.
It pays to keep this program
running, and ultimately,
(HORSE WHINNIES)
our rehabilitation.
And ironically enough,
the police buy most of them.
That horse is crazy.
He's really spooking out
right now.
Why's that?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask him?
You ready?
(HORSE WHINNIES)
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa!
Get back.
Hey, listen up.
'Cause I'm the best
trainer in here.
See this?
This is your hand.
You always wanna
control your hand.
What you wanna do
is find an opening, you know?
Get him going.
Hey, hey. You just wanna
get him going.
And make sure
you stay in the center.
All right? Make him
move around you.
Come on.
Now, normally,
when you start
a new horse,
you can keep him
right along the fence
like he is right now.
Because they're trying
to keep as much space
as they can away from you.
All right? Now the first thing
you wanna do
is just establish direction.
Get him going one way
and then send him
the other way.
And after you get that
down pat,
you can start working
on the hook and the draw.
Or as I like to call,
"the touch."
All right?
Like I said,
respect his space, okay?
And he'll respect yours.
Get your ass in here.
Come on, man.
We ain't got
all fucking day.
(EXHALES)
Don't forget the stick.
All right.
(GRUNTS)
Whenever you're ready,
Roman Coleman.
(HORSE SNORTING)
Hips, Roman.
What about them?
Your shit is tight.
You need to loosen it up
a little bit if you wanna
connect with him, all right?
I bet you don't have
one good fucking dance move.
(HENRYLAUGHS)
Oh, this is gonna be
fucking great.
All right, look.
Drop the stick.
Fuck the stick.
(STICK CLATTERS)
Put your hands up, all right?
Establish a boundary.
Now tell your horse
to back off!
Back off.
With your body.
Back the fuck off.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
You're acting like a bitch
right now, Roman.
Tell him to back off.
Back off!
With your body, Roman.
Come on.
Well, back the fuck off!
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(HENRYLAUGHS)
It's good, Roman Coleman,
but ifyou wanna control
your horse, first you gotta
control yourself.
Yeah. You be the boss.
You got it, Roman.
Just keep working
on them dance moves. Hips!
Go over there.
Go over there, man.
Yeah, come on,
move it.
There you go.
Come on.
You're really not that bad
for a first time.
I'm actually
pretty proud of you.
HENRY: I looked up
and that motherfucker
just ran straight over me.
Then I look back up
and I got 15 horse cocks
swinging in my fucking face.
You actually have
to be on the horse, man.
You spend more time
on the ground
than you do on your horse.
(LAUGHS) Fuck you, Tom.
Have you seen T-Bird?
That motherfucker's a maniac.
He's not one of the lazy,
squishy donkey types.
What, man?
ROMAN: I'm just listening.
ELlJAH: Hey,
what's your name again?
Roman.
You got
the new horse, right?
Yeah.
(HENRY LAUGHS)
Ooh! The new horse!
(ALL LAUGHING)
When I first saw T-Bird
lwas like,
"I pity the fool
that gotta ride
that motherfucker!"
Happened to be me.
GUARD: Time's up!
(ALL LAUGH)
Come on, man.
You know we got like
three more minutes in here.
GUARD: You're done.
Time's up!
All right, all right!
What you looking at, man?
All you need to be looking at
is them hips, shoulders,
hips, shoulders,
hips, shoulders.
Work on them dance moves, man.
You'll be all right.
(INMATES TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
INMATE: Hey, man.
What's up?
Hey.
Hey there.
Hey, how you feeling?
Any better?
INMATE 2: What up, dawg?
DAN: What's up?
HENRY: Yo, watch my back.
(HENRY WHISTLING)
INMATE 3:
That's a soldier, too.
He's got the crazy eye.
(MAN YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
I already signed that.
You forgot to initial.
Emancipation?
What the fuck is that?
I found a job,
I have a boyfriend
and I'm ready to leave.
Just sign.
My boyfriend's a mechanic.
He's opening up
a garage in Atlanta
and I'm gonna work there
as a receptionist.
PHOTOGRAPHER:
Hey there. Would you guys
like your photo taken today?
Yeah, sure.
That'd be great.
No, not really, man.
Yeah, it'd be great.
Thank you.
PHOTOGRAPHER:
All right, come with me.
Come with me.
Come on, Dad.
lfyou're all set,
then why do you need this?
I'm selling Grandma's house
in Bakersfield,
but I can't
unless you sign.
All right, now don't look
at the camera.
Just look at my finger
over here.
Okay. You can even smile,
if you like.
Take your picture, man.
You can't sell
the house.
I need to sell
PHOTOGRAPHER: Great.
Just one more. Hold on.
Uh, maybe you turn
and face each other
a little bit.
Great.
Yeah, we're done.
That's a nice one.
I need the money
to raise this baby.
So he got a daddy?
Well, I ain't
the Virgin Mary.
So why doesn't he take care
of the baby then?
What do you know about
taking care of a baby?
taking care of anything?
That house is mine.
Lower your voice.
It belongs to me.
Grandma left it to me.
No, she left it to us.
Really?
Yeah.
And you need it here?
Here, where your clothes
are washed,
your meals are served.
You have a bed.
Shit, you're even tan.
You're a dependent
of the state
and it's like you're on
permanent fucking vacation.
Shut the fuck up!
(ROBERTO LAUGHING)
TOM: I think you'd marry
that horse ifyou could.
Don't worry, homie.
Your secret's safe with me.
You should've seen him
propose earlier, man.
Hey, lthink
you already got engaged,
homie. Straight up!
HENRY: Whoa, man,
I ain't even playing.
Ooh, someone's mad.
Roman!
Hey, Roman!
MYLES: You know,
riding a mustang,
that's the easy part.
The hard part
is getting your hands on him
in the first place.
Isn't that right, Coleman?
Why don't you
come on over here
and get in there
and calm him down?
I'm not getting in there.
Do it.
And not only do it,
get it done. Go.
(HORSE HUFFlNG)
Don't forget your stick.
As soon as he turns around,
you get in there.
Come on. Come on.
Now get his attention.
Behave yourself.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
Push him back.
Hang in there, Roman!
You're doing great.
Come on. Yeah, that's it.
Come on, you stop now.
Come here, come here.
MAN: Come on, Coleman,
block him up!
You stop. You stop. Just stop!
Stop it!
(ALL EXCLAIM)
You got game, son!
Hang in there with him!
INMATE 1:
Get out of there, bro!
INMATE 2: Get out of there!
(HORSE WHINNIES AND SNORTS)
(PANTING)
(ROMAN GRUNTING)
Jesus Christ!
What the hell
are you doing?
Get out of there!
(ROARS)
(ROMANGROANS)
MYLES: Back off! Back off!
Back off!
Thomas! Bring the ketamine
and tranquilize him!
Coleman, can you breathe?
TOM: Easy, easy, easy.
INMATE: Man, come on!
GUARD: Ask me
at the horse program.
I never wanna see
your goddamn face again.
(ROMAN PANTING)
(ROMAN GROANS)
(HORSE GROANING)
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
(BANGING ON DOOR)
Psst. Psst. Psst.
Shit.
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
GUARD: Come on,
Coleman, get up.
I got a cellblock to feed.
(ROMAN GROAN S)
(EXHALES)
(THUDDING)
(MAN YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
(INHALES AND EXHALES DEEPLY)
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
MAN: Psst!
GUARD: What do you want?
A magazine.
lgotyou.
No,no,no,
noterthat
Marquis... Marquis...
(HORSES SNORTING AND NEIGHING)
ROMAN: Come on.
Yeah, good boy. Good boy.
Now come with me.
Come with me. Come on.
That's it. That's it.
That's it.
Now don't come here.
Don't come here.
And stop.
Now get back there.
Get back there. Come on.
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
Coleman, out of bed!
Come on, man. Hurry up!
ROMAN: What's going on?
GUARD: Get dressed.
A nasty thunderstorm
is seven miles out.
Need all the riders
we can get. Let's go!
(ALARM BLARING)
(MEN YELLING INDISTINCTLY)
INMATE: We gotta get control
over this side.
(HORSE WHINNYING)
TOM: Get that horse
out of that pen over there.
It's not the fence,
it's not the fence.
It's the horses.
They're gonna hurt themselves!
(MEN CONTINUE
ARGUING INDISTINCTLY)
ROMAN: Easy.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
Calm down.
Easy.
Come here.
MYLES: Henry!
Easy.
(HORSES WHINNYING)
Come on.
That's it.
Comeon
Easy,easy!
(HORSE SNORTS AND NEIGHS)
MYLES: Come on,
get bridles on them
and get them out!
(METAL CLANGING)
MYLES: Walk them down
to the kitchen.
(WIND WHOOSHING)
MYLES: All right, fellas,
let's make some room in here!
Try to get as many horses
as you can in here.
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(MEN SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
INMATE 1: Can somebody
bring an extra halter?
I'm right here, okay? Easy.
HENRY: Torn,
are you okay?
Mikey, are you okay?
INMATE 2: Stop that.
Stop that. Go on, get away.
Stop that.
INMATE 3: Henry!
(INMATE 3 GROANING)
INMATE 4: Yo, back off!
(HORSES WHINNYING)
(INMATES EXCLAIM HAPPILY)
MYLES: Jesus Christ.
INMATE 4: All right.
He's good, man. He's good.
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(HORSE GROANS)
INMATE:
You're all right. Relax.
Coleman!
You're back.
lfyou ever
hit another horse,
I'm gonna see you do 10 years
in a psychiatric ward.
You got that?
I do, sir. Thank you.
You earned that.
We've got four weeks
before the auction.
Let's see ifyou
and your horse
can catch up.
How's your horse?
Doing all right.
HENRY: There you go.
(WOMAN SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY ON PA)
(MUMBLLING INDISTINCTLY)
(HENRY WHOOPING)
HENRY: Yeah, price is gonna
blow up at the auction, man!
ROBERTO: Come on,
give T-Bird a kiss.
(HENRY GROANS)
ROBERTO: You're gonna be
top seller, huh?
(ALL CHEERING)
And he can still cha-cha!
INMATE: That's what
I'm talking about!
INMATE 2: That's right, homie.
Do the Macarena!
Hey,bud.
(HORSE SNORTS)
It's me.
Come here.
What the fuck?
Look like somebody's
mad at you today, huh?
He won't listen.
He won't let me approach him.
I wouldn't let you
approach me either,
motherfucker.
All right, cowboy, look.
Jump in the middle.
It's real simple.
When both ears
are pointing one way,
to the front,
he's happy.
When they're both
pointing to the back,
he ain't so happy.
You see his ears?
Just tell me what to do,
all right?
You gotta be
patient, man.
You gotta be patient
ifyou wanna
get your hands on him.
(HENRY LAUGHING)
It's a real nice horse
you got here, man.
What'd you name him?
I haven't named him yet.
Everybody need a name, Roman.
It might be the reason
he's not coming
when you call him.
| read something
about a guy
who could gallop
so slow,
it took him an hour
to go 300 yards.
That's the whole story?
That's slower than
that mule over there.
That's very unimpressive.
No,no,no.
It's about
controlling strength.
He was using silk reins.
Silk reins?
Yeah.
Okay.
The guy's name was Marquis.
(HORSE WHINNIES AND SNORTS)
(CHUCKLES) Look alive!
We got happy ears.
Marquis.
Now that you've figured
that part out,
you might as well go ahead
andjump in the middle.
All right?
Be on his time.
And remember what I told you
about your shoulders?
You gotta loosen up.
What's up?
INMATE: What's up, man?
INMATE 2: I think so, boss.
lthink so.
(HORSE SNORTS AND NEIGHS)
You turn
your back on me?
(SNORTS)
(HORSE SNORTS)
All right, come here.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
(METAL CLANGING)
Come on.
Come on!
Stay there.
All right?
Come on.
Come on. Come on!
(PANTING)
AII right.
All right.
Now just stay there.
That's it.
That's it, easy.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
Come on.
I'm tired, man.
And you're tired, too. So...
Now let's do it.
Come on. Please.
Please stay there.
Please, come on.
Come on, please!
Come on, stay there, man!
Just fucking listen to me!
Do you hear me?
I'm not gonna hurt you!
You hear me?
You hear me,
you stupid animal?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Hey,bud.
(SNIFFLES)
(CREAKING)
(MAN COUGHING)
ROMAN:
All right, now...
Where are you going?
Hey, stay here.
(GRUNTS)
(ALL CHEER)
Oh, my God.
What a business.
But to really
get his attention,
you gotta use your hands.
Attaboy, Coleman.
You're getting it.
The horse needs to feel
you and him are in sync.
Whoa! Easy, easy,
easy,easy,easy.
Come on, keep going.
Looks like
he's ready to ride.
Really?
Yeah.
But loosen the rein
on his neck.
That's good.
Right there is perfect.
Keep going. Keep going.
lt's balance.
It's all about balance
and not getting discouraged.
TOM: Good job out there.
Way to stick with it.
Thanks, man.
ELIJAH: Yeah, man.
Great work, man.
Thanks.
He thought
I didn't see that shit.
Hey, man,
what'd | tell you?
Hips, shoulders,
hips, shoulders, baby.
You still can't fucking dance,
but you might be
a cowboy in no time,
let me tell you. (LAUGHS)
You know,
itwon't fucking kill
you to smile, man.
That shit's free.
It don't cost nothing.
(LAUGHS)
GUARD: Pop three!
(DOOR BUZZES)
Hey,bud.
How's the farm?
How are you?
I heard somebody's
smuggling the ketamine.
None of my business.
Now it is.
Your daughter's real pretty.
We wanna taste that dope
on Monday morning.
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
What's your problem, man?
MAN: Huh?
INMATE 1: Trying to get
a fight for that?
INMATE 2: What the fuck
you doing that for?
You better
stay there, boy.
(GUARD BLOWS WHISTLES)
Stay away
from my game.
GUARD: Back to the game!
INMATE 3: That's right,
motherfucker.
Lift some weights.
INMATE 4: Get outta here.
INMATE 5: Come on, man.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
(GLASS CLAN KING)
(MAN SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY ON PA)
(LIQUID POURING)
(SNIFFS)
That was good.
All right, that's it.
Why's that?
Hmm?
Did you know that
at six months,
a fetus can suck
its own thumb?
Pretty crazy, ain't it?
There are guys out there
who know where
your daughter lives.
She wasn't hard to find.
Sleep tight, John Wayne.
MYLES: The auction's
in two weeks!
You gotta be ready.
(HORSE NEIGHS)
Stay in sync with him!
What?
MYLES: Stay in sync with him!
lfyou pull back,
he's gonna stop.
If you spur him,
he's gonna go.
Make up your fucking mind.
That's it.
Now you got it, God damn it.
There you go.
There you...
Why do you spur him?
God damn it,
don't pull his head back!
(ROMAN GROANS)
That's it.
That's all?
Yeah, I'm not
the only one
doing this.
You're gonna
have to wait
a week or two.
That's not gonna work.
MYLES: Coleman,
stop pulling and pushing.
He doesn't know
what message
you're trying to send him,
to stop or go forward.
That's good. Now, that's it.
Stop. Now go forward.
Move him forward.
Move him forward!
Now you're getting it.
Now you got it.
Straighten up, cowboy.
Now you got it!
God damn it,
who knew? (LAUGHS)
I got the touch!
I got it!
INMATE: That's right, bro.
You got it.
Did you see that?
I got it.
You're following me?
(ROMAN CHUCKLES)
AII right.
Go there.
Come on.
What did I tell you?
Go there.
Huh?
(HORSE NICKERS)
Why are you
not listening to me?
Give me some space.
That's it.
PSYCHOLOGIST:
Welcome to today’s
restorative justice session,
otherwise known
as anger management.
I wanna
commend you all again
for making
the courageous decision
to understand
and address
the harm that you caused
the victims of your crimes.
And welcome
to our new participant,
Roman Coleman.
Roman, thank you
for making the choice to come.
Today,ourgoal
is to experience empathy,
to understand the power
of an apology,
and to be open to our faults.
Who would like to start?
Remember,
this is a safe space.
You guys have already made
a lot of headway here.
I got, uh, 10 years
for manslaughter.
PSYCHOLOGIST: And how long
from the thought of the crime
to the actual crime?
(SIGHS)
About a second.
PSYCHOLOGIST:
About a second?
Seventeen years
for strong-arm robbery.
Eighteen years.
PSYCHOLOGIST: For what?
For first-degree murder.
Since I was 14.
And how long
from the thought of the crime
to the actual crime?
(INHALES AND EXHALES DEEPLY)
Ten seconds.
Five seconds.
Twenty-two seconds.
About three seconds.
PSYCHOLOGIST: How long
have you been in prison?
Twelve years.
And how long
from the thought of the crime
to the actual crime?
A split second.
(HANDCUFFS JANGLING)
Thanks for coming.
It was nice
what you wrote to me.
So what is it
you wanna tell me?
I'm working outdoors
with horses.
Horses?
Yeah.
The ones you see
on your way in here.
l'm riding them.
I'm training them.
We got this auction thing
coming up next week.
I'd like you to come.
Sounds fun.
I think you'd like him.
His name is Marquis.
That's my horse.
You think riding horses
can change anything?
I'm gonna
ask you something.
Something I don't deserve.
I know that.
I want you
to hear me out.
What's that?
There are so many things
I've been wanting to say
for such a long time.
I'm not who I used to be.
Whatever happened
was an accident.
(VOICE BREAKING)
I never meant to hurt her.
(TEARFULLY)
And whatever I've done,
you'll always
be my baby girl.
I'm listening.
Come on,
sit down, sit down.
I don't remember everything.
She flushed
my party stuff
down the drain.
She was looking out for me
and I didn't see it like that.
She started yelling.
I started yelling.
We got into a fight,
and we're running around
the house.
And she hit me.
I hit her back.
l was so angry.
So I hit her head
against the sink,
until her skull cracked.
lwasa kid...
lwasa kid.
You left me alone
to take care of my mom.
To dress her and feed her,
and wipe her ass,
and give her
her medicine every day.
Do you know
what that was like?
I love you.
I love you so much.
(SOBBING)
You'll never know.
One day, someday,
I'll make it up to you.
I promise.
(HOOVES POUNDING)
MYLES: ljust wanna
say to all of you,
we're not training
these horses
for little kids' birthday
parties and pony rides.
Some of these horses
are gonna go
and protect the United States
border down there.
So you gotta get them
used to racing and chasing.
Got it?
INMATES: Yes, boss.
Tell you what, man. You see
my cousin, you run
the other way, all right?
MYLES: Come on,
we're out of here, Thomas.
(HENRY GROANING)
(GUARDS BLOWING WHISTLES)
(ALARMS BLARING)
GUARD: Get down!
Everybody on
the fucking ground! Now!
Now, down, down!
Everybody down, down!
Don't move!
GUARD 2: Face in the dirt!
GUARD: Control, I need backup
on the lower yard.
I got a man down.
I need medical.
I need backup now.
GUARD 2: Don't move!
GUARD 3: Shut up!
Get yourface in the dirt!
GUARD: Tower, anybody move...
(DOOR CLOSES)
(DAN SNIFFING)
(DAN GROANS)
(BOTH GRUNTING AND GROANING)
Fuck you. You fucking
piece of shit!
Guard!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(HORSES NEIGHING)
(FIRE CRACKLING)
TOM: Spirits never break.
I don't know
that my spirit's broken.
But it took
a hell of a beating today,
I'll tell you that.
l'll ride his horse.
MYLES: Okay.
Get it done.
Proud to work with you.
INMATE: Good night.
INMATE 2: Good night, boss.
MYLES: See y'all
tomorrow morning.
We'll ride for Henry.
(LIVELY COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING)
(MEN TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
MAN: Come on, come on.
You ready?
Yeah.
You think
she's gonna come?
Huh?
MYLES: (ON SPEAKER)
Well, folks...
Thank you for showing up
and I wanna welcome you
to the 25th Nevada State
Wild Horse Inmate Auction.
(ALL CHEERING)
TOM: Okay,
everybody get ready.
It's almost showtime.
MYLES: An association
we got to give a shout-out to
the Bureau of Land Management.
And together
we’re all real proud
to present some of the most
beautiful animals
you will ever see.
Thanks to you,
farmers, ranchers,
border patrol police,
they'll find a home today.
So give it up for my men!
(ALL CHEERING AND APPLAUDING)
MAN: Yeah,
give it up for them.
Attaboy, Thomas.
(AUDIENCE APPLAUDING)
(MAN WHISTLES)
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
(U.S. NATIONAL ANTHEM PLAYING)
(ALL CHEERING)
First up,
Thomas Youngblood
on T-Bird,
trained by Henry Cooper.
AUCTIONEER: All right,
Thomas, bring him in.
This is number 1283,
first horse today.
A blaze face,
three white feet.
What do we get for him?
How about $1,500?
Fifteen! Would you give 15,
would you give 15?
Give 500 to start. 500!
Now half. Would you give 500?
Anybody for 550?
NOW $600.
I'm at five-and-a-half.
Would you give 600?
650, now seven.
Six-and-a-half.
Would you give seven?
Seven to buy him new.
Would you give $700,
seven-and-a-half?
800, now half, now 900!
I'm at 900!
Now nine-and-a-half.
Your turn again.
We ’re at nine-and-a-half.
Don't let him
get away for that.
Nine-and-a-half.
$ 1, 000. NOW 1, 050.
I'm at 1,000.
Would you give 1,050?
Would you give 1, 050?
Thank you, sir!
Now 11, now a half, now 12.
12, 12, 12. Anybody here,
would you give 1,200?
Sold! Right here, $1,200!
1,200!
(AUDIENCE APPAUDING
AND CHEERING)
MYLES: Let’s have a big hand
for Tom and T-Bird!
ROBERTO: Hell no, man. 1,200?
I'm telling you,
Henry would've got
three times
more than that.
Straight out, man.
MYLES: Sold to the Las Vegas
Police Department
at $1,200!
Next up, Michael Anderson
on Lollypop!
AUCTIONEER: He's number 1287.
Hey, what are we
gonna get for him?
You tell me. What do you think
about 2, 500 for him?
Here's 25, 25.
Would you give 25?
Would you give $1,000?
(HORSE GRUNTING AND NEIGHING)
You gotta... Look, you gotta
let him think about it.
You're trying
to rush him too much.
OFFICER: All right, go. Go!
No, no, man.
You gotta take it easy.
I'm serious. This is...
He's gonna blow up on you.
It's okay.
That's it. That's it.
(SNIFFLES)
MYLES: Okay.
Just remember,
all the proceeds
from the auction
will go directly
to the Bureau
of Land Management’s
Wild Mustang
Conservation Program.
Remember along with me, folks,
these horses need your help.
And we 've come
to the final horse
and rider of today’s auction.
Hey, hey!
Marquis and Roman Coleman.
Calm down.
(HORSE WHINNIES)
Let's go.
(ALL EXCLAIM)
Damn it!
(AUDIENCE CHEERING)
God damn, Roman!
That's what's up!
Good boy.
AU CTlONEER:
All right, folks.
What are we gonna
get for him?
I wanna get 1,500.
Would you give 15,
would you give 15,
would you give 1,500?
$1,000. 500 here, now 600.
I'm at five.
Would you give 600?
600, sir?
600, now seven.
Would you give 700, ma'am?
Seven, now 800, sir.
Eight, would you give 800?
Eight, now nine. Now nine.
NOW 950. NOW 1, 000.
Now nine.
Would you give $1, 000?
Thank you! Now 1,100?
Eleven to buy him.
Would you give 11 for it?
1 1, 1 1 to buy him.
Maybe you would.
Eleven, 11, 10-and-a-half?
Eleven, now half,
1 1-and-a-half.
Would you give
1 1-and-a-half?
Now 12.
Now half.
Would you give
12-and-a-half?
12-and-a-half
to buy him?
1 1 to buy him.
You wanna give 11 for it?
11, 11 to buy him?
Maybe you would.
11, 11, 10-and-a-half?
(VOICE FADES)
Eleven, now half.
11-and-a-half. Now 12.
Twelve? Now half.
Would you give 12-and-a-half?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(HELICOPTER BLADES WHIRRING)
Marquis! Marquis!
(ROMAN YELLS)
(AUDIENCE EXCLAIMING)
(ROMAN GROANING)
Thomas! Thomas, get in there!
Get the ketamine
and control him!
Help me! Help me!
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
Yeah.
(DOOR OPENS)
GUARD:
l have Coleman here, sir.
Bring him in.
Come on in, Coleman.
Well, get that shit
off his wrists.
GUARD: Yes, sir.
Thank you, bud.
lfyou can wait outside,
that'd be cool.
Yes, sir.
Thank you.
Have a seat.
See there?
Forty-two years ago,
me in the saddle.
(LAUGHS)
You wanted to see me, sir?
'Cause they're shutting
the program down.
I'm really sorry, sir.
You're sorry?
Jesus Christ,
don't tell me you're sorry.
Go out there
and tell your horse
you're sorry!
'Cause when the vet gets here,
(SIGHS) he's gonna
put him down!
What are you talking about?
That surprises you?
You have
to remember something.
I've worked with horses
a long goddamn time.
And some you can break,
and some you can't.
And you know
what else is a real shame?
The humpty dumpty way
they put that goddamn fence
back together again.
With adhesive tape!
Just like on your head.
Adhesive tape!
To mend a fucking fence?
Jesus Christ!
(MYLES TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
(THUDDING)
(THUDDING INTENSIFIES)
Marquis.
(SOFTY) Hey.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Come on. Come on.
(GRUNTING)
Come here, come here.
Fuck.
(GUARD SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY ON PA)
(GRUNTING)
Come here. Come here.
Get in there.
Wait a minute.
Go. Come on.
(ALARM BLARING)
No!
Come on. Go there.
Go there. Marquis.
Marquis. Marquis.
You gotta go.
When I say go, you go. Okay?
Come on.
Come on, Marquis.
Get out of here.
Get out there!
(ALARM CONTINUES)
GUARD: Down, down!
Don't move!
ROMAN: I'm not going anywhere!
I'm not going anywhere.
I promise,
I'm not going anywhere!
GUARD: On your knees.
Putyourhands
onyourhead!
Onto the ground!
MARTHA: When I was siX,
l, uh started to write
letters of support
to your parole board.
But your parole
was always denied, so...
I thought it was my fault
that you were still in prison.
Because I wasn’t
a good enough writer.
Then when I got older,
I understood.
You didn't wanna get out.
So I stopped writing.
I kept one of those letters.
"My dad is fun.
”Send him back home. "
(CRYING SOFTLY)
Next time I'll bring Martin.
He '3 your grandson.
(HORSE SNORTS)
(ROMAN CHUCKLES)