1
00:00:47,250 --> 00:00:50,000
{\an8}（五年前）

2
00:00:56,578 --> 00:00:59,512
这里是特雷弗上尉 坐标509。
This is Captain Trevor at coordinate 509.

3
00:00:59,514 --> 00:01:02,515
我们正在追踪数个不明飞行物，它们在高速飞行。
We're tracking several UFOs and they're moving fast.

4
00:01:02,517 --> 00:01:04,417
我勒个去？
What the hell?

5
00:01:04,419 --> 00:01:06,553
中尉，你也和我一样看到那些东西了吗？
Lieutenant, are you seeing what I'm seeing?

6
00:01:06,555 --> 00:01:09,190
<i>是的。长官，它们要过来了。</ i>
<i>Copy that. Sir, we've got incoming.</i>

7
00:01:09,192 --> 00:01:11,160
<i>它们就在上方……</ i>
<i>They're right on top of...</i>

8
00:02:33,910 --> 00:02:36,208
我...我这是死了吗？
Am I... Am I dead?

9
00:02:36,210 --> 00:02:37,713
当然不是。
Of course not.

10
00:02:39,347 --> 00:02:41,949
这看起来像天堂。
This looks like heaven.

11
00:02:41,951 --> 00:02:45,321
而你是一位天使。
And you're an angel.

12
00:02:46,488 --> 00:02:48,955
你还处在因受伤带来的眩晕之中。
You're still light-headed from your injuries.

13
00:02:48,957 --> 00:02:50,326
我叫戴安娜
I'm Diana.

14
00:02:51,160 --> 00:02:52,927
戴安娜...
Diana...

15
00:02:52,929 --> 00:02:54,127
见鬼。
Shit.

16
00:02:54,129 --> 00:02:57,100
冷静点。你会没事的。
Calm down. You're going to be fine.

17
00:03:00,469 --> 00:03:03,003
在天堂岛上你是安全的。
You're safe here on Themyscira.

18
00:03:03,005 --> 00:03:04,070
什么岛？
Thema-what?

19
00:03:04,072 --> 00:03:05,038
天堂岛。
Themyscira.

20
00:03:05,040 --> 00:03:06,939
亚马逊人的家园。
Home to the Amazons.

21
00:03:06,941 --> 00:03:08,909
众神所钟爱的天堂
A paradise favored by the gods,

22
00:03:08,911 --> 00:03:11,778
隐藏在凡人世界目光下数百年之久。
hidden for centuries from the gaze of man's world.

23
00:03:11,780 --> 00:03:14,748
由我的母亲，希波吕忒女王所统治的国度。
Ruled by my mother, Queen Hippolyta.

24
00:03:14,750 --> 00:03:18,587
所以这就是说你是公主，对吗？
So that means you're a princess, right?

25
00:03:19,287 --> 00:03:20,689
差不多吧。
Something like that.

26
00:03:21,656 --> 00:03:23,425
我被一位公主救了吗？
Saved by a princess?

27
00:03:24,093 --> 00:03:25,825
有问题吗？
Is there a problem?

28
00:03:25,827 --> 00:03:28,094
不。我喜欢生活中来点刺激。
Nope. I like a little drama.

29
00:03:28,096 --> 00:03:30,198
这点我也是如此。
Then that makes two of us.

30
00:03:33,369 --> 00:03:36,236
看吧，全都治好了。
There, it's all healed.

31
00:03:36,238 --> 00:03:38,004
哇。这是什么？
Wow. What is this thing?

32
00:03:38,006 --> 00:03:39,839
是紫色治愈射线。
The purple healing ray.

33
00:03:39,841 --> 00:03:41,643
是啊，那名字叫什么呢？
Yeah, but what is it called?

34
00:03:42,477 --> 00:03:44,778
就叫紫色治愈射线。
The purple healing ray.

35
00:03:44,780 --> 00:03:46,349
真的吗？好吧。
Really? Okay.

36
00:03:47,482 --> 00:03:49,516
听我说，谢谢你的营救，公主，
Look, thanks for the save, Princess,

37
00:03:49,518 --> 00:03:51,083
但是我必须离开这里。
but I've got to get out of here.

38
00:03:51,085 --> 00:03:54,621
某种外星人……恶魔入侵了地球。
Some kind of alien... Demons are invading the Earth.

39
00:03:54,623 --> 00:03:56,389
我看到你们的战斗了。
I saw the battle.

40
00:03:56,391 --> 00:03:59,426
你在毫无胜算的情况下还在不停攻击。
You continued to attack against hopeless odds.

41
00:03:59,428 --> 00:04:01,361
是的，那是我的职责。
Yeah, that's the job.

42
00:04:01,363 --> 00:04:04,530
听着，还没有人察觉到这些生物的出现，所以我必须警告他们。
Look, nobody knows about these creatures and I've got to warn them.

43
00:04:04,532 --> 00:04:06,734
你必须明白，特雷弗上尉。
You have to understand, Captain Trevor.

44
00:04:06,736 --> 00:04:09,435
作为一个男人和外乡人，
You are the first man, the first outsider,

45
00:04:09,437 --> 00:04:12,772
你是第一个踏足天堂岛的。
to ever set foot on Themyscira.

46
00:04:12,774 --> 00:04:14,540
你会被关押在正义的牢房中
You will be held in the cells of justice

47
00:04:14,542 --> 00:04:17,577
直到我的母亲和参议院决定好该如何处置你。
until my mother and the senate can decide your fate.

48
00:04:17,579 --> 00:04:19,712
监狱？你要把我关进监狱吗？
Jail? You're going to put me in jail?

49
00:04:19,714 --> 00:04:21,714
我可什么都没做啊
I haven't done anything.

50
00:04:21,716 --> 00:04:23,883
不，不，不，你们不能这样。我得回去
No, no, no, you can't. I need to get back.

51
00:04:23,885 --> 00:04:25,452
我必须警告他们。
I have to warn them.

52
00:04:25,454 --> 00:04:28,156
这些怪物现在可能已经在侵略地球了。
Those monsters could be invading Earth right now.

53
00:04:28,825 --> 00:04:30,257
戴安娜！
Diana!

54
00:04:30,259 --> 00:04:33,096
戴安娜，我们必须得做点什么。
Diana, somebody's got to do something.

55
00:04:44,673 --> 00:04:47,640
你们想没想过做做度假旅游生意？
You ever think about opening a resort business?

56
00:04:47,642 --> 00:04:49,943
因为我有一个叫埃塔的朋友
'Cause I've got a friend named Etta

57
00:04:49,945 --> 00:04:54,315
她愿意花上大价钱来到这个充满漂亮女性健美者的小岛。
who'd give her right arm for an island full of beautiful female bodybuilders.

58
00:04:54,317 --> 00:04:58,154
我想我母亲已经明确表达了好客不是她的美好品德。
I think my mother has proven hospitality is not her priority.

59
00:05:03,457 --> 00:05:06,058
公主，您怎么来了？
Princess, what brings you here?

60
00:05:06,060 --> 00:05:07,363
很不幸，有事要做。
Unfortunately, this.

61
00:05:11,265 --> 00:05:12,834
原谅我吧，好姐妹
Forgive me, sister.

62
00:05:14,168 --> 00:05:16,469
看来审议已经结束了。
I take it deliberations are over.

63
00:05:16,471 --> 00:05:18,240
它进行的并不顺利。
It did not go well.

64
00:05:23,678 --> 00:05:28,916
凡人世界的史蒂文·特雷弗，我来这是要带你回家的。
Steven Trevor of man's world, I am here to take you home.

65
00:05:28,918 --> 00:05:33,422
嗯，谢谢，天使，但我们不应该走那边吗？
Um, thanks, angel, but shouldn't we be headed that way?

66
00:05:39,827 --> 00:05:41,895
要逃跑的话就不是了。
Not if we're escaping.

67
00:05:41,897 --> 00:05:43,832
好吧，既然你都这样做了...
Well, when you put it like that...

68
00:05:58,413 --> 00:06:00,113
只要我们上了船，
Once we get to the boat,

69
00:06:00,115 --> 00:06:02,752
我就可以带你穿越屏障，回到你的人身边。
I can take you across the barrier and back to your people.

70
00:06:04,086 --> 00:06:06,486
戴安娜
Diana.

71
00:06:06,488 --> 00:06:08,789
这样做你妈妈不会高兴的。
Your mom is not going to be happy about this.

72
00:06:08,791 --> 00:06:12,058
指给我船的位置，我可以自己从这里乘船回去。
Point me toward the boat and I can take it from here.

73
00:06:12,060 --> 00:06:15,964
我看到了那个杀死你朋友并摧毁你飞行器的恶魔。
I saw the demon that killed your friends and destroyed your craft.

74
00:06:17,365 --> 00:06:19,733
你们需要我的帮助。
You need my help.

75
00:06:19,735 --> 00:06:21,633
众神曾经预言过这一天的到来
The gods foretold of this day,

76
00:06:21,635 --> 00:06:24,037
就是当来自天堂岛的斗士被召唤去
when a champion from Themyscira would be called upon

77
00:06:24,039 --> 00:06:27,173
保护凡人世界免受无尽恐惧侵扰的那一天。
to protect man's world from untold horrors.

78
00:06:27,175 --> 00:06:30,544
我母亲告诉过我，亚马逊人只做正确的事情，
My mother taught me that an Amazon does what is right,

79
00:06:30,546 --> 00:06:32,712
无论付出任何代价。
no matter the cost.

80
00:06:32,714 --> 00:06:34,448
这就是我要做的。
So that's what I intend to do.

81
00:06:34,450 --> 00:06:35,784
戴安娜
Diana.

82
00:06:43,192 --> 00:06:45,726
给我一个解释。
Explain yourself.

83
00:06:45,728 --> 00:06:47,960
不要试图阻止我了，母亲。
Do not try to stop me, Mother.

84
00:06:47,962 --> 00:06:49,863
我是你的女王
I am your queen.

85
00:06:49,865 --> 00:06:53,433
所以你得将那个神圣的铠甲放回到它原有的位置。
Which is why you will return that sacred armor to its rightful place.

86
00:06:53,435 --> 00:06:56,101
你得把那个囚犯送回他的牢房。
You will return that prisoner to his cell.

87
00:06:56,103 --> 00:06:58,837
你会感谢我的怜悯。
You will thank me for my mercy.

88
00:06:58,839 --> 00:07:01,344
然后我们就当无事发生过。
And we will never discuss this again.

89
00:07:06,514 --> 00:07:08,347
他叫史蒂文。
His name is Steven.

90
00:07:08,349 --> 00:07:10,217
我发誓要把他送回到他的人民身边
I have sworn to return him to his people

91
00:07:10,219 --> 00:07:12,652
我还打算和他一起走。
and I intend to go with him.

92
00:07:12,654 --> 00:07:14,820
如果你想从亚马逊人手里偷东西，
If you wish to steal from the Amazons,

93
00:07:14,822 --> 00:07:17,623
你就必须问问他们的保护者。
you will have to go through their protector.

94
00:07:17,625 --> 00:07:19,825
这就是你要的吗？
Is that what you want?

95
00:07:19,827 --> 00:07:21,361
不。
No.

96
00:07:21,363 --> 00:07:23,332
这是您教给我的
It's what you taught me.

97
00:07:24,166 --> 00:07:25,635
那就来吧。
So be it.

98
00:07:30,372 --> 00:07:32,337
他的到来是一个信号。
His arrival is a sign.

99
00:07:39,447 --> 00:07:41,681
凡人世界需要我们的帮助。
Man's world needs our help.

100
00:07:41,683 --> 00:07:44,116
凡人世界已经受过帮助了。
Man's world is past help.

101
00:07:47,423 --> 00:07:49,625
这不是您能决定的。
That is not your choice to make.

102
00:08:04,072 --> 00:08:07,640
如果你离开了这里，你将永远无法成为女王。
If you leave, you will never become queen.

103
00:08:07,642 --> 00:08:09,976
你将永远无法再踏上这座岛屿。
You will never set foot on this island again.

104
00:08:09,978 --> 00:08:13,513
你是否真的愿意抛弃一切
Are you truly willing to throw away everything you are

105
00:08:13,515 --> 00:08:16,051
只为了一个偶然的机缘去帮助他们？
for the mere chance of helping them?

106
00:08:28,262 --> 00:08:29,998
再问我一次，母亲
Ask me again, Mother.

107
00:08:35,704 --> 00:08:39,438
真奇怪，你明明是我自己的女儿，
It's strange that you should be my own daughter,

108
00:08:39,440 --> 00:08:42,844
可是我已经再也认不出你了
and yet someone I do not recognize anymore.

109
00:09:17,878 --> 00:09:19,849
天堂岛的边界。
The edge of Themyscira.

110
00:09:20,983 --> 00:09:22,481
一旦越过那里
Once we cross,

111
00:09:22,483 --> 00:09:24,387
我们将永远无法返回。
we will never be able to return.

112
00:09:26,055 --> 00:09:27,690
我就是孤身一人了。
I will be alone.

113
00:09:28,522 --> 00:09:30,090
不，戴安娜，你不是的。
No, Diana, you won't.

114
00:09:30,092 --> 00:09:31,560
我会和你一起面对。
We're in this together.

115
00:09:32,194 --> 00:09:33,596
好吗？
All right?

116
00:10:18,406 --> 00:10:20,073
埃塔 坎蒂。
Etta Candy.

117
00:10:20,075 --> 00:10:23,108
你确定卡帕特里斯博士会喜欢这样吗？
Are you sure Dr. Kapatelis is okay with this?

118
00:10:23,110 --> 00:10:27,213
戴安娜，朱莉亚 卡帕特里斯是古代文化方面的专家，
Diana, Julia Kapatelis is an expert on ancient cultures,

119
00:10:27,215 --> 00:10:28,881
而你本身就是一种古代文化。
and you're an ancient culture.

120
00:10:28,883 --> 00:10:30,850
穿着精美的鞋子走来走去。
Walking around in great shoes.

121
00:10:30,852 --> 00:10:32,452
还让你在她家住下？
Having you stay at her place?

122
00:10:32,454 --> 00:10:35,190
我想我得花好大力气才能把她从地板上扶起来。
I thought I was gonna have to scrape her off the floor.

123
00:10:36,557 --> 00:10:38,625
这是件好事。
That's a good thing.

124
00:10:38,627 --> 00:10:40,860
也正是我们这样做的原因。
Which is exactly why we're doing this.

125
00:10:40,862 --> 00:10:42,462
他们会喜欢你的，戴。
They'll love you, Di.

126
00:10:42,464 --> 00:10:43,898
你只要放松就好。
You just gotta relax.

127
00:10:54,575 --> 00:10:57,110
好吧，地毯吸过尘了，厨房也收拾干净了，
Okay, vacuumed the rug, kitchen's clean,

128
00:10:57,112 --> 00:10:58,711
厕所也洗了 两次。
toilet's scrubbed, twice.

129
00:10:58,713 --> 00:11:01,548
我怎么听不到你在扫地了？
Why don't I hear sweeping?

130
00:11:01,550 --> 00:11:05,151
因为如果再扫的话，我的手臂就会脱臼了。
Because if I sweep any more, my arms are gonna fall off.

131
00:11:05,153 --> 00:11:07,722
她又不是来舔地板的。
It's not like she's gonna lick the floor.

132
00:11:08,724 --> 00:11:10,758
凡妮莎 卡帕特利斯，一位真正的
Vanessa Kapatelis, an actual,

133
00:11:11,824 --> 00:11:12,759
字面意义上的公主要来了。
literal princess is coming here.

134
00:11:12,761 --> 00:11:15,294
这意味着你不能垂头丧气的，不能砸吧嘴，
That means no slouching, no open-mouth chewing,

135
00:11:15,296 --> 00:11:19,031
如果你的手臂脱臼了，那也只是小意思而已。
and if your arms fall off, it is a small price to pay.

136
00:11:19,033 --> 00:11:21,836
天哪，我检查过花香的有效期了吗？
My God, did I check the expiration date on the potpourri?

137
00:11:35,150 --> 00:11:36,252
公主。
A princess.

138
00:11:38,118 --> 00:11:39,852
哇。
Wow.

139
00:11:39,854 --> 00:11:42,356
是的，但是你应该叫我凡妮莎。
Yes, but you should call me Vanessa.

140
00:11:42,358 --> 00:11:43,823
我的意思是“戴安娜”。
I mean, "Diana."

141
00:11:43,825 --> 00:11:45,261
很显然，你是凡妮莎。
You're Vanessa, obviously.

142
00:11:45,994 --> 00:11:46,995
对吗？
Right?

143
00:11:51,432 --> 00:11:53,500
你在打扫房子吗
Are you cleansing your house?

144
00:11:53,502 --> 00:11:54,568
来吧，我来帮忙。
Here, let me help.

145
00:11:54,570 --> 00:11:55,668
你真的不必...
You really don't have to...

146
00:11:55,670 --> 00:11:57,205
凡妮莎，有人按门铃吗？
Vanessa, was that the doorbell?

147
00:12:00,307 --> 00:12:02,140
不许垂肩。
No slouching.

148
00:12:02,142 --> 00:12:03,576
戴安娜公主
Princess Diana,

149
00:12:03,578 --> 00:12:05,180
欢迎来到我们的家。
welcome to our home.

150
00:12:07,849 --> 00:12:10,286
我也很高兴认识您，卡帕特里斯博士。
It is an honor to meet you as well, Dr. Kapatelis.

151
00:12:11,085 --> 00:12:12,919
你们俩位。
Both of you.

152
00:12:12,921 --> 00:12:17,490
嗯，干嘛不跟我去房子的其他地方看看呢？
Um, why don't I show you the rest of the house?

153
00:12:17,492 --> 00:12:18,891
我已经重新布置了房间。
I've rearranged the rooms.

154
00:12:18,893 --> 00:12:21,327
在早晨你会感受到明媚的阳光。
Yours gets lovely sunlight in the morning.

155
00:12:21,329 --> 00:12:22,830
这真令人兴奋。
This is so exciting.

156
00:12:23,864 --> 00:12:25,731
我理解你的感受。
I know how you feel.

157
00:12:25,733 --> 00:12:27,268
我也有一个强势的母亲。
I have a strong mother, too.

158
00:12:32,840 --> 00:12:34,973
我有很多东西要教给你
I have so much to teach you,

159
00:12:34,975 --> 00:12:37,745
当然，还有很多东西可以向你学习。
and so much to learn from you, of course.

160
00:12:38,613 --> 00:12:40,214
你喜欢花香吗？
Do you like potpourri?

161
00:12:55,430 --> 00:12:57,563
你介意我也进来坐坐吗？
Do you mind if I am also here?

162
00:12:57,565 --> 00:12:59,133
好啊。为什么不呢？
Sure. Why not?

163
00:13:00,801 --> 00:13:02,302
你的寝室很像我在天堂岛
Your sleeping chamber is like my room

164
00:13:02,304 --> 00:13:04,571
皇宫里的房间
in the royal palace on Themyscira,

165
00:13:04,573 --> 00:13:05,770
尽管小了一点
albeit a bit smaller

166
00:13:05,772 --> 00:13:08,076
当然了，也没有侍女服侍
and without handmaidens, of course.

167
00:13:15,349 --> 00:13:18,086
对不起，昨天让你遇到麻烦了。
I'm sorry I put you in trouble yesterday.

168
00:13:19,219 --> 00:13:20,252
没关系。
It's okay.

169
00:13:20,254 --> 00:13:22,688
对妈妈来说，你就是头等大事。
You're like a big, huge deal to Mom.

170
00:13:22,690 --> 00:13:25,060
“行走的历史”之类的。
"Living history" and all that.

171
00:13:25,693 --> 00:13:27,760
你想它了吗？
Do you miss it?

172
00:13:27,762 --> 00:13:29,131
你的家？
Your home?

173
00:13:30,099 --> 00:13:31,496
一点点吧。
A bit.

174
00:13:31,498 --> 00:13:35,000
但是我来这里是为了让你们的世界更美好。
But I came here to make your world a better place.

175
00:13:35,002 --> 00:13:37,672
而且只要你的母亲教给我更多关于你们的文化，
And once your mother teaches me more about your culture,

176
00:13:38,373 --> 00:13:39,742
我就会开始实施了。
that's what I'll do.

177
00:13:40,974 --> 00:13:43,244
你能决定得了吗？
Can you just decide that?

178
00:13:44,612 --> 00:13:47,279
使整个世界变得更好？
To make the whole world better?

179
00:13:47,281 --> 00:13:50,917
每个人都可以自己决定如何去生活。
Everyone gets to decide what they want to do with their life.

180
00:13:50,919 --> 00:13:52,717
我可能不会成功，
I might not succeed,

181
00:13:52,719 --> 00:13:54,922
但这就是我选择去尝试的。
but this is what I choose to try.

182
00:13:59,194 --> 00:14:02,895
可是并非每个人都必须选择同一件事。
But not everyone has to choose the same thing.

183
00:14:02,897 --> 00:14:04,264
那你呢，凡妮莎？
What about you, Vanessa?

184
00:14:04,266 --> 00:14:06,334
你会投身于什么事业中呢？
What will you dedicate your life to?

185
00:14:08,237 --> 00:14:11,303
我不知道，杀死了吸血鬼少年？
I don't know, killing teenage vampires?

186
00:14:11,305 --> 00:14:12,938
不用担心
Don't worry.

187
00:14:12,940 --> 00:14:15,174
吸血鬼不是真的。
Vampires aren't real.

188
00:14:15,176 --> 00:14:16,344
我不担心
I wasn't worried.

189
00:14:17,179 --> 00:14:18,347
但他们是真的。
And they are.

190
00:14:23,318 --> 00:14:25,451
但是我想要什么并不重要。
But it doesn't matter what I want.

191
00:14:25,453 --> 00:14:26,986
我妈妈是考古学家。
My mom's an archeologist.

192
00:14:26,988 --> 00:14:28,755
她的父亲是一位考古学家。
Her dad was an archeologist.

193
00:14:28,757 --> 00:14:30,689
等等等等等等。
Blah, blah, blah.

194
00:14:30,691 --> 00:14:32,393
如果你可以选择呢？
What if you could choose?

195
00:14:34,195 --> 00:14:35,861
我不知道。
I don't know.

196
00:14:35,863 --> 00:14:37,731
我喜欢上武术课。
I like my martial arts class.

197
00:14:37,733 --> 00:14:39,365
我喜欢数学。
I like math.

198
00:14:39,367 --> 00:14:42,702
我以前打过鼓，直到邻居们开始抱怨。
I used to play the drums until the neighbors complained.

199
00:14:44,339 --> 00:14:47,776
我猜...我想成为不一样的人。
I guess... I want to be something else.

200
00:14:49,276 --> 00:14:50,478
什么样的都行。
Anything else.

201
00:14:52,546 --> 00:14:53,949
你告诉你妈妈了吗
Have you told your mother?

202
00:14:55,050 --> 00:14:56,881
告诉我什么？
Told me what?

203
00:14:56,883 --> 00:15:00,154
是指我突然允许把鞋子放到床上了吗？
That I've suddenly allowed people to put their shoes on the bed?

204
00:15:03,657 --> 00:15:04,856
没事的，戴安娜。
Don't worry, Diana.

205
00:15:04,858 --> 00:15:07,461
你是我们的客人
You're our guest.

206
00:15:07,463 --> 00:15:10,065
来吧，凡妮莎，是时候收拾桌子了。
Come on, Vanessa, time to set the table.

207
00:16:17,000 --> 00:16:19,500
{\an8}（会好起来的 戴安娜）

208
00:16:32,914 --> 00:16:34,780
你们坐好了吗
Are you sitting down?

209
00:16:34,782 --> 00:16:35,983
是的
Yeah.

210
00:16:37,752 --> 00:16:40,321
我的意思是我们坐着呢。
I mean, yes. We're sitting.

211
00:16:41,055 --> 00:16:43,021
给他们看看，戴。
Just show them, Di.

212
00:16:43,023 --> 00:16:44,993
她真的很兴奋。
She's really excited.

213
00:16:54,169 --> 00:16:56,004
觉得怎么样？
What do you think?

214
00:16:57,039 --> 00:16:58,837
有点...
It's...

215
00:16:58,839 --> 00:17:00,640
完全蠢爆了？
Totally embarrassing?

216
00:17:00,642 --> 00:17:01,640
凡妮莎。
Vanessa.

217
00:17:01,642 --> 00:17:03,208
得了吧 老妈
Come on, Mom.

218
00:17:03,210 --> 00:17:05,510
她想要干什么，当一个超级英雄？
What's she gonna be, a superhero?

219
00:17:05,512 --> 00:17:07,415
你甚至还不会开车呢。
You can't even drive yet.

220
00:17:10,584 --> 00:17:12,284
戴安娜，这是怎么回事？
Diana, what's going on?

221
00:17:12,286 --> 00:17:15,257
你是想成为像哥谭市那个疯子一样的人吗？
Are you trying to be like that nut in Gotham?

222
00:17:15,856 --> 00:17:17,791
这就是我这来的目的。
It is why I came.

223
00:17:17,793 --> 00:17:20,459
为了保护凡人世界。
To help protect man's world.

224
00:17:20,461 --> 00:17:23,129
成为英雄的方法不只一种。
There's more than one way to be a hero.

225
00:17:23,131 --> 00:17:25,198
我的雇主凯尔博士建立了一个了不起的...
My employer, Dr. Cale, has set up an amazing...

226
00:17:25,200 --> 00:17:27,800
我们不是来请求你许可的，朱莉娅。
We're not asking for your permission, Julia.

227
00:17:27,802 --> 00:17:29,636
戴安娜已经在接受任务了。
Diana's already taking missions.

228
00:17:29,638 --> 00:17:31,637
现在有一个关于她和总统会面的讨论。
There's talk of her meeting the president.

229
00:17:31,639 --> 00:17:34,273
媒体已经给她起了个代号。
The press has already given her a code name.

230
00:17:34,275 --> 00:17:37,610
朱莉娅，我相信加入你的公司能帮助很多人。
Julia, I'm sure I could help many by joining you.

231
00:17:37,612 --> 00:17:40,248
但对来说这才是帮助他人的正确方法。
But this is the right way to help for me.

232
00:17:42,283 --> 00:17:44,684
那么你就应该这样做。
Then that's what you should do.

233
00:17:44,686 --> 00:17:46,151
什么？
What?

234
00:17:46,153 --> 00:17:47,820
谢谢 姐妹们
Thank you, sisters.

235
00:17:47,822 --> 00:17:49,658
我会让你们为我骄傲的。
I'll make you proud.

236
00:17:50,325 --> 00:17:51,459
随你吧。
Whatever.

237
00:17:52,626 --> 00:17:55,998
那么，你的代号是什么？
So, what's your code name?

238
00:18:19,086 --> 00:18:21,390
是神奇女侠。轰爆她
It's Wonder Woman. Blast her.

239
00:18:22,891 --> 00:18:24,924
<i>嘿，戴？戴？</ i>
<i>Hey, Di? Di?</i>

240
00:18:24,926 --> 00:18:26,993
<i>无论你现在在痛扁谁</ i>
<i>Whoever you're punching in the face right now,</i>

241
00:18:26,995 --> 00:18:28,226
<i>可以搞快一点吗？</ i>
<i>can you do it a little faster?</i>

242
00:18:28,228 --> 00:18:30,595
<i>我要在正义大厅前和你见见。</ i>
<i>I need you at the Hall.</i>

243
00:18:30,597 --> 00:18:32,698
我总是忘记你有多有趣。
I always forget how funny you are.

244
00:18:32,700 --> 00:18:34,399
<i>我不怪你</ i>
<i>I forgive you.</i>

245
00:18:34,401 --> 00:18:36,101
<i>但只是因为大多数亚马逊人在闻不到气味的时候</ i>
<i>But only because most Amazons wouldn't know a sense of humor</i>

246
00:18:36,103 --> 00:18:37,570
是感受不到幽默的。
if it bit their noses off.

247
00:18:37,572 --> 00:18:38,772
我就是亚马逊人。
I'm an Amazon.

248
00:18:38,774 --> 00:18:40,438
<i>你恰恰证明了我的观点。</ i>
<i>And you just proved my point.</i>

249
00:18:40,440 --> 00:18:42,307
退后，神奇女侠。
Back off, Wonder Woman.

250
00:18:42,309 --> 00:18:43,208
别挂断。
Hang on.

251
00:18:43,210 --> 00:18:44,712
不然我发誓我会把她的头崩掉。
I swear I'll blow her head off.

252
00:18:50,719 --> 00:18:53,386
这可不是仅有的两个选项。
Those are not the only two outcomes.

253
00:18:58,992 --> 00:19:00,528
我想这是你的。
I believe this is yours.

254
00:19:01,162 --> 00:19:03,464
嗯 谢谢
Um, thanks?

255
00:19:05,132 --> 00:19:06,399
不客气。
No problem.

256
00:19:06,401 --> 00:19:08,469
很抱歉，这些人打扰了您的生活。
I'm sorry these men hampered your day.

257
00:19:13,000 --> 00:19:14,750
{\an8}（现在）

258
00:19:12,274 --> 00:19:15,140
“打扰了您的生活？”
"Hampered your day?"

259
00:19:15,142 --> 00:19:19,210
到底还要过多久你才能不像我奶奶那样说话？
Exactly how long is it gonna be before you stop talking like my grandma?

260
00:19:19,212 --> 00:19:20,748
别傻了
Don't be silly.

261
00:19:22,417 --> 00:19:24,553
我比你奶奶岁数大得多。
I'm much older than your grandmother.

262
00:19:25,687 --> 00:19:27,786
你真的很特别
You really are something special,

263
00:19:27,788 --> 00:19:28,990
知道吗？
you know that?

264
00:19:31,058 --> 00:19:32,126
怎么了？
What is it?

265
00:19:33,259 --> 00:19:34,893
没什么...
Nothing, it's just...

266
00:19:34,895 --> 00:19:37,095
我曾经为此感到自豪，
I used to pride myself on that,

267
00:19:37,097 --> 00:19:38,332
作为独一无二的人
being unique.

268
00:19:41,201 --> 00:19:43,471
我以前没有意识到这并不总是一件好事。
I hadn't realized it's not always a good thing.

269
00:19:45,139 --> 00:19:48,507
对合适的人来说这就是一件好事。
It's always a good thing to the right people.

270
00:19:48,509 --> 00:19:50,176
说到合适的人，
Speaking of the right people,

271
00:19:50,178 --> 00:19:52,647
有一位老朋友需要你见一见。
a blast from our past just walked in.

272
00:19:55,750 --> 00:19:56,785
朱莉娅？
Julia?

273
00:19:59,953 --> 00:20:01,789
太久没见到你了。
It's been too long.

274
00:20:09,197 --> 00:20:10,399
怎么了？
What is it?

275
00:20:11,098 --> 00:20:12,532
是凡妮莎。
It's Vanessa.

276
00:20:12,534 --> 00:20:15,303
我觉得她有麻烦了，我们需要你的帮助。
I think she's in trouble, and we need your help.

277
00:20:19,273 --> 00:20:22,006
我在她的办公室里发现了一些可怕的电子邮件。
I found some disturbing e-mails in her office.

278
00:20:22,008 --> 00:20:23,476
如果凯尔博士读了这些...
If Dr. Cale read these...

279
00:20:23,478 --> 00:20:26,144
维罗妮卡·凯尔？那位制药业大亨？
Veronica Cale? The pharmaceutical magnate?

280
00:20:26,146 --> 00:20:28,714
制药公司找考古学家做什么？
What does a drug company want with archeologists?

281
00:20:28,716 --> 00:20:32,751
技术创新并不像许多人想象的那样是一维的，埃塔。
Innovation isn't nearly as linear as many people think, Etta.

282
00:20:32,753 --> 00:20:35,653
我们在凯尔制药的工作很有价值。
Our work at Cale Pharmaceuticals is valuable.

283
00:20:35,655 --> 00:20:40,359
但是恐怕对我女儿来说这样赚的钱还不够多。
But I fear that it hasn't been profitable enough for my daughter.

284
00:20:40,361 --> 00:20:44,596
凡妮莎计划将凯尔的一件文物卖给其他人。
Vanessa's planning to sell one of Cale's artifacts to someone else.

285
00:20:44,598 --> 00:20:47,365
如果有人发现，她会进监狱的。
If anyone finds out, she'll go to prison.

286
00:20:47,367 --> 00:20:49,701
她都不是我认识的她了。
I don't even know her anymore.

287
00:20:49,703 --> 00:20:51,571
帮帮我，戴安娜。
Help me, Diana.

288
00:20:51,573 --> 00:20:53,742
帮我把女儿带回来。
Help me get my daughter back.

289
00:21:00,015 --> 00:21:01,913
你好？
Hello?

290
00:21:01,915 --> 00:21:03,250
有人在吗？
Is anyone here?

291
00:21:04,219 --> 00:21:05,519
你好？
Hello?

292
00:21:09,190 --> 00:21:11,125
回答我，该死！
Answer me, damn it!

293
00:21:12,293 --> 00:21:14,126
如此放肆。
So presumptuous.

294
00:21:14,128 --> 00:21:19,367
已有很长时间没有人敢以这种方式与毒药博士对话了。
It's been a long time since anyone spoke to Dr. Poison that way.

295
00:21:20,767 --> 00:21:21,870
毒药？
Poison?

296
00:21:22,937 --> 00:21:25,371
你们谁是赛博博士？
Which one of you is Dr. Cyber?

297
00:21:25,373 --> 00:21:28,107
她是之前和我谈判的人。
She's the one I negotiated with.

298
00:21:28,109 --> 00:21:30,876
赛博做事情从不露面。
Cyber doesn't do anything face-to-face.

299
00:21:30,878 --> 00:21:33,845
这是她与我合作的原因之一。
It's one of the reasons she teamed up with me.

300
00:21:33,847 --> 00:21:37,248
<i>放心，她一直在盯着我们。</ i>
<i>Rest assured, she's keeping an eye out for us.</i>

301
00:21:37,250 --> 00:21:38,652
<i>你货带来了吗？</ i>
<i>Do you have the item?</i>

302
00:21:39,653 --> 00:21:41,352
我要我的钱。
I want my money.

303
00:21:41,354 --> 00:21:43,791
我需要确保它是能用的才行。
I need to make sure it's viable first.

304
00:21:49,630 --> 00:21:52,698
<i>毒药，你遇到一个超级麻烦了。</ i>
<i>Poison, you've got a super incoming.</i>

305
00:21:52,700 --> 00:21:54,635
<i>他们直接冲着你来了。</ i>
<i>They're headed straight for you.</i>

306
00:21:56,269 --> 00:21:58,970
你出卖了我们。杀了她！
You double-crossed us. Kill her!

307
00:22:07,248 --> 00:22:08,947
凡妮莎。
Vanessa.

308
00:22:08,949 --> 00:22:11,920
<i> 停。</ i>你们会损坏神器的。
<i>Nein.</i> You'll damage the artifact.

309
00:22:13,889 --> 00:22:15,688
戴安娜
Diana?

310
00:22:15,690 --> 00:22:17,724
我不是为你而来的，毒药。
I'm not here for you, Poison.

311
00:22:17,726 --> 00:22:19,492
凡妮莎。
Vanessa.

312
00:22:19,494 --> 00:22:21,659
那个箱子是维罗妮卡 凯尔的。
That case belongs to Veronica Cale.

313
00:22:21,661 --> 00:22:23,729
这与你无关。
This isn't any of your business.

314
00:22:23,731 --> 00:22:25,732
你甚至都不知道发生了什么。
You don't even know what's going on.

315
00:22:25,734 --> 00:22:29,034
<i>毒药，如果我是你，我会离开那里。</ i>
<i>Poison, I'd get out of there if I were you.</i>

316
00:22:29,036 --> 00:22:32,207
杀死那些特工。拿下这个英雄。
Kill the agents. Take the hero.

317
00:22:37,210 --> 00:22:39,278
是时候重赛一场了，神奇贱货。
Time for a rematch, Wonder Wench.

318
00:22:47,787 --> 00:22:49,321
巨化女
Giganta.

319
00:22:49,323 --> 00:22:51,623
更大也更强了，贱人。
Bigger and better, bitch.

320
00:22:51,625 --> 00:22:53,295
快趴下。
Get down.

321
00:23:03,371 --> 00:23:04,805
待在这。
Stay here.

322
00:23:31,431 --> 00:23:33,535
我已经弄到了神器。
I've secured the artifact.

323
00:23:41,742 --> 00:23:44,411
那种事，我不会允许。
Now that, I will not allow.

324
00:24:09,569 --> 00:24:11,871
你那句话怎么说来着？
How does your saying go?

325
00:24:11,873 --> 00:24:15,376
“块头越大，摔的越惨？”
"The bigger they are, the more they fall down?"

326
00:24:17,612 --> 00:24:18,511
对。
Yes.

327
00:24:18,513 --> 00:24:19,981
就是这么说。
That's it exactly.

328
00:24:32,126 --> 00:24:35,396
我想我们都明白你们做出了一些糟糕的人生选择。
I think we can all agree you've made some poor life choices.

329
00:24:37,898 --> 00:24:39,564
也许入狱一段时间...
Perhaps some time in prison will...

330
00:24:39,566 --> 00:24:40,801
不！
No!

331
00:24:43,971 --> 00:24:46,072
妈妈。妈妈。
Mom. Mom.

332
00:24:46,074 --> 00:24:47,406
我在这。
I'm here.

333
00:24:51,546 --> 00:24:54,582
戴，戴安娜
Di, Diana...

334
00:25:09,229 --> 00:25:10,899
她本不应该来这的。
She shouldn't have been here.

335
00:25:11,766 --> 00:25:13,935
你也不应该来这。
You shouldn't have been here.

336
00:25:16,036 --> 00:25:18,203
她死了。
She's dead.

337
00:25:18,205 --> 00:25:20,775
那都是你的错
And it's all your fault.

338
00:25:26,113 --> 00:25:28,048
别碰我
Don't touch me.

339
00:25:30,450 --> 00:25:33,017
凡妮莎。凡妮莎！
Vanessa. Vanessa!

340
00:25:33,019 --> 00:25:34,588
戴？戴。
Di? Di.

341
00:25:35,856 --> 00:25:37,024
不。
No.

342
00:25:59,479 --> 00:26:01,548
我以为凡妮莎会来呢。
I thought Vanessa would be here.

343
00:26:02,917 --> 00:26:04,216
我...
I...

344
00:26:04,218 --> 00:26:06,718
我真希望向她道歉。
I'd hoped to apologize.

345
00:26:06,720 --> 00:26:09,588
你没有什么要道歉的，天使。
You don't have anything to apologize for, angel.

346
00:26:09,590 --> 00:26:11,490
不是你开枪打的朱莉娅。
You didn't shoot Julia.

347
00:26:11,492 --> 00:26:13,492
她也没有被弹跳击中
She didn't get hit by a ricochet either,

348
00:26:13,494 --> 00:26:15,226
射击角度都是不对的。
the angles were all wrong.

349
00:26:15,228 --> 00:26:17,463
我检查了十几遍。
I checked a dozen times.

350
00:26:17,465 --> 00:26:19,534
我本可以救下她的。
I should have been able to save her.

351
00:26:20,667 --> 00:26:22,871
一个真正的亚马逊人会救下她的。
A true Amazon would have.

352
00:26:23,437 --> 00:26:24,738
我...
I...

353
00:26:25,606 --> 00:26:28,041
我现在又让另一个母亲失望了。
I've failed two mothers now.

354
00:26:32,212 --> 00:26:34,548
我让凡妮莎失去了一切。
I've cost Vanessa everything.

355
00:26:35,682 --> 00:26:38,449
那么我们得尽自己所能去弥补。
Then we'll make it right, as much as we can.

356
00:26:38,451 --> 00:26:40,888
我会和你一起面对，还记得吗？
We're in this together, remember?

357
00:26:58,573 --> 00:27:00,305
<i>令人恶心。</ i>
<i>Disgusting.</i>

358
00:27:00,307 --> 00:27:02,142
<i>我讨厌廉价的伤感。</ i>
<i>I detest cheap sentiment.</i>

359
00:27:03,311 --> 00:27:04,779
这不公平。
It's not fair.

360
00:27:05,712 --> 00:27:07,214
对吗，凡妮莎？
Is it, Vanessa?

361
00:27:13,854 --> 00:27:14,889
算上我。
I'm in.

362
00:27:16,391 --> 00:27:18,824
我会全程参与。
All the way.

363
00:28:27,500 --> 00:28:30,250
{\an8}（库拉克）

364
00:28:59,293 --> 00:29:01,726
我们有货要给博士们送过去。
We have a delivery for the doctors.

365
00:29:01,728 --> 00:29:03,195
躲开，小妞。
Step aside, girl.

366
00:29:03,197 --> 00:29:07,299
我还有一大笔酬劳要取呢。
You're standing between me and a lot of money.

367
00:29:07,301 --> 00:29:11,436
毒药博士和赛博博士指派我来收取你的货物。
Dr. Poison and Cyber instructed me to accept your delivery.

368
00:29:11,438 --> 00:29:13,471
至于给你的付款，
As for your payment,

369
00:29:13,473 --> 00:29:15,108
就跟我没关系了。
I wouldn't worry about it.

370
00:29:21,181 --> 00:29:24,382
你是什么人？
What are you?

371
00:29:24,384 --> 00:29:25,684
一个比过去优秀
More than I was,

372
00:29:25,686 --> 00:29:28,120
将来还会更强大的人。
and not as much as I will be.

373
00:29:44,705 --> 00:29:47,772
你要是再打坏更多的机器人，我们就要揭竿而起了。
You wreck any more robots and we're gonna have an uprising.

374
00:29:48,976 --> 00:29:50,876
我正在训练。
I'm trying to train.

375
00:29:50,878 --> 00:29:53,214
我知道你想做什么，戴。
I know what you're trying to do, Di.

376
00:29:54,481 --> 00:29:56,180
我们找到她了。
We found her.

377
00:29:56,182 --> 00:29:59,684
凡妮莎被库拉克边界上的间谍卫星侦测到了。
Vanessa popped up on a spy satellite on the Qurac border.

378
00:29:59,686 --> 00:30:03,021
她正在走私医疗设备，科技和文物。
She's smuggling medical equipment, tech, and artifacts.

379
00:30:03,023 --> 00:30:06,725
所有这些都与赛博博士和毒药博士有关。
All linked to Dr. Cyber and Dr. Poison.

380
00:30:06,727 --> 00:30:09,093
我想她没有吸取教训。
I guess she didn't learn her lesson.

381
00:30:09,095 --> 00:30:11,697
或者，是我们让她别无选择。
Or we didn't leave her any options.

382
00:30:11,699 --> 00:30:14,800
她太年轻，以为自己很孤单。
She's young, thinks she's alone.

383
00:30:14,802 --> 00:30:17,570
我们需要向她证明这不是真的。
We need to show her that's not true.

384
00:30:17,572 --> 00:30:18,969
就知道你会这么说。
Thought you might say that.

385
00:30:18,971 --> 00:30:20,938
埃塔，能给我们找个交通工具吗？
Etta, can you get us transport?

386
00:30:20,940 --> 00:30:23,842
来个不那么显眼的？
Something discreet?

387
00:30:23,844 --> 00:30:25,846
我正好知道有一个。
I know just the thing.

388
00:30:46,933 --> 00:30:52,103
埃塔，你是从军方那里偷来了隐形飞机吗？
Etta, did you steal an invisible jet from the US military?

389
00:30:52,105 --> 00:30:54,206
<i>史蒂文·特雷弗，你的话真让我惊讶。</ i>
<i>Steven Trevor, I'm surprised at you.</i>

390
00:30:54,208 --> 00:30:57,077
<i>哪里有什么隐形飞机。</ i>
<i>There's no such thing as an invisible jet.</i>

391
00:31:03,383 --> 00:31:07,087
我必须承认，不用天天对着办公桌的感觉很好。
I gotta admit, it feels good to get away from the desk for a while.

392
00:31:07,921 --> 00:31:10,091
我喜欢飞行。
I love flying.

393
00:31:11,092 --> 00:31:14,092
你从来没有和我一起飞过。
You never flew with me.

394
00:31:14,094 --> 00:31:17,062
是啊，嗯，你以前是和超人一起飞的。
Yeah, well, you were flying with Superman.

395
00:31:17,064 --> 00:31:18,766
三个人的话就太挤了。
And three's a crowd.

396
00:31:20,801 --> 00:31:22,970
现在我不和超人一起飞了。
I'm not flying with Superman now.

397
00:31:33,180 --> 00:31:35,514
我们有足够的燃料能盘旋约一个小时。
We've got enough fuel to hover for about an hour.

398
00:31:35,516 --> 00:31:36,614
让我们行动起来吧。
Let's rock and roll.

399
00:31:36,616 --> 00:31:37,815
你会担心吗？
Are you worried?

400
00:31:37,817 --> 00:31:39,851
会的，所以我才能活到今天。
Yeah, that's why I'm not dead yet.

401
00:31:44,458 --> 00:31:45,927
女士优先？
Ladies first?

402
00:32:05,345 --> 00:32:07,278
你打不开吗
You can't open it?

403
00:32:07,280 --> 00:32:09,916
我可以，这样他们就会来硬的。
I can, it's just gonna be the hard way.

404
00:32:23,430 --> 00:32:25,296
看到了 来硬的。
Yeah see? Hard way.

405
00:32:25,298 --> 00:32:27,901
<i>你们一无所知。</ i>
<i>You have no idea.</i>

406
00:32:42,616 --> 00:32:45,583
<i>毒药，内墙被突破了。</ i>
<i>Poison, inner walls are breached.</i>

407
00:32:45,585 --> 00:32:47,287
<i>时间紧迫。</ i>
<i>Tick-tock, tick-tock.</i>

408
00:32:49,590 --> 00:32:51,989
你必须给我们一些时间来升空。
You have to give us time to get in the air.

409
00:32:51,991 --> 00:32:55,059
如果我们失败了，我们将永远无法再执行任务。
If we lose it, we'll never be able to execute the mission.

410
00:32:55,061 --> 00:32:57,095
让我来吧。
I'll do it.

411
00:32:57,097 --> 00:32:59,997
无论谁在进攻大门，我都能应付。
I can handle whoever's storming the gates.

412
00:32:59,999 --> 00:33:04,503
在仓库的那天晚上我就知道你是个战士。
I knew you were a fighter that night in the warehouse.

413
00:33:04,505 --> 00:33:08,176
让我看看你比那时提升了多少。
Show me how much more you've become since then.

414
00:33:13,080 --> 00:33:15,016
<i>她还没准备好，毒药。</ i>
<i>She's not ready, Poison.</i>

415
00:33:16,350 --> 00:33:18,219
<i>有的升级还没有完成。</ i>
<i>Not without all the upgrades.</i>

416
00:33:18,986 --> 00:33:21,453
没错，但她是一个牺牲品。
No, but she is expendable.

417
00:33:21,455 --> 00:33:24,525
而原型是我们的使命，绝不能有闪失。
The prototype, our mission, is not.

418
00:33:41,909 --> 00:33:43,374
凡妮莎？
Vanessa?

419
00:33:43,376 --> 00:33:44,845
凡妮莎死了。
Vanessa's dead.

420
00:33:49,082 --> 00:33:50,849
现在我是银天鹅。
It's Silver Swan now.

421
00:33:58,458 --> 00:33:59,557
为什么？
Why?

422
00:33:59,559 --> 00:34:01,627
你为什么让他们这样对你？
Why did you let them do this to you?

423
00:34:01,629 --> 00:34:04,062
你总是那么完美。
You were always so perfect.

424
00:34:04,064 --> 00:34:05,900
好吧，我现在也一样完美了。
Well, I'm perfect now.

425
00:34:16,676 --> 00:34:19,176
赛博和毒药看到了这一点。
Cyber and Poison saw to that.

426
00:34:19,178 --> 00:34:22,848
他们不是你的朋友。
They are not your friends.

427
00:34:22,850 --> 00:34:24,482
他们当然是。
Of course, they are.

428
00:34:24,484 --> 00:34:26,286
他们帮助了我去杀掉你。
They helped me kill you.

429
00:34:44,103 --> 00:34:45,469
她还好吗？
Is she all right?

430
00:34:45,471 --> 00:34:47,940
看起来她只是被打晕了。
Looks like she just got her bell rung a bit.

431
00:34:47,942 --> 00:34:50,842
但是现在呢？我们要呼叫正义联盟吗？
But what now? Do we call the League?

432
00:34:50,844 --> 00:34:53,511
不，凡妮莎现在神智还不清醒。
No. Vanessa's not in her right mind.

433
00:34:53,513 --> 00:34:58,250
她所遭受的残害足以证明这一点。
The mutilation she's endured is proof enough of that.

434
00:34:58,252 --> 00:35:01,389
我们需要一个全心全意帮她的人。
We need someone whose only concern is helping her.

435
00:35:02,823 --> 00:35:04,323
埃塔
Etta.

436
00:35:04,325 --> 00:35:06,792
<i>我们需要一个在生物技术方面有专长的</ i>
<i>We need someone with expertise in bio-tech,</i>

437
00:35:06,794 --> 00:35:08,259
<i>拥有高度安全的设施</ i>
<i>high-security facilities,</i>

438
00:35:08,261 --> 00:35:10,531
<i>还能管住自己嘴的人</i>。
<i>and the ability to keep their mouth shut.</i>

439
00:35:12,431 --> 00:35:15,134
说曹操曹操到。
Speak of the devil.

440
00:35:15,136 --> 00:35:17,271
找一个能满足其中两项呢？
How 'bout two out of three?

441
00:35:19,540 --> 00:35:22,306
神奇女侠本人。
The Wonder Woman herself.

442
00:35:22,308 --> 00:35:24,109
我要说实话。
I'm gonna be real honest.

443
00:35:24,111 --> 00:35:27,179
埃塔给我打电话时，把我逗笑了。
When Etta called me, I laughed.

444
00:35:27,181 --> 00:35:29,915
做梦都没想到像你这样杰出的人
Never dreamed someone as illustrious as yourself

445
00:35:29,917 --> 00:35:32,116
能够光临本公司
would grace my door.

446
00:35:32,118 --> 00:35:35,256
更不用说还把我的前雇员抱在怀里了。
Let alone with my own ex-employee in your arms.

447
00:35:36,489 --> 00:35:37,855
维罗妮卡·凯尔。
Veronica Cale.

448
00:35:37,857 --> 00:35:39,489
名字就写在外面。
The name's out front.

449
00:35:39,491 --> 00:35:42,027
很高兴认识您，凯尔博士。
A pleasure to meet you, Dr. Cale.

450
00:35:42,029 --> 00:35:43,728
你知道凡妮莎的问题出在哪里吗？
Do you know what's wrong with Vanessa?

451
00:35:43,730 --> 00:35:47,833
问题在于这些植入物根本没有真正被植入。
The issue is these implants aren't really implanted at all.

452
00:35:47,835 --> 00:35:50,768
它们是技术有机病毒的外在表达。
They're the expression of a techno-organic virus.

453
00:35:50,770 --> 00:35:55,772
这个叫银天鹅的东西并不是嫁接到凡妮莎身上的。
Vanessa didn't have this Silver Swan-thing grafted onto her.

454
00:35:55,774 --> 00:35:58,576
她正从内而外转变成银天鹅
She's being turned into it from the inside out

455
00:35:58,578 --> 00:36:00,545
而且病变还在继续。
and it's still going on.

456
00:36:00,547 --> 00:36:02,380
最糟糕的是
The worst part is,

457
00:36:02,382 --> 00:36:04,585
我找不到任何关掉它的开关。
I can't find any off switch.

458
00:36:06,585 --> 00:36:08,853
这种病毒将继续侵占她的身体
This virus will keep replacing her

459
00:36:08,855 --> 00:36:10,524
直到原来的她彻底消失。
until there's nothing left.

460
00:36:11,826 --> 00:36:13,694
她会死在病变过程中。
Killing her in the process.

461
00:36:14,828 --> 00:36:16,527
从理论上讲，我可以治愈她，
In theory, I could heal her,

462
00:36:16,529 --> 00:36:20,401
但她剩的时间不够了，我也没有那种科技。
but she doesn't have the time, and I don't have the tech.

463
00:36:21,701 --> 00:36:23,504
天堂岛有。
Themyscira does.

464
00:36:24,337 --> 00:36:26,138
紫色治愈射线。
The purple healing ray.

465
00:36:26,140 --> 00:36:28,873
好吧，如果这么简单，
Well, if it's so easy,

466
00:36:28,875 --> 00:36:30,308
你为什么要来这里？
why'd you need to come here?

467
00:36:30,310 --> 00:36:33,312
你积分卡上的免费飞行英里数用光了吗？
You out of free miles on your rewards card?

468
00:36:33,314 --> 00:36:36,080
我不知道天堂岛在哪里。
I don't know where Themyscira is.

469
00:36:36,082 --> 00:36:37,750
这是一种保护手段。
It's a security measure.

470
00:36:37,752 --> 00:36:40,719
任何人一旦离开该岛，他们就会忘记它的位置。
As soon as anyone leaves the island, they forget its location.

471
00:36:40,721 --> 00:36:42,353
戴安娜也一样。
Even Diana.

472
00:36:42,355 --> 00:36:44,458
但是你会去再次寻找它吗？
But you're going to find it again?

473
00:36:45,826 --> 00:36:47,161
为了凡妮莎，
For Vanessa,

474
00:36:49,696 --> 00:36:51,495
我必须去。
I have to.

475
00:36:51,497 --> 00:36:55,232
好吧，如果你答应给我点好东西作为回报的话，
Well, if you promise to bring me back something nice,

476
00:36:55,234 --> 00:36:57,402
我很清楚你们该从哪里入手。
I know exactly where you can start.

477
00:37:05,879 --> 00:37:08,415
这是茱莉亚的办公室。
This was Julia's office.

478
00:37:09,283 --> 00:37:10,915
就是这样。
Such as it is.

479
00:37:10,917 --> 00:37:13,351
她总是说起天堂岛。
She always talked about Themyscira.

480
00:37:13,353 --> 00:37:16,189
寻找它是她个人的拿手项目。
Finding it was her personal pet project.

481
00:37:16,989 --> 00:37:18,325
祝你们好运。
Good luck.

482
00:37:34,174 --> 00:37:36,241
我从事情报工作近十年了，
I've been in intelligence for nearly a decade,

483
00:37:36,243 --> 00:37:38,509
但即使我也无法理清这团乱麻。
and even I can't navigate this mess.

484
00:37:38,511 --> 00:37:40,243
这里有些很棒的东西。
Some of this stuff is amazing.

485
00:37:40,245 --> 00:37:42,246
波尔修斯之墓？
The tomb of Persises?

486
00:37:42,248 --> 00:37:45,150
珀尔修斯。杀掉美杜莎的那个。
Perseus. He slew Medusa.

487
00:37:45,152 --> 00:37:47,217
这里有关于美杜莎细胞
There are notes in here about Medusa cells

488
00:37:47,219 --> 00:37:48,520
被用于治疗的注释。
being used in treatment.

489
00:37:48,522 --> 00:37:50,922
我甚至不知道她真的存在。
I didn't even know she was real.

490
00:37:50,924 --> 00:37:54,225
我们第一次见面时你也不认为我是真的。
You didn't think I was real the first time we met.

491
00:37:54,227 --> 00:37:56,663
我当时脑震荡了。
I was concussed.

492
00:38:00,267 --> 00:38:02,400
也许我们找错了方向。
Maybe we're looking in the wrong place.

493
00:38:02,402 --> 00:38:05,703
凯尔说寻找天堂岛是茱莉亚的拿手项目，
Cale said finding Themyscira was Julia's pet project,

494
00:38:05,705 --> 00:38:08,406
但是茱莉亚在遇见凯尔之前就已经知道这个岛了。
but Julia knew about the island before she met Cale.

495
00:38:08,408 --> 00:38:11,009
所以她的笔记不会堆在最上面...
So her notes won't be on the top of the piles...

496
00:38:11,011 --> 00:38:12,480
而是在最里面。
They'd be on the bottom.

497
00:38:22,422 --> 00:38:25,790
在这。帕西法厄神庙。
Here. The temple of Pasiphae.

498
00:38:25,792 --> 00:38:27,426
帕西法厄。
Pasiphae.

499
00:38:27,428 --> 00:38:31,596
著名的...怕吸阀女神？
Famed goddess of... Pacifiers?

500
00:38:31,598 --> 00:38:35,165
她是与迷宫有关的掌管神谕的女神。
She's an oracular goddess associated with mazes.

501
00:38:35,167 --> 00:38:37,534
她能帮助人们看到未来。
She helps people see the future.

502
00:38:37,536 --> 00:38:41,138
如果她的圣地仍然完整，它可能会给我们指出天堂岛的方向。
If her shrine is still intact, it could point the way to Themyscira.

503
00:38:41,140 --> 00:38:43,409
那我们还在等什么呢？
Then what the hell are we waiting for?

504
00:38:48,515 --> 00:38:51,116
好吧。这就是个错误。
Okay. This is a mistake.

505
00:38:51,118 --> 00:38:53,652
我有一个非常舒适的办公室，你们知道的。
I have a really nice office, you know.

506
00:38:53,654 --> 00:38:54,853
那有皮椅。
Leather chair.

507
00:38:54,855 --> 00:38:56,687
休息室里还有台漂亮的咖啡机。
That fancy espresso machine in the lounge.

508
00:38:56,689 --> 00:38:57,922
而现在我在哪？
And where am I?

509
00:38:57,924 --> 00:39:00,290
飞往某个被神抛弃寸草不生
Flying to some god-forsaken no-woman's land

510
00:39:00,292 --> 00:39:02,761
还会毁掉我靴子的地方。
to ruin my boots.

511
00:39:02,763 --> 00:39:05,864
埃塔，是你要加入这个任务的。
Etta, you asked to come on this mission.

512
00:39:05,866 --> 00:39:07,766
当然是我。
Of course, I did.

513
00:39:07,768 --> 00:39:10,067
如果你认为我会放弃一个寻找饮用后就能
If you think I'm gonna pass up the chance to find a drinking fountain

514
00:39:10,069 --> 00:39:11,335
预见未来的泉水的机会，
that can tell the future,

515
00:39:11,337 --> 00:39:13,439
你的脑子一定是坏掉了。
your tiara's on too tight.

516
00:39:44,337 --> 00:39:46,203
现在真是令人大开眼界。
Now that is impressive.

517
00:39:46,205 --> 00:39:48,906
光靠步行怎么可能走到这样的地方呢？
How do you even get to a place like this on foot?

518
00:39:48,908 --> 00:39:50,544
慢点走就行了
Not quickly.

519
00:39:52,779 --> 00:39:53,944
豹女。
Cheetah.

520
00:39:53,946 --> 00:39:56,216
以赫拉之名你在这里做什么？
What in the name of Hera are you doing here?

521
00:40:04,623 --> 00:40:06,526
快进神庙。就现在。
Into the temple. Now.

522
00:40:07,794 --> 00:40:10,060
这就是为什么我不喜欢实地作战的原因。
This is why I don't like field work.

523
00:40:10,062 --> 00:40:11,529
实战的第一课。
First lesson in the field.

524
00:40:11,531 --> 00:40:14,232
有时，你只要专心跑步就够了。
Sometimes you've just gotta focus on running.

525
00:40:14,234 --> 00:40:16,301
不要太得意。
Don't get cocky.

526
00:40:16,303 --> 00:40:18,101
你可能救下了你的朋友，
You may have saved your friends,

527
00:40:18,103 --> 00:40:19,937
但是你才是我真正的目标
but you're my real target.

528
00:40:33,486 --> 00:40:37,690
我真希望这整个迷宫的故事只是一个比喻。
I was really hoping the whole maze thing was just a metaphor.

529
00:40:45,966 --> 00:40:47,334
你进步了
You've improved.

530
00:40:48,435 --> 00:40:50,134
但是你还没有打败我呢。
But you haven't beaten me yet.

531
00:40:56,310 --> 00:40:59,444
而现在你也没机会了。
And you won't now.

532
00:40:59,446 --> 00:41:01,712
这点你就错了，公主。
That's where you're wrong, Princess.

533
00:41:01,714 --> 00:41:06,451
为了打倒你 毒药和赛博已组建了一个正规的恶棍股份有限公司。
Poison and Cyber have formed a regular Villains Incorporated to take you down.

534
00:41:06,453 --> 00:41:08,353
而他们所谓的生意。
And they mean business.

535
00:41:08,355 --> 00:41:12,390
是向愿意加入他们小公司的任何人提供股票分利。
Giving stock options to anyone willing to join their little start up.

536
00:41:12,392 --> 00:41:14,658
包括我。
Including me.

537
00:41:46,593 --> 00:41:49,125
史蒂夫，你不感到困扰吗？
Steve, does any of this bother you?

538
00:41:49,127 --> 00:41:50,295
你是说灰尘吗？
You mean the dirt?

539
00:41:50,297 --> 00:41:52,563
不，只有你那样觉得。
No, that's just a you thing.

540
00:41:52,565 --> 00:41:54,732
不，我是说帕西法厄，迷宫。
No. I mean Pasiphae, mazes.

541
00:41:54,734 --> 00:41:56,533
还有一个熟悉的东西。
Something about this is familiar.

542
00:41:56,535 --> 00:41:57,970
回来。
Get back.

543
00:42:01,308 --> 00:42:04,511
必须阻止入侵者。
Must stop intruders.

544
00:42:05,277 --> 00:42:09,350
必须阻止入侵者！
Must stop intruders!

545
00:42:09,882 --> 00:42:10,982
就是它。
That's it.

546
00:42:10,984 --> 00:42:12,984
帕西法厄生出了牛头怪。
Pasiphae gave birth to the Minotaur.

547
00:42:12,986 --> 00:42:14,486
迷宫里的野兽。
The beast of the maze.

548
00:42:16,890 --> 00:42:19,026
你就不能早点想起来吗？
You couldn't remember that sooner?

549
00:42:25,098 --> 00:42:27,699
听着，三岔牛排，我们不想找麻烦。
Listen, tri-tip, we don't want any trouble.

550
00:42:27,701 --> 00:42:31,505
必须阻止入侵者。
Must stop intruders.

551
00:42:42,582 --> 00:42:44,852
不甩掉它我们怎么能到达泉水那呢？
How're we gonna get there before he does?

552
00:42:48,821 --> 00:42:49,856
不用甩掉它。
We're not.

553
00:42:52,993 --> 00:42:54,893
-哟！ -嘿！
- Yoo-hoo! - Hey!

554
00:42:54,895 --> 00:42:57,295
-小牛牛，小牛牛，在这里。 -嘿，在这里。
- Bully, bully, over here. - Hey, over here.

555
00:42:57,297 --> 00:42:58,328
嘿，在这里。
Hey, over here.

556
00:42:58,330 --> 00:42:59,700
不要杀我
Don't kill me.

557
00:43:15,381 --> 00:43:17,480
怎么了，公主
What's the matter, Princess?

558
00:43:17,482 --> 00:43:20,118
反应不过来了？
Feeling a little slow?

559
00:43:20,120 --> 00:43:22,022
是的，实际上。确实有点。
Yes, actually. I am.

560
00:43:32,265 --> 00:43:33,630
你在做什么？
What are you doing?

561
00:43:33,632 --> 00:43:35,636
转换战场。
Changing the battlefield.

562
00:43:50,549 --> 00:43:55,053
必须阻止入侵者。
Must stop intruders.

563
00:43:55,055 --> 00:43:58,725
必须阻止入侵者。
Must stop intruders.

564
00:44:04,864 --> 00:44:05,998
呆着别动。
Stay.

565
00:44:07,100 --> 00:44:08,399
你要去哪里？
Where are you going?

566
00:44:08,401 --> 00:44:10,467
你不能就这样走了
You can't leave me like this.

567
00:44:11,738 --> 00:44:15,205
好吧，显然你可以，但是要绑住我你得...
Well, obviously you can, but I deserve...

568
00:44:16,741 --> 00:44:18,942
用这根绳子正好。
Exactly what I'm getting.

569
00:44:21,281 --> 00:44:25,616
必须阻止入侵者。
Must stop intruders.

570
00:44:25,618 --> 00:44:29,623
-必须阻止入侵者。 -别在靠近了
- Must stop intruders. - Stand down.

571
00:44:33,158 --> 00:44:34,160
看到了？
See?

572
00:44:35,393 --> 00:44:36,726
完全在我掌控之中。
Totally under control.

573
00:44:38,765 --> 00:44:40,297
你们在这。
There you are.

574
00:44:40,299 --> 00:44:42,634
我很高兴你们没事。
I'm so glad you're all right.

575
00:44:42,636 --> 00:44:45,203
如果赫拉克勒斯能击败牛头怪，
If Hercules can beat a Minotaur,

576
00:44:45,205 --> 00:44:46,404
我也可以
so can I.

577
00:44:46,406 --> 00:44:47,908
史蒂夫，别再装了。
Steve, stop trying.

578
00:44:49,209 --> 00:44:52,810
那么，这个圣地里的东西是如何生效的呢？
So, how does this shrine-thing work?

579
00:44:52,812 --> 00:44:55,882
你要给客服打星还是...
Do you hit star for customer service or...

580
00:44:56,482 --> 00:44:58,218
你要恭敬的请求。
You ask politely.

581
00:45:10,663 --> 00:45:14,098
奥林匹斯众神，请听听我的请求。
Gods of Olympus, hear my plea.

582
00:45:14,100 --> 00:45:16,933
告诉我通往天堂岛的道路。
Show me the path to Themyscira.

583
00:45:16,935 --> 00:45:19,906
告诉我回家的路。
Show me the way home.

584
00:45:25,544 --> 00:45:26,979
戴安娜
Diana.

585
00:45:31,285 --> 00:45:32,853
戴安娜！
Diana!

586
00:45:50,036 --> 00:45:51,071
伟大的赫拉。
Great Hera.

587
00:45:52,071 --> 00:45:53,437
你看见什么了？
What did you see?

588
00:45:53,439 --> 00:45:54,739
很多东西。
Much.

589
00:45:54,741 --> 00:45:56,743
但我无法理解。
But I can't make sense of it.

590
00:45:57,944 --> 00:46:00,411
我仍然不知道天堂岛在哪里。
I still don't know where Themyscira is.

591
00:46:00,413 --> 00:46:05,085
必须...停止...入侵者。
Must... Stop... Intruders.

592
00:46:06,319 --> 00:46:09,687
必须阻止入侵者。
Must stop intruders.

593
00:46:09,689 --> 00:46:10,821
史蒂夫，不要。
Steve, don't.

594
00:46:10,823 --> 00:46:13,794
必须阻止入侵者。
Must stop intruders.

595
00:46:14,460 --> 00:46:18,332
必须阻止入侵者。
Must stop intruders.

596
00:46:31,310 --> 00:46:32,710
安静，朋友。
Peace, friend.

597
00:46:32,712 --> 00:46:35,247
没什么需要你保护的了。
There is nothing left for you to protect.

598
00:46:35,681 --> 00:46:36,917
你...
You...

599
00:46:37,584 --> 00:46:39,252
你解放了我
You freed me.

600
00:46:40,654 --> 00:46:42,189
你叫什么名字？
What is your name?

601
00:46:42,888 --> 00:46:45,157
天堂岛的戴安娜。
Diana of Themyscira.

602
00:46:46,225 --> 00:46:48,391
一个亚马逊人。
An Amazon.

603
00:46:48,393 --> 00:46:52,632
我向你承诺奉献我的生命，天堂岛的戴安娜。
I pledge my life to you, Diana of Themyscira.

604
00:46:55,002 --> 00:46:58,770
而我将在余生为你提供庇佑和保护。
And I will shelter and protect you for all of my days.

605
00:46:58,772 --> 00:47:00,404
嗯...
Um...

606
00:47:00,406 --> 00:47:01,908
费迪南德？
Ferdinand?

607
00:47:03,442 --> 00:47:04,645
怎么了？
What?

608
00:47:05,444 --> 00:47:09,480
一个好名字。
An excellent name.

609
00:47:09,482 --> 00:47:11,118
那就起来吧，费迪南德。
Then rise, Ferdinand.

610
00:47:12,886 --> 00:47:15,819
然后了解清楚你今后不需要再战斗了。
And know that you will never need to fight again.

611
00:47:15,821 --> 00:47:17,520
听着，戴
Listen, Di.

612
00:47:17,522 --> 00:47:19,890
我很高兴另一个成员，
I am happy to have another guy,

613
00:47:19,892 --> 00:47:21,359
大概吧 加入团队，
sort of, on the team,

614
00:47:21,361 --> 00:47:23,361
但我们仍然不知道要干什么。
but we still don't know where to go.

615
00:47:23,363 --> 00:47:25,663
说得对。我们应该回到凡妮莎身边。
True. We should return to Vanessa.

616
00:47:25,665 --> 00:47:28,598
一旦我明白了幻象的含义，我们就要迅速采取行动。
Once I figure out the meaning of my vision, we'll need to move quickly.

617
00:47:28,600 --> 00:47:31,636
--我刚从维罗妮卡 凯尔那收到一条短信。
- -I just got a text from Veronica Cale.

618
00:47:31,638 --> 00:47:34,141
哦，她听起来不太开心。
Ooh, she does not sound happy.

619
00:47:39,879 --> 00:47:43,413
我们发现了这个 在毒药的化合物
We found this on some of the molecules

620
00:47:43,415 --> 00:47:45,251
的某些分子上。
from Poison's compounds.

621
00:47:46,352 --> 00:47:48,118
是你的标志。
It's your logo.

622
00:47:48,120 --> 00:47:49,754
还有别的好消息。
There's more good news.

623
00:47:49,756 --> 00:47:52,123
我的技术人员发现了我们的微型印记
My techs found our micro-stamp

624
00:47:52,125 --> 00:47:55,295
就在我们检查了凡妮莎的血液后，
as soon as we examined Vanessa's blood work.

625
00:47:57,631 --> 00:48:00,464
她可能不是你唯一的麻烦。
She may not be your only problem.

626
00:48:00,466 --> 00:48:02,699
我们在圣地遇到了伏击。
We had company when we got to the shrine.

627
00:48:02,701 --> 00:48:06,006
唯一知道我们去向的只有你的人。
Your people were the only ones who knew where we were headed.

628
00:48:06,672 --> 00:48:08,105
真是荒唐。
That's ridiculous.

629
00:48:08,107 --> 00:48:10,373
凡妮莎 卡帕特利斯是唯一曾经泄漏
Vanessa Kapatelis is the only employee

630
00:48:10,375 --> 00:48:13,344
敏感信息的员工。
to ever leak sensitive information.

631
00:48:13,346 --> 00:48:16,047
也许她现在这个样子是她自找的。
Maybe she deserves to stay the way she is.

632
00:48:16,049 --> 00:48:17,315
你不能这么说
You can't mean that.

633
00:48:17,317 --> 00:48:19,917
凡妮莎做这些事的时候，都在忍受着痛苦。
What Vanessa did, she did from pain.

634
00:48:19,919 --> 00:48:21,319
她迷失了自我。
She's lost.

635
00:48:21,321 --> 00:48:23,888
她觉得朱莉娅带着对她的失望死去了。
She thinks Julia died disappointed in her.

636
00:48:23,890 --> 00:48:25,926
你知道这对她的伤害有多大吗？
Do you know how much that can hurt?

637
00:48:27,625 --> 00:48:29,493
你在开玩笑吗？
Are you kidding?

638
00:48:29,495 --> 00:48:32,129
我老妈一瞪眼水都能冻成冰。
My mother could freeze ice with a look.

639
00:48:32,131 --> 00:48:34,200
她就是这样冰镇饮料的。
Chilled her drinks that way.

640
00:48:37,703 --> 00:48:39,404
好吧，公主
Fine, Princess.

641
00:48:39,406 --> 00:48:42,940
你让我的小天使战胜了小恶魔。
You've talked me back to the side of the angels.

642
00:48:42,942 --> 00:48:44,344
下一步是什么？
What's our next step?

643
00:48:45,277 --> 00:48:46,710
我不知道。
I don't know.

644
00:48:46,712 --> 00:48:49,112
我确实在圣地看到了幻象。
I did have a vision at the shrine.

645
00:48:49,114 --> 00:48:51,214
但我无法解析它。
I just can't decipher it.

646
00:48:51,216 --> 00:48:54,053
我看到了花，我的母亲，
There were flowers, my mother,

647
00:48:54,786 --> 00:48:56,223
奇怪的鱼。
strange fish.

648
00:48:57,156 --> 00:48:58,388
真的？
Really?

649
00:48:58,390 --> 00:49:00,056
由于地中海捕鱼过度
The Mediterranean's so over-fished,

650
00:49:00,058 --> 00:49:02,426
某些鱼类已经少到只能在边缘地带生存。
certain species have been reduced to tiny pockets.

651
00:49:02,428 --> 00:49:06,065
天堂岛可能在一个符合所有这些特征的地方。
Themyscira could be the place where all those components meet.

652
00:49:08,901 --> 00:49:10,268
好吧，公主
Okay, Princess.

653
00:49:10,270 --> 00:49:12,372
哪条看起来眼熟？
Which of these looks familiar?

654
00:49:33,591 --> 00:49:36,726
“寻求就会有收获。”
"Seek and ye shall find."

655
00:49:36,728 --> 00:49:38,562
我觉得我们已经找到了。
I think we've got it.

656
00:49:38,564 --> 00:49:40,167
但是那里什么也没有。
But there's nothing there.

657
00:49:40,732 --> 00:49:41,968
几乎没有。
Almost.

658
00:49:43,136 --> 00:49:46,370
除了一个海山，就是水下岛屿。
There's a seamount, an underwater island.

659
00:49:46,372 --> 00:49:49,906
要赌一赌它在现实中是高出海平面的吗？
How much you wanna bet it's a little bit taller in real life?

660
00:49:49,908 --> 00:49:52,643
凯尔博士，你成功了。
Dr. Cale, you did it.

661
00:49:52,645 --> 00:49:53,978
<i>好极了，医生。</ i>
<i>Brava, Doctor.</i>

662
00:49:53,980 --> 00:49:56,179
<i>现在你已经找到了天堂岛，</ i>
<i>Now that you've found Themyscira,</i>

663
00:49:56,181 --> 00:49:58,382
<i>毒药博士和我也是。</ i>
<i>Dr. Poison and I have, too.</i>

664
00:49:58,384 --> 00:50:00,984
你怎么进入我们的私人服务器的？
How did you access our private server?

665
00:50:00,986 --> 00:50:03,922
<i>我不会费劲去联系你的安全团队的。</ i>
<i>I wouldn't bother calling your security team.</i>

666
00:50:03,924 --> 00:50:06,493
<i>我有你所有的访问密码。</ i>
<i>I've got all your access codes.</i>

667
00:50:08,527 --> 00:50:10,828
赛博，这些人跟你毫无过节，
Cyber, these people have done nothing to you,

668
00:50:10,830 --> 00:50:12,529
其他的亚马逊人也是。
neither have the other Amazons.

669
00:50:12,531 --> 00:50:14,431
如果你和毒药博士想报仇，那应该...
If you and Dr. Poison want vengeance, it should...

670
00:50:14,433 --> 00:50:16,500
<i>这与复仇无关。</ i>
<i>This isn't about vengeance.</i>

671
00:50:16,502 --> 00:50:17,835
<i>只与金钱有关。</ i>
<i>It's about money.</i>

672
00:50:17,837 --> 00:50:20,603
<i>我听说过亚马逊人的科技</ i>
<i>I've heard about the tech the Amazons have</i>

673
00:50:20,605 --> 00:50:23,741
<i>现在我们得到了她们的位置，</ i>
<i>and now that we have their location,</i>

674
00:50:23,743 --> 00:50:26,076
<i>就等着我们去取好了。</ i>
<i>it's ours for the taking.</i>

675
00:50:26,078 --> 00:50:30,350
<i>杀死你们所有人是笔好买卖。</ i>
<i>Killing all of you is just good business.</i>

676
00:50:32,484 --> 00:50:33,717
这下好了。
Great.

677
00:50:33,719 --> 00:50:36,085
赛博开启了污染协议。
Cyber turned on the contamination protocols.

678
00:50:36,087 --> 00:50:37,955
计算机认为有病毒在扩散，
The computer thinks a virus is loose,

679
00:50:37,957 --> 00:50:40,690
并且被命令去杀毒。
and it's been ordered to sanitize.

680
00:50:40,692 --> 00:50:44,395
这意味着这层楼都将被焚化。
It means this entire floor is about to be incinerated.

681
00:50:44,397 --> 00:50:47,100
<i>醒醒，醒醒，银天鹅。</ i>
<i>Wakey, wakey, Silver Swan.</i>

682
00:51:08,254 --> 00:51:10,190
为什么总是这么倒霉？
Why does it always get worse?

683
00:51:17,062 --> 00:51:19,763
凡妮莎，你必须听我说。
Vanessa, you have to listen to me.

684
00:51:19,765 --> 00:51:22,102
那些植入物会杀死你。
Those implants are killing you.

685
00:51:33,279 --> 00:51:34,745
我们正在努力帮你。
We're trying to help.

686
00:51:34,747 --> 00:51:35,980
你在撒谎。
You're lying.

687
00:51:35,982 --> 00:51:37,848
你想夺走我的力量
You're trying to steal my power,

688
00:51:37,850 --> 00:51:39,783
就像你偷走了我妈妈那样
just like you stole my mother.

689
00:51:39,785 --> 00:51:41,253
不是那样的
That isn't true.

690
00:51:56,502 --> 00:51:58,305
请放心，凯尔博士，你会没事的。
Don't worry, Dr. Cale, you're gonna be fine.

691
00:51:58,904 --> 00:52:00,304
多么可靠啊。
How reassuring.

692
00:52:00,306 --> 00:52:02,542
我还以为你只是个可爱的秘书。
And I thought you were just the cute secretary.

693
00:52:14,120 --> 00:52:15,886
拜托，凡妮莎。
Please, Vanessa.

694
00:52:15,888 --> 00:52:17,288
这不是真正的你
This isn't you.

695
00:52:17,290 --> 00:52:19,089
你又不了解我
You don't know me.

696
00:52:19,091 --> 00:52:20,857
我就想要这样。
I want this.

697
00:52:20,859 --> 00:52:22,192
真的吗？
Do you?

698
00:52:22,194 --> 00:52:24,331
即使如此朱莉娅也不会复活。
It won't bring Julia back.

699
00:52:33,806 --> 00:52:35,975
用枪？这也太落伍了。
Guns? So freakin' primitive.

700
00:52:56,062 --> 00:52:58,631
<i>天鹅，在她分心救人的时候离开那里。</ i>
<i>Swan, get out of there while she's distracted.</i>

701
00:53:03,002 --> 00:53:04,667
嘿，等等。我可不会飞
Hey, wait. I can't fly.

702
00:53:04,669 --> 00:53:06,071
你也得救我！
You gotta save me too!

703
00:53:16,716 --> 00:53:20,217
你必须等到千钧一发的时候才出现，不是吗？
You just had to wait for the dramatic entrance, didn't you?

704
00:53:20,219 --> 00:53:22,488
我以为你喜欢生活中来点刺激。
I thought you liked a little drama.

705
00:53:26,493 --> 00:53:28,125
我们需要搜索这层楼。
We need to search the floor.

706
00:53:28,127 --> 00:53:30,527
可能还有幸存者。
There could still be survivors.

707
00:53:30,529 --> 00:53:32,196
不用白费力气了
Don't bother.

708
00:53:32,198 --> 00:53:35,132
这一层是空的，并且与大楼其他部分隔绝。
That floor's empty and sealed off from the rest of the building.

709
00:53:35,134 --> 00:53:36,600
也是好事
Good thing, too.

710
00:53:36,602 --> 00:53:40,069
现在我的公司仅仅是被部分摧毁了。
Now my company's only partially destroyed.

711
00:53:40,071 --> 00:53:43,242
毒药和赛博可能已经对天堂岛宣战了...
Poison and Cyber may have declared war on Themyscira...

712
00:53:44,676 --> 00:53:47,243
但是如果说亚马逊人有什么特长的话，
But if there's one thing Amazons know,

713
00:53:47,245 --> 00:53:49,048
那就是作战了。
it's how to fight a war.

714
00:53:51,017 --> 00:53:53,252
现在战斗的时刻到了。
And it's time to fight.

715
00:54:00,192 --> 00:54:03,426
看来你们不会留下吃晚餐了。
I take it you won't be staying for dinner.

716
00:54:03,428 --> 00:54:04,728
是的。
No.

717
00:54:04,730 --> 00:54:08,234
但是，如果我们能带份便当，那就最好不过。
But if we could get a to-go box, that'd be great.

718
00:54:40,799 --> 00:54:43,299
下一站，天堂岛。
Next stop, Themyscira.

719
00:54:43,301 --> 00:54:45,601
希望能有个喜欢胖女人的亚马逊人。
And hopefully an Amazon who likes 'em thick.

720
00:54:45,603 --> 00:54:49,109
如果我们能幸存下来，我可以给你介绍一下。
If we survive this, I can make a few introductions.

721
00:55:02,654 --> 00:55:04,788
这次的结局不会很美好，你懂的。
This isn't gonna end well, you know.

722
00:55:04,790 --> 00:55:07,757
嗯，我们要飞往一个永生战士生活的岛屿
Well, we are flying to an island of immortal warriors

723
00:55:07,759 --> 00:55:10,426
从有剃刀翅膀的杀人机器手中拯救他们。
to save them from a razor-winged killing machine.

724
00:55:10,428 --> 00:55:12,897
但是我也不会太担心。
But I wouldn't worry too much.

725
00:55:12,899 --> 00:55:16,136
我是说戴安娜这次的结局不会很美好。
I meant this isn't going to end well for Diana.

726
00:55:18,102 --> 00:55:19,671
我知道你的意思。
I know what you meant.

727
00:55:20,739 --> 00:55:22,105
无论发生什么，
Whatever happens,

728
00:55:22,107 --> 00:55:25,341
她很可能不会再和我们一起回来了。
there's a good chance she's not coming back with us.

729
00:55:25,343 --> 00:55:28,213
除非你给她一点动力？
Unless she had a little motivation?

730
00:55:38,491 --> 00:55:41,828
你知道，我想要的正是这种让女性感到安稳的效果。
You know, that's exactly the effect I like to have on women.

731
00:55:43,328 --> 00:55:44,795
我知道有你在背后支持我。
I know you've got my back.

732
00:55:44,797 --> 00:55:47,163
但这段时间我的压力相当大。
And this has been a rather stressful time.

733
00:55:47,165 --> 00:55:48,732
你和达克赛德战斗过。
You fought Darkseid.

734
00:55:48,734 --> 00:55:50,801
这次连那次的一半都比不了。
This is, like, half as bad as that.

735
00:55:50,803 --> 00:55:52,402
最多三分之一。
A third, at best.

736
00:55:52,404 --> 00:55:54,871
另外，你这是去保卫自己的家乡。
Besides, you're gonna save your own hometown.

737
00:55:54,873 --> 00:55:58,107
如果事情顺利，她们会让你来当女王。
You play your cards right, they'll make you queen.

738
00:55:58,109 --> 00:55:59,845
她们不会让我成为女王的。
They won't make me queen.

739
00:56:01,212 --> 00:56:02,478
好吧，你说得对。
Yeah, you're right.

740
00:56:02,480 --> 00:56:04,380
也许你已经不是皇室成员了
It's not like you're already royal,

741
00:56:04,382 --> 00:56:06,016
或被众神保佑...
or blessed by the gods...

742
00:56:06,018 --> 00:56:07,583
她们不会了。
They won't.

743
00:56:07,585 --> 00:56:09,288
在我做出那些事情之后
Not after what I did.

744
00:56:11,823 --> 00:56:13,358
我偷走了这个盔甲
I stole this armor,

745
00:56:14,026 --> 00:56:15,991
还有套索，我...
the lasso, I...

746
00:56:15,993 --> 00:56:18,462
我背叛了自己的母亲。
I betrayed my own mother.

747
00:56:18,464 --> 00:56:19,962
可她放你走了。
She let you go.

748
00:56:19,964 --> 00:56:21,233
没有。
No.

749
00:56:22,067 --> 00:56:25,134
你离开后，我们打了起来。
After you left, we fought.

750
00:56:25,136 --> 00:56:28,507
我把剑对准了自己的母亲。
I turned my sword on my own mother.

751
00:56:30,542 --> 00:56:32,811
我从来没见过她像那样感到羞耻。
I've never seen her more ashamed.

752
00:56:35,147 --> 00:56:40,049
神奇女侠是凡人世界对于我的神化。
Wonder Woman is a myth man's world told itself about me.

753
00:56:40,051 --> 00:56:42,986
她不是借着夜幕掩护逃跑的叛徒。
She didn't slink away in the cover of night.

754
00:56:42,988 --> 00:56:46,491
她也没有让她的人民和母亲感到失望。
She is not a disappointment to her people, her mother.

755
00:56:47,359 --> 00:56:49,558
还管她干吗 去她们的。
Screw her. Screw them.

756
00:56:49,560 --> 00:56:53,029
凡妮莎？亚马逊人？
Vanessa? The Amazons?

757
00:56:53,031 --> 00:56:56,001
她们的生命并不比我的低贱。
Their lives can't be worth less than mine.

758
00:56:57,937 --> 00:57:00,471
也不可能比你的生命还珍贵。
They can't be worth more either.

759
00:57:00,473 --> 00:57:03,040
亚马逊人只做正确的事情。
An Amazon does what is right.

760
00:57:03,042 --> 00:57:04,410
无论付出任何代价。
No matter the cost.

761
00:57:07,046 --> 00:57:08,745
你对我来说就是整个世界，戴。
You mean the world to me, Di.

762
00:57:08,747 --> 00:57:11,884
我，我只是希望你不要这么为难自己。
I, I just wish you wouldn't be so hard on yourself.

763
00:57:14,020 --> 00:57:18,358
史蒂夫，你对我来说也意味着全世界。
Steve, you mean the world to me too.

764
00:57:24,730 --> 00:57:26,999
伙计们？
Guys?

765
00:57:31,904 --> 00:57:33,406
天堂岛。
Themyscira.

766
00:57:34,073 --> 00:57:36,005
就是这。
It's here.

767
00:57:36,007 --> 00:57:37,310
我知道的。
I know it.

768
00:57:44,817 --> 00:57:47,053
不幸的是，我们不是唯一到达的人。
Unfortunately, we're not the only ones.

769
00:58:02,602 --> 00:58:05,703
凡人世界已经发现了天堂岛。
Man's world has come to Themyscira.

770
00:58:05,705 --> 00:58:08,641
确保不要让他们的野心得逞。
Make sure they do not find it wanting.

771
00:58:25,890 --> 00:58:29,292
这就是为什么我不喜欢实地作战的原因。
This is why I don't like being in the field.

772
00:58:29,294 --> 00:58:30,960
我们又接收到另一个信号。
We've got another signal inbound.

773
00:58:30,962 --> 00:58:32,895
看来公主找到了我们。
Looks like the princess found us.

774
00:58:32,897 --> 00:58:36,667
关于这个，还言之过早。
And here I was starting to doubt them.

775
00:58:36,669 --> 00:58:39,372
凡妮莎，拖住那些英雄，好吗？
Vanessa, hold off the heroes, will you?

776
00:58:43,009 --> 00:58:45,275
我会对付前门的。
I'll take care of the front gate.

777
00:58:45,277 --> 00:58:46,844
你来准备原型。
You prep the prototype.

778
00:58:46,846 --> 00:58:50,013
我的确喜欢大规模破坏。
I do so love mass destruction.

779
00:58:50,015 --> 00:58:52,484
希望她也是这样。
Let's hope she does too.

780
00:59:09,768 --> 00:59:11,435
她要把我们撕开了！
She's gonna tear us apart!

781
00:59:12,971 --> 00:59:13,973
戴安娜，不！
Diana, no!

782
00:59:15,607 --> 00:59:17,076
只要掩护好我就行了。
Just watch my back.

783
01:00:12,531 --> 01:00:14,931
我不会再说第二遍
I will not tell you twice,

784
01:00:14,933 --> 01:00:16,466
投降吧。
surrender.

785
01:00:16,468 --> 01:00:18,603
“投降？”
"Surrender?"

786
01:00:20,071 --> 01:00:21,840
撤退！撤退！
Retreat! Retreat!

787
01:00:33,652 --> 01:00:36,856
戈耳工是不会向亚马逊人投降的。
A Gorgon does not surrender to Amazons.

788
01:00:41,593 --> 01:00:44,863
你确实是一个伟大的造物。
You truly are a magnificent creature.

789
01:00:45,730 --> 01:00:47,563
一旦把他们的技术搞到手，
Once their tech is ours,

790
01:00:47,565 --> 01:00:49,933
我要建立一支戈耳工军队
I'm going to build an army of you

791
01:00:49,935 --> 01:00:52,071
-足以...-嘘。
- strong enough to... - Shh.

792
01:00:53,471 --> 01:00:56,473
凡人总是喋喋不休。
Mortals talk too much.

793
01:00:56,475 --> 01:00:58,308
你是听命与我们的，怪物。
You serve us, monster.

794
01:00:58,310 --> 01:01:00,911
不管你打算要干什么
Whatever your plans were,

795
01:01:00,913 --> 01:01:02,145
听清楚这个，
know this,

796
01:01:02,147 --> 01:01:04,446
我是美杜莎。
I am Medusa.

797
01:01:06,417 --> 01:01:08,518
没有人能掌控我的命运。
No one controls my fate.

798
01:01:08,520 --> 01:01:11,422
没有人能抵挡我的目光。
No one holds my gaze.

799
01:01:11,424 --> 01:01:14,192
机械木偶不能。
Not you mechanical puppets.

800
01:01:17,495 --> 01:01:19,462
短视的傻瓜也不能
And not small-minded fools

801
01:01:19,464 --> 01:01:21,897
还自以为了解了和他们打交道的是谁。
who think they know what they are dealing with.

802
01:01:21,899 --> 01:01:24,266
抱歉，美杜莎。
My apologies, Medusa.

803
01:01:24,268 --> 01:01:25,534
我可以补偿你。
I can make it up to you.

804
01:01:25,536 --> 01:01:27,837
我可以使你更强大。
I can make you stronger.

805
01:01:27,839 --> 01:01:31,942
我不是来这里抢劫亚马逊人的。
I did not come here to rob the Amazons.

806
01:01:31,944 --> 01:01:34,212
看着我，可怜虫。
Look at me, wretch.

807
01:01:38,716 --> 01:01:41,217
我是来摧毁他们的。
I came to destroy them.

808
01:01:41,219 --> 01:01:42,752
不，美杜莎
No, Medusa.

809
01:01:42,754 --> 01:01:44,524
不，不要！
No, don't!

810
01:03:47,980 --> 01:03:50,882
女王，我们必须撤退。
My queen, we have to retreat.

811
01:03:53,085 --> 01:03:54,384
后退。
Fall back.

812
01:03:54,386 --> 01:03:55,685
撤到内门去。
To the inner gates.

813
01:03:55,687 --> 01:03:57,554
凡妮莎，住手。
Vanessa, stop.

814
01:03:57,556 --> 01:03:59,058
你还是可以被治好的。
You can still be healed.

815
01:04:02,093 --> 01:04:03,826
我还是你的朋友
I am still your friend.

816
01:04:03,828 --> 01:04:06,164
你真的那么傻吗
Are you really that stupid?

817
01:04:09,435 --> 01:04:11,333
这与友谊无关。
This isn't about friendship.

818
01:04:11,335 --> 01:04:12,603
与家人无关。
Or family.

819
01:04:12,605 --> 01:04:15,270
这是以眼还眼，戴安娜。
This is an eye for an eye, Diana.

820
01:04:19,277 --> 01:04:22,411
你伤害了我，现在我要伤害你。
You hurt me, and now I hurt you.

821
01:04:27,185 --> 01:04:29,321
不管你做了什么，我仍然会陪着你。
No matter what you've done, I'm still with you.

822
01:04:30,721 --> 01:04:32,424
我不会放弃你的
I won't let you go.

823
01:04:52,710 --> 01:04:54,979
后退。后退。
Fall back. Fall back.

824
01:05:05,690 --> 01:05:07,093
伟大的赫拉。
Great Hera.

825
01:05:16,401 --> 01:05:17,567
见鬼。
Shit.

826
01:05:22,573 --> 01:05:24,074
你去帮她，我能处理。
Go help her, I got this.

827
01:05:24,076 --> 01:05:25,444
但是你不知道该怎么...
But you don't know how to...

828
01:05:28,413 --> 01:05:29,982
交给我吧！
I got this!

829
01:05:38,857 --> 01:05:41,826
没有人能逃脱我的复仇。
No one escapes my vengeance.

830
01:05:44,428 --> 01:05:45,930
你不可能是她。
You can't be her.

831
01:05:46,864 --> 01:05:48,765
珀尔修斯杀死了美杜莎。
Perseus killed Medusa.

832
01:05:48,767 --> 01:05:51,967
但现在我已经重生了。
And now I've been reborn.

833
01:05:51,969 --> 01:05:54,404
仅仅是复制品的话能石化她们吗？
Could a mere replica do this?

834
01:05:56,241 --> 01:05:57,540
住手！
Stop!

835
01:05:57,542 --> 01:06:00,042
不管毒药告诉你什么，不管赛博对你做了什么，
Whatever Poison told you, whatever Cyber did to you,

836
01:06:00,044 --> 01:06:02,645
你可以有别的选择。
you can choose another path.

837
01:06:02,647 --> 01:06:05,448
没有必要与我们为敌。
We do not have to be your enemies.

838
01:06:05,450 --> 01:06:07,518
我了解亚马逊人。
I know the Amazons.

839
01:06:07,520 --> 01:06:10,587
我们一直都是敌人。
We have always been enemies.

840
01:06:10,589 --> 01:06:14,393
但如果你母亲乞求的够卑贱的话...
And if your mother begs sweetly enough...

841
01:06:14,859 --> 01:06:16,692
戴安娜
Diana.

842
01:06:16,694 --> 01:06:21,265
我保证在砍掉她的四肢前会先石化她。
I promise to turn her to stone before I take off her limbs.

843
01:06:21,267 --> 01:06:22,500
那种事...
Now that...

844
01:06:24,870 --> 01:06:26,505
我不会允许
I will not allow.

845
01:06:40,618 --> 01:06:42,020
关上大门。
Close the gates.

846
01:07:22,694 --> 01:07:24,028
不！
No!

847
01:07:34,205 --> 01:07:36,174
史蒂夫，不。别看
Steve, no. Don't look.

848
01:07:42,848 --> 01:07:45,150
你喜欢他们。
You like them.

849
01:07:46,551 --> 01:07:48,420
我必须把它记下来。
I must remember that.

850
01:08:05,036 --> 01:08:08,937
我的小可爱有非常特别的毒液。
My lovelies have very special venom.

851
01:08:08,939 --> 01:08:11,007
几乎能吞噬所有东西。
Eats through almost anything.

852
01:08:30,795 --> 01:08:32,628
众神保卫我们。
Gods defend us.

853
01:08:32,630 --> 01:08:36,266
戴安娜不可能打败那个怪物。
There's no way Diana can defeat that monster.

854
01:08:36,268 --> 01:08:38,935
-我的意思是-你说的够明白了
- I meant... - You meant what you said.

855
01:08:38,937 --> 01:08:40,803
而且你可能是对的。
And you may well be right.

856
01:08:40,805 --> 01:08:44,175
这也许不是我女儿可以打赢的战斗。
This may not be a fight my daughter can win.

857
01:09:39,630 --> 01:09:42,066
看着我，女孩。
Look at me, girl.

858
01:09:44,469 --> 01:09:46,636
放开我。
Let me go.

859
01:09:46,638 --> 01:09:48,170
我必须去看
I have to look.

860
01:09:48,172 --> 01:09:50,373
不！听我说，凡妮莎。
No! Listen to me, Vanessa.

861
01:09:50,375 --> 01:09:52,544
我不会让她伤害你。
I will not let her harm you.

862
01:09:55,313 --> 01:09:57,646
我罪有应得。
I deserve this.

863
01:09:59,216 --> 01:10:00,719
我罪有应得。
I deserve this.

864
01:10:01,419 --> 01:10:03,386
我知道你的想法。
I know you think that.

865
01:10:03,388 --> 01:10:05,454
你觉得无法达到那些爱你的人的期望。
That you're not enough for those who loved you.

866
01:10:05,456 --> 01:10:07,390
永远无法让他们满意。
That you never will be.

867
01:10:07,392 --> 01:10:09,526
我也曾有类似的害怕。
I've felt that fear too.

868
01:10:09,528 --> 01:10:11,393
但是我清楚我人生的目标，
But I knew my purpose in this life,

869
01:10:11,395 --> 01:10:13,596
以及它是否在我的能力之内，
and if it is at all in my power,

870
01:10:13,598 --> 01:10:17,534
你会活下去 活到足以找到你自己的目标。
you will survive long enough to learn yours.

871
01:10:17,536 --> 01:10:20,302
无论如何，亚马逊，
By all means, Amazon,

872
01:10:20,304 --> 01:10:23,039
强迫她不要看的企图。
try to compel her not to look.

873
01:10:23,041 --> 01:10:25,711
只会使她的心智崩溃。
It will only tear her mind apart.

874
01:10:27,011 --> 01:10:29,480
我挡在这她就无法看到你。
She can't see you through me.

875
01:10:30,014 --> 01:10:31,813
很好，英雄。
Very well, hero.

876
01:10:31,815 --> 01:10:34,353
你可以先尝尝我的凝视
You can look at me first.

877
01:10:37,922 --> 01:10:39,823
我不会。
I will not.

878
01:10:39,825 --> 01:10:42,892
看着我。
Look at me.

879
01:10:42,894 --> 01:10:46,431
我拒绝。
I refuse.

880
01:10:50,301 --> 01:10:52,470
看着我。
Look at me.

881
01:10:55,672 --> 01:10:58,341
你是傻瓜吗
Are you a fool?

882
01:10:58,343 --> 01:11:01,779
你不可能用我自己的毒液毒死我。
You can't poison me with my own venom.

883
01:11:05,850 --> 01:11:07,551
也许。
Perhaps.

884
01:11:07,553 --> 01:11:10,354
但那不是我的计划。
But that is not what I was planning.

885
01:11:25,236 --> 01:11:27,736
不！看着我！
No! Look at me!

886
01:11:27,738 --> 01:11:29,640
如你所愿。
As you wish.

887
01:12:01,072 --> 01:12:04,073
公主会战死的。
The princess cannot survive this.

888
01:12:04,075 --> 01:12:06,609
她就是这么想的。
She does not intend to.

889
01:12:06,611 --> 01:12:09,911
如果能和这个怪物同归于尽她愿意付出生命。
She will die if she can take the monster with her.

890
01:12:09,913 --> 01:12:12,350
像一个真正的亚马逊人那样。
Like a true Amazon.

891
01:12:51,790 --> 01:12:55,557
你想让我为自己选择一条路，戴安娜。
You wanted me to choose a path for myself, Diana.

892
01:12:55,559 --> 01:12:58,196
我选择和你并肩作战。
I choose to stand by you.

893
01:13:33,197 --> 01:13:35,030
抓住我的手。
Keep a hand on me.

894
01:13:35,032 --> 01:13:36,799
我会把你送到她旁边
I'll get you to her.

895
01:13:36,801 --> 01:13:38,269
剩下就交给你了。
You do the rest.

896
01:14:14,339 --> 01:14:16,172
史蒂夫。
Steve.

897
01:14:16,174 --> 01:14:17,509
不！
No!

898
01:14:35,693 --> 01:14:37,361
史蒂夫！
Steve!

899
01:14:51,475 --> 01:14:53,778
我为你感到骄傲，瓦妮莎。
I'm so proud of you, Vanessa.

900
01:14:55,313 --> 01:14:56,715
戴安娜
Diana.

901
01:15:00,785 --> 01:15:01,787
母亲，
Mother,

902
01:15:02,554 --> 01:15:04,656
我很抱歉。
I am so sorry.

903
01:15:06,491 --> 01:15:09,060
对不起，我不能成为您期望的样子。
I'm sorry I couldn't be the daughter you wanted.

904
01:15:18,568 --> 01:15:21,404
我的乖孩子
My little girl.

905
01:15:21,406 --> 01:15:24,343
你今天是一个真正的亚马逊人。
You were a true Amazon today.

906
01:15:29,980 --> 01:15:33,816
我知道他们在凡人世界中给你的头衔。
I know the title they gave you in man's world.

907
01:15:33,818 --> 01:15:36,985
这么久了，我听到它还是很难受
For so long, it was hard for me to hear

908
01:15:36,987 --> 01:15:40,424
因为那意味着你不再是我的戴安娜了，
because it meant you were not my Diana anymore,

909
01:15:41,193 --> 01:15:42,761
而是别人的。
you were theirs.

910
01:15:43,527 --> 01:15:45,130
我错了
I was so wrong.

911
01:15:46,665 --> 01:15:49,097
你配得上他们起的名字。
You have earned their name.

912
01:15:49,099 --> 01:15:50,901
你真的是
You truly are

913
01:15:51,903 --> 01:15:53,805
一个神奇女侠。
a Wonder Woman.

914
01:15:56,707 --> 01:15:59,411
我将永远是您的戴安娜。
I will always be your Diana.

915
01:16:00,510 --> 01:16:02,781
但是我是带着任务来到这里的。
But I came here with a mission.

916
01:16:05,550 --> 01:16:07,052
您会帮我们吗？
Will you help us?

917
01:16:34,612 --> 01:16:36,245
亚马逊同胞们
Amazons,

918
01:16:36,247 --> 01:16:38,047
我的姐妹们，
my sisters,

919
01:16:38,049 --> 01:16:39,716
我的朋友。
my friends.

920
01:16:39,718 --> 01:16:42,884
我们与凡人世界分隔已久。
Long have we been separated from man's world.

921
01:16:42,886 --> 01:16:44,954
开始是应众神之命，
At the behest of the gods,

922
01:16:44,956 --> 01:16:48,790
后来因为是你们女王的昏聩
and then the folly of your queen.

923
01:16:48,792 --> 01:16:53,963
但是现在，我明白我们重返尘世的时机早己经到来了。
But now, I see it is past time that we were called back into the realm.

924
01:16:53,965 --> 01:16:56,731
-我女儿很久以前就告诉过我...-恭喜了，天使。
- My daughter told me a long time ago... - Congratulations, angel.

925
01:16:56,733 --> 01:17:00,035
...众神在呼唤着我们回来。
...that the gods were calling for our return.

926
01:17:00,037 --> 01:17:04,874
那些在境外的人需要我们的帮助。
That there were those outside our borders that needed our help.

927
01:17:04,876 --> 01:17:09,411
把你们的欢呼声献给戴安娜，
Raise up your voice to Diana,

928
01:17:09,413 --> 01:17:11,713
天堂岛的捍卫者。
the champion of Themyscira.

929
01:17:11,715 --> 01:17:14,450
戴安娜万岁！
All hail Diana!

930
01:17:14,452 --> 01:17:18,320
众所周知的神奇女侠。
Known to all as Wonder Woman.

931
01:17:18,322 --> 01:17:21,490
戴安娜万岁！
All hail Diana!

932
01:17:21,492 --> 01:17:24,094
戴安娜万岁
All hail Diana.

933
01:17:41,145 --> 01:17:43,913
很高兴回到我的姐妹们中间。
It is good to be back among my sisters.

934
01:17:43,915 --> 01:17:46,982
作为我担任天堂岛保护者后的第一次活动，
And, as my first act as protector of Themyscira,

935
01:17:46,984 --> 01:17:49,418
我荣幸地宣布，
it is my honor to proclaim,

936
01:17:49,420 --> 01:17:52,556
让比赛开始吧。
let the games commence.

937
01:19:04,662 --> 01:19:06,494
好吧，福至心灵。
Well, bless your heart.

938
01:19:06,496 --> 01:19:08,263
你终于想通了。
You figured it out.

939
01:19:08,265 --> 01:19:10,768
我不得不弄瞎双眼来看清你的背叛。
I had to go blind to see your treachery.

940
01:19:11,501 --> 01:19:13,203
为什么，凯尔博士？
Why, Dr. Cale?

941
01:19:14,237 --> 01:19:15,804
因为你，亲爱的。
Because of you, dear.

942
01:19:15,806 --> 01:19:19,075
朱莉娅从未停止过赞美你那神奇的亚马逊
Julia never stopped raving about you marvelous Amazons

943
01:19:19,077 --> 01:19:22,610
那里有我梦寐以求的科技。
whose technology I couldn't even dream of.

944
01:19:22,612 --> 01:19:24,914
然而，我可以窃取它。
However, I could take it.

945
01:19:24,916 --> 01:19:27,652
但是唯一可以找到它的人
But the only person that could find it

946
01:19:28,653 --> 01:19:30,151
就是你。
was you.

947
01:19:30,153 --> 01:19:33,190
你只需要被适当的诱导就行了。
You just had to be properly motivated.

948
01:19:34,192 --> 01:19:36,892
是你杀了朱莉娅。
You killed Julia.

949
01:19:36,894 --> 01:19:40,829
<i>我不能让她看出来是我在资助毒药和赛博。</ i>
<i>I couldn't let her figure out I was bankrolling Poison and Cyber.</i>

950
01:19:40,831 --> 01:19:42,934
<i>这点甚至连凡妮莎都不知道。</ i>
<i>Not even Vanessa knew that.</i>

951
01:19:45,336 --> 01:19:49,373
凡妮莎成为我的武器，而你暴露了你的岛屿。
Vanessa became my weapon and you gave up your island.

952
01:19:50,541 --> 01:19:52,508
你的攻击失败了。
Your attack failed.

953
01:19:52,510 --> 01:19:54,643
天堂岛完好无缺。
Themyscira is whole.

954
01:19:54,645 --> 01:19:56,878
而且就在它原来的位置。
And exactly where I left it.

955
01:19:56,880 --> 01:19:58,849
我期待着去造访那里。
I'm looking forward to visiting.

956
01:20:00,852 --> 01:20:02,383
这提醒了我。
That reminds me.

957
01:20:02,385 --> 01:20:05,356
你要我给你带东西作为回报。
You asked me to bring you back something from home.

958
01:20:10,827 --> 01:20:14,530
多亏了你 我和我母亲和解了。
My mother and I are reconciled thanks to you.

959
01:20:14,532 --> 01:20:18,236
这意味着我现在正式成为天堂岛的捍卫者。
Which means I am now officially the champion of Themyscira.

960
01:20:19,737 --> 01:20:23,271
如果你想伤害我或我的朋友，
If you seek to harm it, or my friends,

961
01:20:23,273 --> 01:20:24,908
你应该有把武器。
you should have a weapon.

962
01:20:31,549 --> 01:20:34,083
你以为我被吓到了？
You think I'm intimidated?

963
01:20:34,085 --> 01:20:35,249
我已经赢了
I've won.

964
01:20:35,251 --> 01:20:37,786
我不会放过你的，神奇女侠。
I'm coming for you, Wonder Woman.

965
01:20:37,788 --> 01:20:39,887
你听见了吗，神奇女侠？
Do you hear me, Wonder Woman?

966
01:20:39,889 --> 01:20:42,660
我不会放过你的！
I am coming for you!

